[
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            7,
            -22,
            10,
            -4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker consumes 818 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Nixon is 32 years old. How much calories should Nixon consume?",
        "answer": 1636,
        "options": [
            313,
            1636,
            201,
            230,
            451
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnathan consumes 849 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Terrance is 34 years old. How much calories should Terrance consume?",
        "answer": 1698,
        "options": [
            331,
            206,
            1698,
            462,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a airpods in 34 minutes. How much time will it take for a 10 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            22,
            32,
            55,
            5,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given dogs ? 27 45 2 9 28 37 23 46 38 30 12 45 5 37 38 10 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "81.00",
            "81.00",
            "135.00",
            "27.00",
            "135.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            8,
            1,
            -2,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a tablet in 47 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            79,
            85,
            50,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 142 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            20,
            195,
            50,
            131,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Greyson and Branson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Greyson consumes 1774 calories per day whereas Branson consumes 2481 calories per day. Greyson is stronger than Branson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given kangaroos ? 41 10 45 36 13 15 48 43 47 49 7 44 41 4 27 40 17 34 27 42 16 24 44 6 21 38 30 29 43 31 15 ",
        "answer": "29.90",
        "options": [
            "119.60",
            "59.80",
            "59.80",
            "29.90",
            "59.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gael sold a book to Emery at a price of 926 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1006.52",
        "options": [
            "873.58",
            "870.30",
            "1006.52",
            "857.41",
            "890.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a laptop in 55 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            57,
            64,
            59,
            72,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Solomon consumes 528 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Kingsley is 28 years old. How much calories should Kingsley consume?",
        "answer": 1056,
        "options": [
            221,
            127,
            1056,
            176,
            289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 45 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "34*47",
        "options": [
            "34*47",
            "47*88",
            "53*64",
            "47*106",
            "54*67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 315 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            84,
            87,
            42,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Emilio and Ford are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Emilio consumes 1891 calories per day whereas Ford consumes 2019 calories per day. Emilio is more weight than Ford.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Liam by 3 years. 9 years ago Liam was 28 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "40",
            "37",
            "34",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pedro and Immanuel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pedro consumes 2790 calories per day whereas Immanuel consumes 2153 calories per day. Pedro is more weight than Immanuel.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper annealed ?",
        "answer": "4760",
        "options": [
            "244",
            "334",
            "4760",
            "199",
            "108"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Javier consumes 803 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Kareem is 37 years old. How much calories should Kareem consume?",
        "answer": 1606,
        "options": [
            434,
            190,
            237,
            1606,
            313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given human ? 3 8 43 44 10 38 40 23 47 45 9 45 25 31 34 21 46 43 24 26 28 9 47 32 36 37 43 1 27 36 7 6 44 19 16 33 ",
        "answer": "31.50",
        "options": [
            "44.00",
            "43.00",
            "36.00",
            "36.00",
            "31.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cristian and Wells are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cristian consumes 2508 calories per day whereas Wells consumes 2682 calories per day. Cristian is stronger than Wells.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            6,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Damon and Maison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Damon consumes 1686 calories per day whereas Maison consumes 2587 calories per day. Damon is more weight than Maison.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            31,
            45,
            65,
            35,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 772 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3088,
        "options": [
            6176,
            6176,
            "3088",
            6948,
            5404
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 9 watt charger charges a powerbank in 38 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            100,
            93,
            98,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            -8,
            17,
            7,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in silver is 3650. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11097",
            "343",
            "4634",
            "9478",
            "8818"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker sold a book to Billy at a price of 236 after giving 60 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "590.00",
        "options": [
            "147.50",
            "162.76",
            "159.46",
            "181.54",
            "590.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            97,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            57,
            98,
            "9"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 686 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2744,
        "options": [
            5488,
            6860,
            "2744",
            4116,
            4802
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 247 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            61,
            92,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            37,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            80,
            73,
            90,
            93,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10690",
            "7480",
            "343",
            "10283",
            "6118"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nikolai and Julio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nikolai consumes 2457 calories per day whereas Julio consumes 1509 calories per day. Nikolai is bulkier than Julio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 30 minutes. What is the temperature after 30 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            25,
            31,
            21,
            18,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "24*22",
        "options": [
            "65*58",
            "24*22",
            "48*48",
            "46*77",
            "56*64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 414 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "203",
        "options": [
            "203",
            12,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            16,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the cooler for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            78,
            60,
            75,
            56,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            153,
            123,
            132,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin sold a book to Augustine at a price of 130 after giving 30 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "185.71",
        "options": [
            "185.71",
            "104.84",
            "113.04",
            "100.00",
            "106.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            86,
            70,
            95,
            80,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            32,
            "19",
            "Not possible",
            97,
            40,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            62,
            65,
            46,
            53,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaac sold a book to Alvaro at a price of 549 after giving 47 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1035.85",
        "options": [
            "405.91",
            "398.98",
            "373.47",
            "444.53",
            "1035.85"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Javier and Alessandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Javier consumes 2528 calories per day whereas Alessandro consumes 2342 calories per day. Javier is heavier than Alessandro.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            83,
            83,
            50,
            87,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a laptop in 45 minutes. How much time will it take for a 24 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            2,
            56,
            32,
            1,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a powerbank in 49 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            94,
            87,
            56,
            64,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Declan sold a book to Jamie at a price of 715 after giving 57 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1662.79",
        "options": [
            "500.88",
            "455.41",
            "491.07",
            "1662.79",
            "556.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 460 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            57,
            2,
            "Not possible",
            12,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Owen consumes 678 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Jakob is 33 years old. How much calories should Jakob consume?",
        "answer": 1356,
        "options": [
            212,
            1356,
            256,
            377,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            62,
            72,
            66,
            36,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Abraham consumes 827 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Jerry is 24 years old. How much calories should Jerry consume?",
        "answer": 1654,
        "options": [
            223,
            445,
            299,
            1654,
            194
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            56,
            44,
            42,
            40,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derrick consumes 782 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Jericho is 30 years old. How much calories should Jericho consume?",
        "answer": 1564,
        "options": [
            285,
            167,
            209,
            440,
            1564
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nash is younger than Ramon by 1 years. 10 years ago Ramon was 25 years old. What is Nash 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "56",
            "46",
            "34",
            "47",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 401 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            26,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            "Not possible",
            41,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given cats ? 35 32 49 45 8 10 47 30 3 30 46 50 ",
        "answer": "32.08",
        "options": [
            "128.32",
            "96.24",
            "64.16",
            "64.16",
            "32.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            23,
            1922,
            1767,
            1321,
            1122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            10,
            4,
            7,
            11,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 289 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 282,
        "options": [
            202,
            282,
            159,
            416,
            469
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 406 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            87,
            99,
            94,
            "Not possible",
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 207 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            21,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            54,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matteo and Zeke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matteo consumes 1794 calories per day whereas Zeke consumes 2471 calories per day. Matteo is weaker than Zeke.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Peter and Mordechai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Peter consumes 2014 calories per day whereas Mordechai consumes 2964 calories per day. Peter is weaker than Mordechai.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 58 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            21,
            56,
            93,
            64,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a phone in 52 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            2,
            30,
            44,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Winston consumes 654 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Branson is 29 years old. How much calories should Branson consume?",
        "answer": 1308,
        "options": [
            347,
            1308,
            268,
            160,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            86,
            79,
            70,
            76,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 205 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            26,
            91,
            84,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 201 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            64,
            "Not possible",
            43,
            32,
            94,
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 251 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 244,
        "options": [
            247,
            312,
            244,
            449,
            168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "107",
            "316",
            "5940",
            "168",
            "277"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 55 * 49. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "31*26",
        "options": [
            "81*72",
            "101*59",
            "31*26",
            "78*52",
            "69*76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 241 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 230,
        "options": [
            361,
            158,
            308,
            149,
            230
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 166 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 162,
        "options": [
            319,
            162,
            146,
            20,
            318
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given dogs ? 7 12 36 48 25 20 10 5 13 25 5 31 37 21 25 1 39 48 16 37 30 41 5 45 30 1 27 34 47 4 43 36 48 21 26 10 46 18 45 32 37 8 42 33 11 7 ",
        "answer": "26.50",
        "options": [
            "5.00",
            "32.00",
            "48.00",
            "26.50",
            "37.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "River is younger than Chandler by 2 years. 6 years ago Chandler was 25 years old. What is River 's age today?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            "29",
            "33",
            "49",
            "33",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 469 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            70,
            86,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            "Not possible",
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 292 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 284,
        "options": [
            30,
            405,
            308,
            284,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Amir and Tadeo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Amir consumes 2877 calories per day whereas Tadeo consumes 2444 calories per day. Amir is weaker than Tadeo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 319 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 310,
        "options": [
            504,
            166,
            310,
            540,
            397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            104,
            109,
            113,
            114,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 313 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            10,
            16,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 76 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            92,
            64,
            67,
            118,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark sold a book to Kannon at a price of 393 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "418.09",
        "options": [
            "418.09",
            "370.75",
            "381.55",
            "376.08",
            "375.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silver ?",
        "answer": "3650",
        "options": [
            "189",
            "184",
            "311",
            "235",
            "3650"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 39. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "31*31",
        "options": [
            "61*60",
            "49*76",
            "31*31",
            "74*61",
            "63*74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in concrete ?",
        "answer": "3700",
        "options": [
            "3700",
            "333",
            "237",
            "340",
            "256"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 250 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            54,
            41,
            26,
            "Not possible",
            31,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a phone in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            46,
            7,
            3,
            14,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in molybdenum is 6250. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "8883",
            "13707",
            "11254",
            "3647"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Patrick and Moshe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Patrick consumes 1946 calories per day whereas Moshe consumes 1523 calories per day. Patrick is lighter than Moshe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 458 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            95,
            41,
            61,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Khalil and Jamie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Khalil consumes 2954 calories per day whereas Jamie consumes 2413 calories per day. Khalil is more weight than Jamie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            13,
            46,
            23,
            41,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 124 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            42,
            50,
            "Not possible",
            32,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given kangaroos ? 37 4 23 39 25 21 7 1 33 36 41 7 38 36 35 33 35 7 34 49 44 23 48 19 38 36 43 47 31 28 12 43 13 ",
        "answer": "34.00",
        "options": [
            "34.00",
            "23.00",
            "23.00",
            "7.00",
            "36.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Benjamin by 1 years. 12 years ago Benjamin was 35 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "46",
            "45",
            "57",
            "48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 306 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            33,
            76,
            87,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            "23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 87, 60, 33. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Barrett and Abdullah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Barrett consumes 1572 calories per day whereas Abdullah consumes 2695 calories per day. Barrett is stronger than Abdullah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Skyler consumes 773 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Ricky is 27 years old. How much calories should Ricky consume?",
        "answer": 1546,
        "options": [
            181,
            218,
            269,
            1546,
            408
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kairo consumes 789 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Arian is 33 years old. How much calories should Arian consume?",
        "answer": 1578,
        "options": [
            295,
            203,
            1578,
            418,
            214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            79,
            77,
            79,
            56,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 318 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 312,
        "options": [
            439,
            312,
            489,
            315,
            232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 52 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            102,
            51,
            83,
            39,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oakley and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oakley consumes 2983 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2049 calories per day. Oakley is more weight than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 82 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            128,
            79,
            88,
            130,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zachariah consumes 861 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Dane is 39 years old. How much calories should Dane consume?",
        "answer": 1722,
        "options": [
            478,
            329,
            194,
            226,
            1722
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            59,
            64,
            60,
            56,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adriel and Eliseo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adriel consumes 2383 calories per day whereas Eliseo consumes 2005 calories per day. Adriel is more weight than Eliseo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 243 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "95",
        "options": [
            36,
            74,
            38,
            "95",
            "Not possible",
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead annealed ?",
        "answer": "2160",
        "options": [
            "2160",
            "206",
            "145",
            "225",
            "263"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 51 minutes. What is the temperature after 51 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            113,
            103,
            111,
            112,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul consumes 865 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Kylen is 22 years old. How much calories should Kylen consume?",
        "answer": 1730,
        "options": [
            450,
            237,
            184,
            324,
            1730
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 255 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 245,
        "options": [
            245,
            410,
            64,
            154,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alonzo sold a book to Eugene at a price of 817 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1856.82",
        "options": [
            "523.72",
            "1856.82",
            "638.28",
            "575.35",
            "564.23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finnegan sold a book to Braydon at a price of 753 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1981.58",
        "options": [
            "503.34",
            "464.81",
            "513.99",
            "1981.58",
            "574.81"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than William by 3 years. 10 years ago William was 31 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "44",
            "32",
            "58",
            "32",
            "58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 121 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            66,
            44,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            101,
            101,
            110,
            95,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "5940",
            "227",
            "303",
            "132",
            "251"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            106,
            129,
            95,
            108,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 136 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 132,
        "options": [
            188,
            124,
            19,
            132,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rowan consumes 892 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Zev is 34 years old. How much calories should Zev consume?",
        "answer": 1784,
        "options": [
            346,
            1784,
            238,
            188,
            495
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 149 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            3,
            144,
            104,
            79,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 201 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            33,
            "23",
            "Not possible",
            35,
            40,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 246 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 235,
        "options": [
            226,
            235,
            85,
            310,
            288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Santiago and Baker are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Santiago consumes 2267 calories per day whereas Baker consumes 2770 calories per day. Santiago is less weight than Baker.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            105,
            88,
            76,
            108,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            74,
            76,
            93,
            77,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jonathan and Morgan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jonathan consumes 2228 calories per day whereas Morgan consumes 1868 calories per day. Jonathan is heavier than Morgan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 472 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            87,
            70,
            6,
            83,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derrick consumes 780 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Dash is 31 years old. How much calories should Dash consume?",
        "answer": 1560,
        "options": [
            1560,
            417,
            288,
            217,
            202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a powerbank in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            31,
            70,
            24,
            30,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            1188,
            3,
            1156,
            1351,
            1989
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rhett sold a book to Isaias at a price of 405 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1094.59",
        "options": [
            "1094.59",
            "307.98",
            "248.47",
            "269.28",
            "275.04"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 168 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            217,
            159,
            32,
            187,
            267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in monel is 5350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10000",
            "12859",
            "343",
            "14199",
            "2239"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            36,
            44,
            44,
            61,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marco is younger than Otis by 1 years. 12 years ago Otis was 34 years old. What is Marco 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "47",
            "45",
            "59",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 128 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            59,
            120,
            202,
            15,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a powerbank in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            5,
            22,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            4,
            32,
            31,
            50,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 132 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            152,
            130,
            109,
            241,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson is younger than Moshe by 1 years. 14 years ago Moshe was 35 years old. What is Lawson 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "79",
            "64",
            "48",
            "64",
            "78"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jase consumes 732 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Mauricio is 23 years old. How much calories should Mauricio consume?",
        "answer": 1464,
        "options": [
            219,
            187,
            266,
            1464,
            411
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given martians ? 19 36 47 10 15 9 3 36 24 40 4 23 8 8 20 19 22 6 ",
        "answer": "19.39",
        "options": [
            "77.56",
            "38.78",
            "96.95",
            "96.95",
            "19.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniel consumes 577 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Koda is 27 years old. How much calories should Koda consume?",
        "answer": 1154,
        "options": [
            175,
            326,
            1154,
            221,
            153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 136 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            43,
            9,
            21,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 324 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            66,
            2,
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "Not possible",
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            4111,
            4882,
            4713,
            3,
            3780
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 259 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 257,
        "options": [
            26,
            130,
            403,
            257,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            109,
            98,
            109,
            119,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given martians ? 21 34 48 22 6 47 ",
        "answer": "28.00",
        "options": [
            "6.00",
            "28.00",
            "47.00",
            "34.00",
            "6.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1009,
            7,
            18,
            15,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 659 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2636,
        "options": [
            3954,
            6590,
            5272,
            5272,
            "2636"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pierce is younger than Ramon by 1 years. 9 years ago Ramon was 31 years old. What is Pierce 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "50",
            "59",
            "59",
            "51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 119 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            52,
            21,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            "15",
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 268 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            38,
            76,
            35,
            99,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliott and Zahir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliott consumes 2189 calories per day whereas Zahir consumes 2916 calories per day. Elliott is stronger than Zahir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wyatt and Joe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wyatt consumes 2677 calories per day whereas Joe consumes 2981 calories per day. Wyatt is bulkier than Joe.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxson sold a book to Demetrius at a price of 957 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2518.42",
        "options": [
            "639.71",
            "653.24",
            "730.53",
            "590.74",
            "2518.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 55 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "54*27",
        "options": [
            "86*69",
            "72*56",
            "54*27",
            "102*47",
            "104*60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Christian and Rogelio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Christian consumes 1945 calories per day whereas Rogelio consumes 2394 calories per day. Christian is weaker than Rogelio.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a laptop in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 25 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            39,
            37,
            27,
            73,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 265 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 264,
        "options": [
            264,
            145,
            63,
            441,
            202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Milan and Nickolas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Milan consumes 2040 calories per day whereas Nickolas consumes 1721 calories per day. Milan is more weight than Nickolas.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 163 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            46,
            48,
            "17",
            4,
            32,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kash consumes 689 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Dorian is 24 years old. How much calories should Dorian consume?",
        "answer": 1378,
        "options": [
            362,
            246,
            170,
            1378,
            220
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Barrett and Titan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Barrett consumes 2820 calories per day whereas Titan consumes 1671 calories per day. Barrett is more weight than Titan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a phone in 34 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            26,
            51,
            10,
            25,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given tigers ? 21 12 34 46 37 6 24 8 31 11 39 14 3 25 24 48 25 48 38 47 7 1 12 2 14 25 11 28 37 21 37 36 1 10 47 36 ",
        "answer": "24.06",
        "options": [
            "48.12",
            "120.30",
            "72.18",
            "72.18",
            "24.06"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            483,
            577,
            642,
            2977,
            871
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conor consumes 626 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Aron is 33 years old. How much calories should Aron consume?",
        "answer": 1252,
        "options": [
            167,
            325,
            166,
            241,
            1252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kasen consumes 748 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Tristen is 30 years old. How much calories should Tristen consume?",
        "answer": 1496,
        "options": [
            391,
            267,
            189,
            1496,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 467 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            84,
            51,
            18,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            88,
            139,
            107,
            108,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cade and Mohammed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cade consumes 1891 calories per day whereas Mohammed consumes 2050 calories per day. Cade is lighter than Mohammed.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 261 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            "15",
            54,
            "Not possible",
            18,
            43,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            108,
            105,
            107,
            115,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            89,
            70,
            61,
            44,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 242 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "35",
            100,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 287 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 281,
        "options": [
            281,
            407,
            365,
            222,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 199 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            86,
            "Not possible",
            93,
            "47",
            3,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            33,
            23,
            43,
            40,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            9,
            -15,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Simon and Zechariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Simon consumes 2581 calories per day whereas Zechariah consumes 2856 calories per day. Simon is lighter than Zechariah.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 57, 54, 69. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Spencer and Yousef are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Spencer consumes 2240 calories per day whereas Yousef consumes 2355 calories per day. Spencer is more weight than Yousef.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Daniel and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Daniel consumes 2656 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 1931 calories per day. Daniel is weaker than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            144,
            124,
            131,
            140,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given martians ? 35 14 17 16 11 44 39 12 50 22 50 50 50 6 33 32 34 9 29 5 12 26 50 47 15 37 24 26 34 42 42 42 27 44 49 14 4 35 9 38 13 30 48 19 13 ",
        "answer": "30.00",
        "options": [
            "42.00",
            "44.00",
            "15.00",
            "30.00",
            "44.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 21 45 17 37 3 7 3 12 17 28 1 23 10 19 35 14 1 32 25 20 37 4 17 28 22 5 27 19 49 35 40 19 25 34 13 9 38 38 19 35 25 41 46 31 48 36 16 23 ",
        "answer": "23.94",
        "options": [
            "119.70",
            "47.88",
            "47.88",
            "47.88",
            "23.94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 501 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2004,
        "options": [
            5010,
            5010,
            4008,
            "2004",
            4509
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            68,
            59,
            72,
            68,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            66,
            71,
            75,
            94,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edward consumes 923 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Huxley is 28 years old. How much calories should Huxley consume?",
        "answer": 1846,
        "options": [
            338,
            255,
            1846,
            198,
            494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 39 minutes. What is the temperature after 39 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            9,
            13,
            14,
            16,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Braxton consumes 955 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Wayne is 21 years old. How much calories should Wayne consume?",
        "answer": 1910,
        "options": [
            202,
            494,
            1910,
            334,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maverick and Lochlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maverick consumes 2841 calories per day whereas Lochlan consumes 1949 calories per day. Maverick is stronger than Lochlan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph sold a book to Jad at a price of 663 after giving 60 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1657.50",
        "options": [
            "457.24",
            "414.38",
            "447.97",
            "1657.50",
            "510.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 237 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            31,
            55,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leon and Trent are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leon consumes 2344 calories per day whereas Trent consumes 2419 calories per day. Leon is less weight than Trent.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 261 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            80,
            86,
            24,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wade and Bodie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wade consumes 1645 calories per day whereas Bodie consumes 2546 calories per day. Wade is stronger than Bodie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Franklin and Forest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Franklin consumes 2693 calories per day whereas Forest consumes 2196 calories per day. Franklin is more weight than Forest.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rocco and Ronnie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rocco consumes 2625 calories per day whereas Ronnie consumes 2015 calories per day. Rocco is lighter than Ronnie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            74,
            "Not possible",
            "69",
            96,
            13,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in cork ?",
        "answer": "518",
        "options": [
            "319",
            "306",
            "115",
            "518",
            "252"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Samuel runs at a speed of 20 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jaxxon 's place which is 159 km away?",
        "answer": "7.95",
        "options": [
            "31.80",
            "7.95",
            "23.85",
            "31.80",
            "39.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in annealed tungsten is 5220. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8261",
            "343",
            "9372",
            "14028",
            "13428"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 318 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            12,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            "Not possible",
            74,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Emerson and Mauricio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Emerson consumes 2288 calories per day whereas Mauricio consumes 2474 calories per day. Emerson is less weight than Mauricio.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 414 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            16,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            25,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 50 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            33,
            39,
            73,
            38,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaden and Finnley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaden consumes 2409 calories per day whereas Finnley consumes 2197 calories per day. Kaden is heavier than Finnley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Luciano consumes 615 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Zain is 30 years old. How much calories should Zain consume?",
        "answer": 1230,
        "options": [
            181,
            163,
            326,
            1230,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gianni consumes 995 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Zyaire is 23 years old. How much calories should Zyaire consume?",
        "answer": 1990,
        "options": [
            1990,
            211,
            368,
            294,
            529
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Riley sold a book to Creed at a price of 185 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "284.62",
        "options": [
            "137.04",
            "284.62",
            "146.53",
            "144.53",
            "157.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun consumes 694 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Rodney is 27 years old. How much calories should Rodney consume?",
        "answer": 1388,
        "options": [
            171,
            368,
            1388,
            219,
            251
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            20,
            56,
            51,
            56,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 296 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            93,
            "39",
            62,
            81,
            61,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 83, 60, 37. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 22 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            7,
            26,
            17,
            5,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 270 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 262,
        "options": [
            268,
            188,
            45,
            339,
            262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 16 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            2,
            3,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 182 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            21,
            99,
            34,
            "7",
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elian and Archie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elian consumes 1837 calories per day whereas Archie consumes 2611 calories per day. Elian is heavier than Archie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis sold a book to Alfred at a price of 364 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "387.23",
        "options": [
            "348.33",
            "353.40",
            "387.23",
            "347.33",
            "343.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 154 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            203,
            43,
            29,
            125,
            151
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Reid and Yusuf are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Reid consumes 1617 calories per day whereas Yusuf consumes 2035 calories per day. Reid is stronger than Yusuf.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 301 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            67,
            20,
            "13",
            72,
            "Not possible",
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given dogs ? 47 3 22 16 24 46 12 48 3 41 35 13 6 41 29 32 43 13 36 44 29 36 34 32 15 4 25 20 29 12 37 44 14 17 29 43 31 ",
        "answer": "27.16",
        "options": [
            "135.80",
            "135.80",
            "27.16",
            "81.48",
            "108.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a airpods in 38 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            1,
            14,
            37,
            25,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finn cycles at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Van 's place which is 114 km away?",
        "answer": "16.29",
        "options": [
            "81.43",
            "16.29",
            "81.43",
            "48.86",
            "48.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 272 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 262,
        "options": [
            262,
            87,
            39,
            81,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kian and Kole are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kian consumes 1934 calories per day whereas Kole consumes 1524 calories per day. Kian is less weight than Kole.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber gum ?",
        "answer": "1550",
        "options": [
            "1550",
            "249",
            "198",
            "252",
            "284"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 198 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            73,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            30,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            112,
            89,
            78,
            103,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "River is younger than Dillon by 3 years. 6 years ago Dillon was 30 years old. What is River 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "54",
            "45",
            "57",
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given elephants ? 47 35 13 31 2 29 30 17 30 13 7 33 45 10 8 43 34 38 11 18 17 39 1 21 42 43 15 41 21 28 29 20 41 16 30 49 ",
        "answer": "29.00",
        "options": [
            "2.00",
            "47.00",
            "18.00",
            "17.00",
            "29.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corbin runs at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel London 's place which is 116 km away?",
        "answer": "16.57",
        "options": [
            "82.86",
            "66.29",
            "82.86",
            "16.57",
            "33.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Albert consumes 739 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Kaison is 23 years old. How much calories should Kaison consume?",
        "answer": 1478,
        "options": [
            1478,
            157,
            290,
            396,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4878",
            "989",
            "343",
            "10162",
            "13973"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 33 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "30*24",
        "options": [
            "30*24",
            "66*68",
            "56*44",
            "63*56",
            "62*42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Frederick and Azariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Frederick consumes 1945 calories per day whereas Azariah consumes 2608 calories per day. Frederick is lighter than Azariah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brandon and Maddux are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brandon consumes 2983 calories per day whereas Maddux consumes 2304 calories per day. Brandon is stronger than Maddux.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a airpods in 16 minutes. How much time will it take for a 17 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            67,
            35,
            5,
            87,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in magnesium annealed ?",
        "answer": "5770",
        "options": [
            "5770",
            "326",
            "208",
            "213",
            "289"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rowen consumes 795 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Noe is 40 years old. How much calories should Noe consume?",
        "answer": 1590,
        "options": [
            441,
            244,
            310,
            1590,
            192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Juan and Zavier are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Juan consumes 1856 calories per day whereas Zavier consumes 2819 calories per day. Juan is lighter than Zavier.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 398 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            66,
            40,
            "Not possible",
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silver ?",
        "answer": "3650",
        "options": [
            "267",
            "124",
            "3650",
            "209",
            "295"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 363 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "35",
            "Not possible",
            95,
            22,
            53,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            21,
            14,
            16,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 335 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 326,
        "options": [
            559,
            310,
            240,
            114,
            326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 839 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3356,
        "options": [
            5034,
            6712,
            8390,
            5873,
            "3356"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "121",
        "options": [
            70,
            94,
            "Not possible",
            "121",
            21,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            35,
            20,
            43,
            36,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 8 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Octagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodrigo sold a book to Konnor at a price of 570 after giving 23 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "740.26",
        "options": [
            "511.21",
            "740.26",
            "486.14",
            "481.42",
            "463.41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            33,
            "75",
            85,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Christopher and Tatum are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Christopher consumes 2257 calories per day whereas Tatum consumes 2971 calories per day. Christopher is weaker than Tatum.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 476 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "901",
        "options": [
            17,
            50,
            36,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            "901"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than James by 2 years. 5 years ago James was 34 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "37",
            "47",
            "43",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 330 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            22,
            96,
            79,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 224 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 220,
        "options": [
            220,
            119,
            41,
            351,
            303
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 368 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            94,
            5,
            "Not possible",
            1,
            "Not possible",
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            91,
            86,
            84,
            109,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            66,
            40,
            56,
            63,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given dogs ? 26 21 49 20 12 26 21 5 43 30 37 31 24 16 43 ",
        "answer": "26.93",
        "options": [
            "134.65",
            "134.65",
            "80.79",
            "26.93",
            "53.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            55,
            38,
            44,
            58,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zayn consumes 510 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Elisha is 39 years old. How much calories should Elisha consume?",
        "answer": 1020,
        "options": [
            152,
            194,
            269,
            1020,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 87 minutes. What is the temperature after 87 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            23,
            40,
            39,
            41,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximiliano consumes 815 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Toby is 28 years old. How much calories should Toby consume?",
        "answer": 1630,
        "options": [
            291,
            439,
            214,
            1630,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cody consumes 653 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Deshawn is 33 years old. How much calories should Deshawn consume?",
        "answer": 1306,
        "options": [
            141,
            1306,
            365,
            237,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            38,
            47,
            31,
            43,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            92,
            72,
            110,
            90,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximus and Braydon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximus consumes 1899 calories per day whereas Braydon consumes 2755 calories per day. Maximus is lighter than Braydon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 126 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            99,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            4,
            "57",
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in stainless steel is 5790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3051",
            "343",
            "4590",
            "14607",
            "14581"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Garrett consumes 535 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Dayton is 34 years old. How much calories should Dayton consume?",
        "answer": 1070,
        "options": [
            312,
            180,
            122,
            207,
            1070
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            65,
            84,
            74,
            72,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colt and Yael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colt consumes 1555 calories per day whereas Yael consumes 1579 calories per day. Colt is lighter than Yael.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Patrick and Sonny are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Patrick consumes 1533 calories per day whereas Sonny consumes 2513 calories per day. Patrick is less weight than Sonny.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a laptop in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            67,
            97,
            97,
            64,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dallas consumes 641 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Keenan is 34 years old. How much calories should Keenan consume?",
        "answer": 1282,
        "options": [
            182,
            158,
            1282,
            235,
            330
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conner is younger than Aron by 3 years. 6 years ago Aron was 29 years old. What is Conner 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "32",
            "38",
            "50",
            "56",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 107 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            "Not possible",
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            -4,
            -12,
            21,
            21,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 42 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            50,
            46,
            32,
            54,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leonel sold a book to Coen at a price of 733 after giving 32 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1077.94",
        "options": [
            "1077.94",
            "631.90",
            "555.30",
            "591.13",
            "583.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            118,
            79,
            84,
            87,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dexter and Idris are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dexter consumes 2828 calories per day whereas Idris consumes 2669 calories per day. Dexter is weaker than Idris.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            -8,
            0,
            -10,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 259 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            65,
            34,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 317 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            46,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "Not possible",
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in constantan ?",
        "answer": "5177",
        "options": [
            "5177",
            "329",
            "203",
            "120",
            "258"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            3,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 345 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 344,
        "options": [
            602,
            467,
            344,
            183,
            246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            65,
            56,
            54,
            53,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kasen sold a book to Mohammed at a price of 841 after giving 2 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "858.16",
        "options": [
            "827.76",
            "832.67",
            "858.16",
            "828.57",
            "824.51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a phone in 45 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            48,
            23,
            82,
            51,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            31,
            31,
            38,
            22,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            12,
            35,
            46,
            35,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 423 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            33,
            2,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            34,
            52,
            43,
            17,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            96,
            95,
            65,
            85,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shane consumes 524 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Justus is 30 years old. How much calories should Justus consume?",
        "answer": 1048,
        "options": [
            171,
            278,
            125,
            203,
            1048
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            3,
            3,
            0,
            17,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 425 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            52,
            39,
            97,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam sold a book to Bobby at a price of 906 after giving 80 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "4530.00",
        "options": [
            "552.44",
            "4530.00",
            "503.33",
            "566.25",
            "647.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezequiel consumes 983 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Brayan is 37 years old. How much calories should Brayan consume?",
        "answer": 1966,
        "options": [
            527,
            353,
            222,
            260,
            1966
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ian consumes 829 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Deshawn is 37 years old. How much calories should Deshawn consume?",
        "answer": 1658,
        "options": [
            455,
            308,
            199,
            1658,
            218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 554 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2216,
        "options": [
            2770,
            "2216",
            4432,
            4986,
            2770
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            50,
            38,
            25,
            31,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 5 years. 13 years ago Liam was 35 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            "64",
            "53",
            "64",
            "59",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Skyler consumes 673 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Brock is 37 years old. How much calories should Brock consume?",
        "answer": 1346,
        "options": [
            268,
            1346,
            170,
            200,
            383
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 142 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "229",
        "options": [
            37,
            19,
            99,
            13,
            "Not possible",
            "229"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Royce sold a book to Rene at a price of 228 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "407.14",
        "options": [
            "168.64",
            "171.43",
            "407.14",
            "158.33",
            "186.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass silicate flint is 3980. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10839",
            "398",
            "3608",
            "4133",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 646 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2584,
        "options": [
            6460,
            5168,
            3876,
            6460,
            "2584"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Victor sold a book to Gustavo at a price of 650 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "764.71",
        "options": [
            "764.71",
            "604.65",
            "565.22",
            "580.36",
            "584.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Noah by 2 years. 11 years ago Noah was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "43",
            "50",
            "35",
            "48",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            43,
            50,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            24,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 4 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Rectangle",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kayden and Marcellus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kayden consumes 1822 calories per day whereas Marcellus consumes 1980 calories per day. Kayden is more weight than Marcellus.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson consumes 933 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Cedric is 35 years old. How much calories should Cedric consume?",
        "answer": 1866,
        "options": [
            236,
            495,
            1866,
            249,
            321
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            73,
            64,
            79,
            68,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 14 watt charger charges a airpods in 54 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            63,
            42,
            72,
            70,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            66,
            79,
            85,
            93,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            100,
            108,
            106,
            132,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            63,
            59,
            60,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a airpods in 41 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            43,
            98,
            58,
            92,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 22 . We turned on the heater for 67 minutes. What is the temperature after 67 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            17,
            12,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lane consumes 796 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Conrad is 35 years old. How much calories should Conrad consume?",
        "answer": 1592,
        "options": [
            423,
            305,
            240,
            1592,
            193
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in drawn tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5410",
        "options": [
            "206",
            "218",
            "133",
            "5410",
            "217"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shawn and Joe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shawn consumes 1920 calories per day whereas Joe consumes 2545 calories per day. Shawn is lighter than Joe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 66 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            89,
            60,
            51,
            57,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kenneth consumes 570 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Layton is 28 years old. How much calories should Layton consume?",
        "answer": 1140,
        "options": [
            1140,
            169,
            318,
            147,
            233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            484,
            565,
            3,
            490,
            503
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 405 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1620,
        "options": [
            2025,
            "1620",
            3645,
            4050,
            2025
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rowen and Abdullah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rowen consumes 2707 calories per day whereas Abdullah consumes 2235 calories per day. Rowen is heavier than Abdullah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 4 . We turned on the heater for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            -17,
            14,
            -3,
            -12,
            -10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 372 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            78,
            76,
            3,
            24,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 20 . We turned on the heater for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            -4,
            19,
            23,
            19,
            -7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in cork ?",
        "answer": "518",
        "options": [
            "326",
            "141",
            "518",
            "307",
            "231"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in mercury ?",
        "answer": "1540",
        "options": [
            "178",
            "261",
            "277",
            "220",
            "1540"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the heater for 51 minutes. What is the temperature after 51 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            57,
            54,
            49,
            66,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 408 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            76,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Conor and Jaxen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Conor consumes 2369 calories per day whereas Jaxen consumes 2356 calories per day. Conor is lighter than Jaxen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Zachary is younger than Jaxx by 5 years. 13 years ago Jaxx was 25 years old. What is Zachary 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "79",
            "33",
            "74",
            "56",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brian consumes 994 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Joe is 38 years old. How much calories should Joe consume?",
        "answer": 1988,
        "options": [
            263,
            233,
            521,
            1988,
            363
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            121,
            118,
            106,
            97,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 85 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            127,
            158,
            104,
            81,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "168",
            "177",
            "125",
            "5950",
            "251"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 399 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1596,
        "options": [
            "1596",
            2394,
            2394,
            1995,
            2394
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 27 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            13,
            35,
            20,
            32,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 63 minutes. What is the temperature after 63 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            102,
            121,
            113,
            105,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 272 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "61",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            49,
            "61",
            64,
            83,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber gum is 1550. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "3758",
            "11401",
            "6592",
            "3253"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            55,
            36,
            26,
            14,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Odin sold a book to Mathew at a price of 835 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1670.00",
        "options": [
            "668.00",
            "556.67",
            "1670.00",
            "596.43",
            "607.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in concrete is 3700. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6710",
            "1473",
            "2524",
            "343",
            "5989"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ryder and Byron are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ryder consumes 2108 calories per day whereas Byron consumes 1580 calories per day. Ryder is lighter than Byron.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 356 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            73,
            27,
            40,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            94,
            101,
            108,
            103,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "309",
            "341",
            "2180",
            "257",
            "226"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass is 5640. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "1400",
            "13654",
            "1745",
            "8958"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 11 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            -19,
            -3,
            -15,
            13,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bennett and Baylor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bennett consumes 2933 calories per day whereas Baylor consumes 1618 calories per day. Bennett is weaker than Baylor.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 343 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "107",
        "options": [
            67,
            "107",
            95,
            75,
            68,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in molybdenum is 6250. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7241",
            "8543",
            "4491",
            "343",
            "6747"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            7,
            9,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 218 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            30,
            97,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 89 minutes. What is the temperature after 89 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            9,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hugo sold a book to Marcel at a price of 963 after giving 37 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1528.57",
        "options": [
            "1528.57",
            "753.82",
            "743.06",
            "812.66",
            "702.92"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 95, 58, 27. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            2977,
            2,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 166 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            159,
            69,
            92,
            185,
            190
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 122 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            62,
            "Not possible",
            98,
            40,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 11 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            0,
            7,
            21,
            8,
            -18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cristian and Joey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cristian consumes 2341 calories per day whereas Joey consumes 1698 calories per day. Cristian is heavier than Joey.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Braylen consumes 957 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Ephraim is 24 years old. How much calories should Ephraim consume?",
        "answer": 1914,
        "options": [
            218,
            1914,
            525,
            260,
            341
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joaquin sold a book to Dominik at a price of 193 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "253.95",
        "options": [
            "253.95",
            "161.91",
            "172.32",
            "163.56",
            "155.65"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 79, 42, 59. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            3176,
            2862,
            2779,
            3458,
            1009
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given martians ? 49 8 29 12 39 33 45 26 5 29 31 48 41 49 25 45 39 36 34 40 6 9 44 3 ",
        "answer": "33.50",
        "options": [
            "39.00",
            "34.00",
            "3.00",
            "49.00",
            "33.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luka and Forest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luka consumes 2405 calories per day whereas Forest consumes 1573 calories per day. Luka is heavier than Forest.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            67,
            75,
            71,
            60,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 92 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            114,
            132,
            72,
            107,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 330 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "65",
        "options": [
            40,
            73,
            "65",
            "Not possible",
            28,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 4 . We turned on the heater for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            -11,
            6,
            3,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 11 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            3,
            19,
            10,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 206 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            53,
            33,
            "23",
            93,
            "Not possible",
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 253 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            100,
            "Not possible",
            99,
            40,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 376 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            60,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            15,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott is younger than Mitchell by 5 years. 11 years ago Mitchell was 32 years old. What is Elliott 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "70",
            "53",
            "59",
            "38",
            "70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in annealed tungsten is 5220. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "7644",
            "6844",
            "10518",
            "8031"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jace and Apollo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jace consumes 2417 calories per day whereas Apollo consumes 2103 calories per day. Jace is more weight than Apollo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesus consumes 800 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Zayd is 37 years old. How much calories should Zayd consume?",
        "answer": 1600,
        "options": [
            288,
            222,
            1600,
            182,
            436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 16 watt charger charges a tablet in 53 minutes. How much time will it take for a 29 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            81,
            69,
            44,
            72,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lucite is 2680. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3711",
            "9907",
            "343",
            "5854",
            "2426"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Uriel and Ahmad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Uriel consumes 1748 calories per day whereas Ahmad consumes 2649 calories per day. Uriel is heavier than Ahmad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 464 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "211",
        "options": [
            79,
            91,
            84,
            "211",
            13,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in marbel is 3810. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12365",
            "10470",
            "343",
            "6101",
            "13850"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 353 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            55,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            24,
            "Not possible",
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 402 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "199",
        "options": [
            28,
            92,
            12,
            23,
            "199",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jorge and Rey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jorge consumes 1640 calories per day whereas Rey consumes 2605 calories per day. Jorge is heavier than Rey.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 319 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "21",
            46,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            70,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matthew and Devon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matthew consumes 1762 calories per day whereas Devon consumes 1848 calories per day. Matthew is more weight than Devon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 4 watt charger charges a phone in 45 minutes. How much time will it take for a 17 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            86,
            70,
            6,
            89,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            3437,
            3352,
            7,
            3749,
            2654
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 368 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            32,
            10,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            38,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jose sold a book to Jaxen at a price of 175 after giving 33 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "261.19",
        "options": [
            "140.28",
            "131.58",
            "150.21",
            "261.19",
            "138.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            135,
            37,
            2977,
            259,
            231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a tablet in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            78,
            63,
            45,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Holden sold a book to Flynn at a price of 430 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "494.25",
        "options": [
            "494.25",
            "391.80",
            "403.76",
            "380.53",
            "389.49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 119 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            38,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            90,
            50,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 162 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            65,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            90,
            77,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a airpods in 37 minutes. How much time will it take for a 4 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            64,
            77,
            71,
            96,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given tigers ? 28 25 6 10 42 25 26 12 32 2 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "25.00",
            "26.00",
            "32.00",
            "42.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 344 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 337,
        "options": [
            337,
            627,
            623,
            140,
            380
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Oliver by 1 years. 6 years ago Oliver was 30 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "33",
            "37",
            "40",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 72 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            1,
            126,
            67,
            123,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            88,
            95,
            85,
            89,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 223 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 215,
        "options": [
            265,
            107,
            215,
            332,
            284
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 203 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 195,
        "options": [
            20,
            108,
            374,
            195,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            7,
            29,
            40,
            41,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Royal consumes 832 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Axl is 21 years old. How much calories should Axl consume?",
        "answer": 1664,
        "options": [
            227,
            1664,
            206,
            326,
            435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            53,
            57,
            65,
            43,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Frederick and Leandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Frederick consumes 2608 calories per day whereas Leandro consumes 1782 calories per day. Frederick is more weight than Leandro.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyrie and Santana are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyrie consumes 1718 calories per day whereas Santana consumes 2667 calories per day. Kyrie is heavier than Santana.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayceon consumes 927 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Archie is 30 years old. How much calories should Archie consume?",
        "answer": 1854,
        "options": [
            357,
            226,
            259,
            1854,
            495
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Justin and Torin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Justin consumes 2402 calories per day whereas Torin consumes 2375 calories per day. Justin is less weight than Torin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luis and Layne are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luis consumes 1506 calories per day whereas Layne consumes 2851 calories per day. Luis is stronger than Layne.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaden consumes 540 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Johan is 29 years old. How much calories should Johan consume?",
        "answer": 1080,
        "options": [
            210,
            290,
            1080,
            159,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            -19,
            16,
            -15,
            -18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wesley sold a book to Dangelo at a price of 841 after giving 22 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1078.21",
        "options": [
            "689.34",
            "757.66",
            "715.14",
            "1078.21",
            "721.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            10,
            -9,
            -3,
            -3,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Asher and Archie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Asher consumes 2720 calories per day whereas Archie consumes 2454 calories per day. Asher is stronger than Archie.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            83,
            47,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a powerbank in 43 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            77,
            41,
            51,
            75,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Santiago and Magnus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Santiago consumes 2161 calories per day whereas Magnus consumes 1956 calories per day. Santiago is bulkier than Magnus.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 270 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1080,
        "options": [
            2160,
            1620,
            2160,
            "1080",
            1350
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edgar consumes 817 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Alfonso is 28 years old. How much calories should Alfonso consume?",
        "answer": 1634,
        "options": [
            188,
            230,
            451,
            1634,
            299
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            117,
            85,
            112,
            100,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cruz and Kamryn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cruz consumes 2605 calories per day whereas Kamryn consumes 2242 calories per day. Cruz is stronger than Kamryn.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Peyton and Brennan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Peyton consumes 1794 calories per day whereas Brennan consumes 2989 calories per day. Peyton is weaker than Brennan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 172 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 168,
        "options": [
            127,
            282,
            168,
            203,
            238
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 209 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            26,
            "19",
            54,
            "Not possible",
            83,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 92 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            168,
            91,
            154,
            115,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Armani and Kylan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Armani consumes 2116 calories per day whereas Kylan consumes 1601 calories per day. Armani is less weight than Kylan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 478 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            91,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iridium is 4790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10616",
            "11124",
            "3830",
            "343",
            "1137"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tate runs at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Kobe 's place which is 197 km away?",
        "answer": "24.62",
        "options": [
            "73.88",
            "73.88",
            "49.25",
            "24.62",
            "123.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            77,
            82,
            69,
            57,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jared consumes 915 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Blaze is 21 years old. How much calories should Blaze consume?",
        "answer": 1830,
        "options": [
            503,
            209,
            240,
            1830,
            319
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Esteban and Marc are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Esteban consumes 1770 calories per day whereas Marc consumes 2557 calories per day. Esteban is more weight than Marc.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Roman and Reginald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Roman consumes 2578 calories per day whereas Reginald consumes 2464 calories per day. Roman is bulkier than Reginald.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            59,
            63,
            54,
            58,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead rolled ?",
        "answer": "1960",
        "options": [
            "1960",
            "178",
            "128",
            "172",
            "208"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            65,
            60,
            96,
            55,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 133 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            20,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            79,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given martians ? 15 16 15 3 24 42 31 35 39 27 8 5 44 ",
        "answer": "23.38",
        "options": [
            "93.52",
            "23.38",
            "93.52",
            "116.90",
            "93.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Trevor and Anson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Trevor consumes 2204 calories per day whereas Anson consumes 2140 calories per day. Trevor is more weight than Anson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 161 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            75,
            "13",
            64,
            16,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 204 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            56,
            88,
            90,
            "43",
            "Not possible",
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 358 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            99,
            "Not possible",
            85,
            70,
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Antonio consumes 712 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Quentin is 33 years old. How much calories should Quentin consume?",
        "answer": 1424,
        "options": [
            274,
            178,
            386,
            1424,
            210
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            114,
            93,
            100,
            81,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lucas and Nixon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lucas consumes 2279 calories per day whereas Nixon consumes 1602 calories per day. Lucas is weaker than Nixon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in magnesium annealed ?",
        "answer": "5770",
        "options": [
            "141",
            "148",
            "5770",
            "299",
            "273"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 78, 40, 62. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            121,
            1009,
            39,
            76,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 417 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            90,
            92,
            88,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Augustus consumes 853 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Jad is 24 years old. How much calories should Jad consume?",
        "answer": 1706,
        "options": [
            1706,
            438,
            257,
            199,
            295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1476",
            "1814",
            "7870",
            "343",
            "13020"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            2,
            12,
            3,
            6,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 107 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            11,
            34,
            45,
            101,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given human ? 2 17 11 35 46 34 1 29 12 1 37 22 19 31 2 20 30 8 18 4 21 12 40 32 4 1 26 26 31 46 29 25 23 3 41 13 ",
        "answer": "21.50",
        "options": [
            "29.00",
            "21.50",
            "4.00",
            "26.00",
            "12.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            9,
            4,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the cooler for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            90,
            63,
            71,
            47,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lucite is 2680. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12436",
            "13620",
            "723",
            "343",
            "3039"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton consumes 507 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Mohammed is 23 years old. How much calories should Mohammed consume?",
        "answer": 1014,
        "options": [
            284,
            1014,
            180,
            138,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Brass ?",
        "answer": "4700",
        "options": [
            "265",
            "133",
            "4700",
            "235",
            "338"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 90 . We turned on the cooler for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 89,
        "options": [
            92,
            89,
            112,
            113,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "224",
            "113",
            "179",
            "230",
            "2180"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mario sold a book to Allan at a price of 291 after giving 71 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1003.45",
        "options": [
            "189.89",
            "170.18",
            "214.76",
            "185.59",
            "1003.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carter and Forrest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carter consumes 2937 calories per day whereas Forrest consumes 2535 calories per day. Carter is stronger than Forrest.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 5 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Pentagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 247 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            76,
            "31",
            "Not possible",
            63,
            45,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            99,
            136,
            101,
            91,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 66 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            66,
            1,
            105,
            57,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 468 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "129",
        "options": [
            "129",
            "Not possible",
            46,
            61,
            47,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cash and Kamdyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cash consumes 2049 calories per day whereas Kamdyn consumes 2122 calories per day. Cash is stronger than Kamdyn.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Lane consumes 972 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Yousef is 31 years old. How much calories should Yousef consume?",
        "answer": 1944,
        "options": [
            260,
            515,
            1944,
            210,
            362
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adrian and Axton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adrian consumes 2516 calories per day whereas Axton consumes 2108 calories per day. Adrian is less weight than Axton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 226 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            49,
            "Not possible",
            81,
            61,
            "13",
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Julius sold a book to Ty at a price of 782 after giving 32 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1150.00",
        "options": [
            "592.42",
            "630.65",
            "1150.00",
            "622.61",
            "674.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in constantan ?",
        "answer": "5177",
        "options": [
            "5177",
            "341",
            "266",
            "242",
            "208"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 436 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "169",
        "options": [
            99,
            90,
            83,
            "169",
            "Not possible",
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the heater for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            44,
            45,
            52,
            20,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeffrey sold a book to Jad at a price of 483 after giving 10 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "536.67",
        "options": [
            "536.67",
            "439.09",
            "449.30",
            "447.22",
            "460.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker sold a book to Douglas at a price of 779 after giving 66 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2291.18",
        "options": [
            "469.28",
            "585.71",
            "2291.18",
            "521.07",
            "509.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 18 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            2,
            7,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 243 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "17",
            9,
            31,
            75,
            71,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wyatt and Fox are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wyatt consumes 2260 calories per day whereas Fox consumes 1941 calories per day. Wyatt is less weight than Fox.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            70,
            87,
            85,
            86,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 135 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 128,
        "options": [
            75,
            149,
            128,
            178,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            14,
            15,
            7,
            18,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 92 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            128,
            74,
            102,
            99,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dallas consumes 761 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Issac is 34 years old. How much calories should Issac consume?",
        "answer": 1522,
        "options": [
            201,
            428,
            207,
            268,
            1522
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyson and Uriah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyson consumes 2785 calories per day whereas Uriah consumes 1581 calories per day. Kyson is heavier than Uriah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 171 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            52,
            5,
            39,
            "15",
            94,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given dogs ? 34 12 43 37 27 39 14 37 17 50 9 37 35 30 6 8 35 25 2 3 45 34 9 6 20 14 4 ",
        "answer": "23.41",
        "options": [
            "46.82",
            "23.41",
            "117.05",
            "117.05",
            "46.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "5950",
            "250",
            "331",
            "106",
            "316"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caleb and Alfonso are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caleb consumes 2523 calories per day whereas Alfonso consumes 2844 calories per day. Caleb is less weight than Alfonso.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 47 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            46,
            30,
            36,
            50,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            52,
            63,
            61,
            51,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 328,
        "options": [
            366,
            328,
            402,
            555,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 146 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            15,
            "Not possible",
            "11",
            67,
            86,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaiden sold a book to Asa at a price of 219 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "995.45",
        "options": [
            "123.03",
            "995.45",
            "134.85",
            "138.17",
            "157.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chase consumes 628 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Roy is 37 years old. How much calories should Roy consume?",
        "answer": 1256,
        "options": [
            222,
            1256,
            143,
            205,
            336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given dogs ? 50 25 19 8 36 41 28 5 ",
        "answer": "26.50",
        "options": [
            "36.00",
            "19.00",
            "26.50",
            "28.00",
            "41.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ellis consumes 770 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Quincy is 38 years old. How much calories should Quincy consume?",
        "answer": 1540,
        "options": [
            426,
            267,
            1540,
            171,
            203
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than William by 1 years. 6 years ago William was 26 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "42",
            "37",
            "33",
            "29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            37,
            30,
            45,
            20,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyler and Aries are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyler consumes 2780 calories per day whereas Aries consumes 1725 calories per day. Kyler is more weight than Aries.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 20 . We turned on the heater for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            13,
            -10,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gideon sold a book to Maurice at a price of 326 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "740.91",
        "options": [
            "254.69",
            "208.97",
            "740.91",
            "229.58",
            "225.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            21,
            14,
            23,
            37,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawrence and Khalid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawrence consumes 2543 calories per day whereas Khalid consumes 1644 calories per day. Lawrence is more weight than Khalid.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            68,
            81,
            65,
            67,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dawson and Adrien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dawson consumes 1719 calories per day whereas Adrien consumes 1767 calories per day. Dawson is lighter than Adrien.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both James and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. James consumes 2016 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 1786 calories per day. James is stronger than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass silicate flint ?",
        "answer": "3980",
        "options": [
            "321",
            "108",
            "172",
            "129",
            "3980"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the heater for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            46,
            50,
            48,
            56,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 70 minutes. What is the temperature after 70 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            15,
            -14,
            32,
            -12,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both August and Rocky are of same age. Both do same physical activity. August consumes 2389 calories per day whereas Rocky consumes 1643 calories per day. August is more weight than Rocky.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "212",
            "213",
            "5940",
            "339",
            "276"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tungsten carbide ?",
        "answer": "6655",
        "options": [
            "195",
            "6655",
            "267",
            "149",
            "306"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 237 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            94,
            30,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "19",
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kamden and Brysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kamden consumes 2181 calories per day whereas Brysen consumes 2766 calories per day. Kamden is less weight than Brysen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 300 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 299,
        "options": [
            60,
            241,
            537,
            299,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given cats ? 19 25 31 15 5 29 25 15 36 45 30 38 42 39 11 38 28 50 10 28 27 17 24 28 37 17 26 43 15 18 37 15 28 2 49 10 16 12 11 9 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "125.00",
            "100.00",
            "125.00",
            "50.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            1,
            -7,
            1,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliot and Abdullah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliot consumes 2935 calories per day whereas Abdullah consumes 1891 calories per day. Elliot is less weight than Abdullah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sage consumes 765 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Marc is 38 years old. How much calories should Marc consume?",
        "answer": 1530,
        "options": [
            223,
            199,
            295,
            1530,
            428
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nikolai and Keenan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nikolai consumes 2103 calories per day whereas Keenan consumes 2667 calories per day. Nikolai is stronger than Keenan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Liam by 3 years. 13 years ago Liam was 29 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "33",
            "36",
            "52",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Messiah and Yael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Messiah consumes 2234 calories per day whereas Yael consumes 1653 calories per day. Messiah is more weight than Yael.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 72 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            60,
            31,
            65,
            119,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 134 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 123,
        "options": [
            97,
            144,
            246,
            123,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given cats ? 13 6 43 18 6 20 35 2 ",
        "answer": "17.88",
        "options": [
            "71.52",
            "17.88",
            "53.64",
            "35.76",
            "71.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayceon consumes 905 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Tristen is 36 years old. How much calories should Tristen consume?",
        "answer": 1810,
        "options": [
            486,
            226,
            245,
            311,
            1810
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nickel ?",
        "answer": "6040",
        "options": [
            "250",
            "134",
            "294",
            "6040",
            "261"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            73,
            63,
            65,
            67,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hugo and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hugo consumes 1936 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 1658 calories per day. Hugo is stronger than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 411 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "33",
            34,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            64,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 25 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            225,
            "100",
            150,
            150,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Albert drives at a speed of 16 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Edison 's place which is 183 km away?",
        "answer": "11.44",
        "options": [
            "57.19",
            "22.88",
            "11.44",
            "22.88",
            "57.19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            142,
            2,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zachariah and Gustavo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zachariah consumes 2110 calories per day whereas Gustavo consumes 2418 calories per day. Zachariah is less weight than Gustavo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in cadmium ?",
        "answer": "2780",
        "options": [
            "2780",
            "313",
            "331",
            "133",
            "101"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean sold a book to Bridger at a price of 711 after giving 75 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2844.00",
        "options": [
            "455.04",
            "444.38",
            "406.29",
            "2844.00",
            "517.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in mercury is 1540. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7959",
            "343",
            "12771",
            "6095",
            "2858"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 301 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            31,
            34,
            80,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 134 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            45,
            "25",
            61,
            99,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Colton consumes 808 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Bronson is 27 years old. How much calories should Bronson consume?",
        "answer": 1616,
        "options": [
            202,
            422,
            247,
            284,
            1616
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given tigers ? 21 17 44 26 14 43 32 35 47 24 31 17 21 19 2 3 50 45 43 ",
        "answer": "28.11",
        "options": [
            "140.55",
            "56.22",
            "140.55",
            "28.11",
            "84.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 175 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 173,
        "options": [
            246,
            232,
            173,
            151,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given kangaroos ? 43 17 5 30 46 29 39 25 24 13 40 38 38 11 34 35 18 19 15 7 18 37 22 6 47 20 25 23 35 45 12 8 20 5 1 1 25 39 47 3 10 43 23 17 4 41 19 36 46 5 ",
        "answer": "24.18",
        "options": [
            "24.18",
            "72.54",
            "96.72",
            "48.36",
            "48.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 42 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            47,
            38,
            34,
            25,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ace and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ace consumes 2270 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 2632 calories per day. Ace is heavier than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 395 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "147",
        "options": [
            13,
            69,
            "147",
            53,
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in stainless steel ?",
        "answer": "5790",
        "options": [
            "323",
            "329",
            "217",
            "5790",
            "317"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean walks at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Case 's place which is 110 km away?",
        "answer": "9.17",
        "options": [
            "9.17",
            "45.83",
            "27.50",
            "45.83",
            "18.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kai consumes 667 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Kylo is 29 years old. How much calories should Kylo consume?",
        "answer": 1334,
        "options": [
            146,
            349,
            254,
            1334,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Atlas and Samson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Atlas consumes 2740 calories per day whereas Samson consumes 2353 calories per day. Atlas is bulkier than Samson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            11,
            28,
            45,
            37,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Braxton and Boston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Braxton consumes 1691 calories per day whereas Boston consumes 2041 calories per day. Braxton is weaker than Boston.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in constantan is 5177. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "8162",
            "11761",
            "1581",
            "9869"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brick is 4200. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "405",
            "8305",
            "6590",
            "1821"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brooks and Thatcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brooks consumes 2494 calories per day whereas Thatcher consumes 2240 calories per day. Brooks is bulkier than Thatcher.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 921 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3684,
        "options": [
            7368,
            4605,
            4605,
            "3684",
            8289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ace and Moshe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ace consumes 1975 calories per day whereas Moshe consumes 1898 calories per day. Ace is stronger than Moshe.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaiah consumes 757 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Arian is 40 years old. How much calories should Arian consume?",
        "answer": 1514,
        "options": [
            271,
            390,
            1514,
            202,
            194
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 152 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "19",
            100,
            54,
            27,
            "Not possible",
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            23,
            1243,
            1691,
            1899,
            1280
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 6 watt charger charges a phone in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            54,
            96,
            55,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass pyrex ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "159",
            "5640",
            "329",
            "224",
            "238"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            63,
            59,
            58,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Uriel and Kabir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Uriel consumes 2102 calories per day whereas Kabir consumes 2903 calories per day. Uriel is weaker than Kabir.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 364 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "141",
        "options": [
            82,
            100,
            66,
            "141",
            5,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bodhi consumes 918 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Harper is 32 years old. How much calories should Harper consume?",
        "answer": 1836,
        "options": [
            498,
            216,
            250,
            1836,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cohen and Jeffery are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cohen consumes 2568 calories per day whereas Jeffery consumes 2665 calories per day. Cohen is bulkier than Jeffery.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 53 * 51. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "44*36",
        "options": [
            "98*94",
            "68*64",
            "44*36",
            "84*76",
            "84*59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Titus sold a book to Cassius at a price of 250 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "833.33",
        "options": [
            "147.06",
            "160.26",
            "163.93",
            "185.19",
            "833.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            63,
            56,
            69,
            61,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 58, 37, 85. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            62,
            71,
            66,
            67,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 106 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            81,
            85,
            27,
            "9",
            "Not possible",
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            6,
            73,
            "Not possible",
            75,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ian consumes 601 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Brett is 31 years old. How much calories should Brett consume?",
        "answer": 1202,
        "options": [
            234,
            136,
            180,
            1202,
            323
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cayden consumes 712 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Brixton is 35 years old. How much calories should Brixton consume?",
        "answer": 1424,
        "options": [
            216,
            1424,
            183,
            395,
            261
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant consumes 656 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Cain is 31 years old. How much calories should Cain consume?",
        "answer": 1312,
        "options": [
            1312,
            370,
            183,
            148,
            251
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 445 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            48,
            81,
            42,
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Solomon and Justus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Solomon consumes 1893 calories per day whereas Justus consumes 2881 calories per day. Solomon is weaker than Justus.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            13,
            13,
            18,
            9,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            11,
            11,
            1,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10869",
            "10146",
            "343",
            "7223",
            "7389"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kasen and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kasen consumes 2402 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 2798 calories per day. Kasen is weaker than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaiah walks at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Vincenzo 's place which is 145 km away?",
        "answer": "12.08",
        "options": [
            "12.08",
            "24.17",
            "60.42",
            "36.25",
            "36.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 45 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            6,
            71,
            32,
            42,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Richard and Darren are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Richard consumes 2493 calories per day whereas Darren consumes 2201 calories per day. Richard is less weight than Darren.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Reid and Gary are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Reid consumes 2476 calories per day whereas Gary consumes 2994 calories per day. Reid is lighter than Gary.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead annealed ?",
        "answer": "2160",
        "options": [
            "139",
            "212",
            "120",
            "240",
            "2160"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 307 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 302,
        "options": [
            398,
            389,
            218,
            410,
            302
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax sold a book to Dangelo at a price of 273 after giving 64 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "758.33",
        "options": [
            "184.46",
            "758.33",
            "206.82",
            "180.56",
            "166.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            46,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            87,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Justin consumes 783 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Rogelio is 36 years old. How much calories should Rogelio consume?",
        "answer": 1566,
        "options": [
            209,
            301,
            1566,
            198,
            437
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeremy consumes 733 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Mathew is 27 years old. How much calories should Mathew consume?",
        "answer": 1466,
        "options": [
            256,
            212,
            186,
            1466,
            397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the heater for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            54,
            57,
            78,
            44,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "9182",
            "6105",
            "2382",
            "7369"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 289 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            38,
            "Not possible",
            69,
            46,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gianni and Gerald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gianni consumes 2501 calories per day whereas Gerald consumes 2718 calories per day. Gianni is bulkier than Gerald.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 348 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 343,
        "options": [
            309,
            677,
            343,
            417,
            536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1447",
            "7119",
            "343",
            "10626",
            "10462"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 155 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            4,
            74,
            19,
            "Not possible",
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            85,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            "19",
            41,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 992 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3968,
        "options": [
            4960,
            8928,
            5952,
            "3968",
            9920
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 367 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "35",
            45,
            61,
            73,
            51,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in diamond ?",
        "answer": "12000",
        "options": [
            "297",
            "220",
            "179",
            "324",
            "12000"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a phone in 42 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            58,
            32,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 272 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "123",
        "options": [
            1,
            "123",
            3,
            6,
            "Not possible",
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leland and Merrick are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leland consumes 2349 calories per day whereas Merrick consumes 1798 calories per day. Leland is lighter than Merrick.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            2,
            30,
            13,
            18,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Robert and Brixton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Robert consumes 2246 calories per day whereas Brixton consumes 1784 calories per day. Robert is weaker than Brixton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 3 years. 10 years ago Liam was 26 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "43",
            "33",
            "40",
            "39",
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 274 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "17",
            68,
            "Not possible",
            83,
            38,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            96,
            81,
            103,
            104,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 206 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 204,
        "options": [
            204,
            61,
            147,
            27,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cohen sold a book to Jefferson at a price of 568 after giving 69 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1832.26",
        "options": [
            "374.30",
            "336.09",
            "1832.26",
            "365.98",
            "422.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 322 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            59,
            77,
            14,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 150 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            88,
            68,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            43,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            6,
            7,
            6,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 2 years. 6 years ago Noah was 29 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "29",
            "35",
            "33",
            "29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason consumes 626 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Mitchell is 34 years old. How much calories should Mitchell consume?",
        "answer": 1252,
        "options": [
            340,
            1252,
            174,
            229,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ellis sold a book to Gannon at a price of 178 after giving 52 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "370.83",
        "options": [
            "117.11",
            "128.06",
            "125.71",
            "370.83",
            "141.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James consumes 950 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Zev is 33 years old. How much calories should Zev consume?",
        "answer": 1900,
        "options": [
            510,
            283,
            1900,
            359,
            213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Andy and Morgan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Andy consumes 2162 calories per day whereas Morgan consumes 2168 calories per day. Andy is more weight than Morgan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the heater for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            50,
            50,
            44,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 513 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2052,
        "options": [
            3591,
            3591,
            5130,
            3078,
            "2052"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 315 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 307,
        "options": [
            583,
            307,
            80,
            518,
            398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            89,
            63,
            54,
            4,
            "9"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            3,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Grayson and Isaias are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Grayson consumes 2965 calories per day whereas Isaias consumes 1849 calories per day. Grayson is less weight than Isaias.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Karter and Wells are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Karter consumes 2233 calories per day whereas Wells consumes 2561 calories per day. Karter is bulkier than Wells.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 168 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 163,
        "options": [
            111,
            163,
            177,
            132,
            313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Orion consumes 723 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Alec is 24 years old. How much calories should Alec consume?",
        "answer": 1446,
        "options": [
            385,
            1446,
            164,
            262,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cork is 518. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8810",
            "11303",
            "13908",
            "14780",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 194 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 776,
        "options": [
            970,
            1164,
            "776",
            1552,
            1164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 254 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 243,
        "options": [
            243,
            378,
            276,
            224,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 434 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            48,
            79,
            63,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 189 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 183,
        "options": [
            323,
            325,
            42,
            113,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 323 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            59,
            78,
            16,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            "21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leon and Marvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leon consumes 2700 calories per day whereas Marvin consumes 1595 calories per day. Leon is less weight than Marvin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 235 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            77,
            61,
            33,
            "Not possible",
            3,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andres consumes 882 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Zyaire is 33 years old. How much calories should Zyaire consume?",
        "answer": 1764,
        "options": [
            478,
            1764,
            337,
            245,
            211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the cooler for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            88,
            62,
            63,
            57,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver sold a book to Mathew at a price of 918 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2239.02",
        "options": [
            "636.40",
            "708.88",
            "577.36",
            "2239.02",
            "623.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the heater for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            42,
            35,
            52,
            67,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 228 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            37,
            "Not possible",
            43,
            "Not possible",
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 3 years. 6 years ago Noah was 32 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "44",
            "44",
            "35",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            702,
            433,
            510,
            595,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 436 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "99",
        "options": [
            "99",
            88,
            53,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jett consumes 724 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Crew is 20 years old. How much calories should Crew consume?",
        "answer": 1448,
        "options": [
            228,
            161,
            1448,
            264,
            385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            -3,
            -5,
            -25,
            5,
            -15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            37,
            46,
            40,
            64,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Uriel and Jasiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Uriel consumes 1702 calories per day whereas Jasiah consumes 1703 calories per day. Uriel is less weight than Jasiah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            27,
            95,
            4,
            "Not possible",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 435 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1740,
        "options": [
            3915,
            "1740",
            3480,
            4350,
            2610
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rowan walks at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Colson 's place which is 175 km away?",
        "answer": "14.58",
        "options": [
            "43.75",
            "14.58",
            "72.92",
            "29.17",
            "29.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jamison and Felipe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jamison consumes 2574 calories per day whereas Felipe consumes 1966 calories per day. Jamison is stronger than Felipe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawson and Jabari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawson consumes 2680 calories per day whereas Jabari consumes 2075 calories per day. Lawson is weaker than Jabari.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given dogs ? 25 46 12 3 12 15 32 6 36 22 34 12 2 28 25 48 19 28 42 38 48 17 4 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "3.00",
            "48.00",
            "46.00",
            "48.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Max sold a book to Ishaan at a price of 815 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "885.87",
        "options": [
            "783.65",
            "768.87",
            "765.98",
            "754.63",
            "885.87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayden sold a book to Danny at a price of 899 after giving 66 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2644.12",
        "options": [
            "601.34",
            "588.35",
            "675.94",
            "541.57",
            "2644.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 171 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            51,
            1,
            38,
            "Not possible",
            72,
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 961 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3844,
        "options": [
            "3844",
            7688,
            9610,
            5766,
            7688
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "27*27",
        "options": [
            "27*27",
            "53*45",
            "39*54",
            "57*66",
            "58*45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given elephants ? 42 40 45 23 44 31 11 14 21 11 24 42 36 18 2 34 5 8 50 7 20 33 42 32 4 16 15 37 4 38 21 50 40 42 9 7 13 16 46 32 1 40 23 28 11 3 8 40 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "42.00",
            "42.00",
            "50.00",
            "42.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 53 minutes. What is the temperature after 53 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            22,
            41,
            60,
            45,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 55, 60, 65. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 302 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            3,
            43,
            84,
            "31",
            29,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            2703,
            354,
            3272,
            2077,
            2173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            144,
            98,
            134,
            117,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a tablet in 53 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            88,
            78,
            77,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Edgar and Duncan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Edgar consumes 1616 calories per day whereas Duncan consumes 2888 calories per day. Edgar is more weight than Duncan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Lukas runs at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Magnus 's place which is 160 km away?",
        "answer": "16.00",
        "options": [
            "16.00",
            "80.00",
            "64.00",
            "32.00",
            "48.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 139 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            68,
            11,
            77,
            45,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            12,
            22,
            26,
            22,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 202 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            51,
            10,
            24,
            9,
            "35",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 442 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            92,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            56,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Legend and Howard are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Legend consumes 1989 calories per day whereas Howard consumes 1645 calories per day. Legend is lighter than Howard.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 411 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "109",
        "options": [
            10,
            68,
            "109",
            68,
            25,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cesar consumes 512 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Marcellus is 35 years old. How much calories should Marcellus consume?",
        "answer": 1024,
        "options": [
            184,
            172,
            131,
            1024,
            271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Orlando at a price of 549 after giving 64 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1525.00",
        "options": [
            "415.91",
            "334.76",
            "1525.00",
            "370.95",
            "363.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            138,
            125,
            2977,
            127,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 130 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 127,
        "options": [
            10,
            88,
            127,
            1,
            250
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leo and Raul are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leo consumes 2221 calories per day whereas Raul consumes 2160 calories per day. Leo is bulkier than Raul.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given tigers ? 29 11 4 18 13 43 14 4 ",
        "answer": "13.50",
        "options": [
            "29.00",
            "13.50",
            "14.00",
            "18.00",
            "4.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "John consumes 515 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Maddux is 39 years old. How much calories should Maddux consume?",
        "answer": 1030,
        "options": [
            282,
            145,
            146,
            185,
            1030
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a powerbank in 36 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            17,
            13,
            41,
            7,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 70, 41, 69. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 146 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            54,
            144,
            199,
            90,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen sold a book to Jasiah at a price of 571 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "722.78",
        "options": [
            "471.90",
            "488.87",
            "516.74",
            "722.78",
            "493.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 213 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            83,
            24,
            44,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arthur sold a book to Nickolas at a price of 518 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "539.58",
        "options": [
            "498.08",
            "539.58",
            "501.94",
            "507.84",
            "502.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "August consumes 789 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Lance is 22 years old. How much calories should Lance consume?",
        "answer": 1578,
        "options": [
            184,
            432,
            288,
            1578,
            228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            5,
            6,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andy is younger than Darwin by 3 years. 8 years ago Darwin was 30 years old. What is Andy 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "49",
            "55",
            "35",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joshua sold a book to Benicio at a price of 169 after giving 55 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "375.56",
        "options": [
            "119.65",
            "117.36",
            "375.56",
            "109.03",
            "132.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ivan sold a book to Willie at a price of 742 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2853.85",
        "options": [
            "541.61",
            "2853.85",
            "477.17",
            "466.08",
            "426.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in constantan is 5177. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3184",
            "7968",
            "5495",
            "7067",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 441 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            76,
            30,
            "19",
            "Not possible",
            30,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 190 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 183,
        "options": [
            287,
            178,
            300,
            278,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 136 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            71,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            96,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Orion consumes 865 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Brysen is 26 years old. How much calories should Brysen consume?",
        "answer": 1730,
        "options": [
            231,
            214,
            320,
            1730,
            480
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            57,
            53,
            57,
            56,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a airpods in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            85,
            95,
            86,
            22,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 233 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 222,
        "options": [
            341,
            222,
            77,
            209,
            415
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a powerbank in 49 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            55,
            24,
            2,
            43,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 466 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            34,
            95,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            "Not possible",
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kashton consumes 683 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Fletcher is 38 years old. How much calories should Fletcher consume?",
        "answer": 1366,
        "options": [
            207,
            277,
            1366,
            166,
            355
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 463 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1852,
        "options": [
            2315,
            4630,
            "1852",
            3241,
            2315
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eduardo and Larry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eduardo consumes 2112 calories per day whereas Larry consumes 2191 calories per day. Eduardo is more weight than Larry.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            3146,
            3357,
            3189,
            3277,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 281 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 278,
        "options": [
            151,
            528,
            278,
            131,
            398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            119,
            106,
            119,
            99,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chase sold a book to Saul at a price of 170 after giving 19 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "209.88",
        "options": [
            "155.25",
            "147.57",
            "142.86",
            "209.88",
            "148.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston consumes 594 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Marcelo is 40 years old. How much calories should Marcelo consume?",
        "answer": 1188,
        "options": [
            162,
            226,
            1188,
            137,
            343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "317",
            "295",
            "3960",
            "253",
            "277"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 139 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            99,
            29,
            7,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given human ? 43 17 10 2 26 18 20 23 10 15 18 13 40 28 5 28 20 4 34 13 19 3 18 39 46 36 40 ",
        "answer": "21.78",
        "options": [
            "21.78",
            "108.90",
            "43.56",
            "65.34",
            "108.90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3127",
            "343",
            "5843",
            "11608",
            "5023"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 33 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "27*25",
        "options": [
            "27*25",
            "65*38",
            "49*34",
            "38*49",
            "60*58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leon and Stefan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leon consumes 1689 calories per day whereas Stefan consumes 1643 calories per day. Leon is weaker than Stefan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Noah by 5 years. 14 years ago Noah was 31 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            "44",
            "44",
            "50",
            "44",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            86,
            84,
            99,
            82,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dante consumes 806 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Lance is 25 years old. How much calories should Lance consume?",
        "answer": 1612,
        "options": [
            442,
            1612,
            218,
            196,
            314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 14 watt charger charges a phone in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            12,
            38,
            45,
            15,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ari and Madden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ari consumes 1542 calories per day whereas Madden consumes 1753 calories per day. Ari is lighter than Madden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 190 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            48,
            75,
            "11",
            "Not possible",
            59,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 42 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            3,
            20,
            39,
            40,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            51,
            "Not possible",
            75,
            45,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a airpods in 25 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            74,
            29,
            9,
            49,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 51 minutes. What is the temperature after 51 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            123,
            118,
            115,
            115,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            100,
            31,
            "39",
            49,
            "Not possible",
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            46,
            44,
            60,
            77,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnathan sold a book to Chaim at a price of 263 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "320.73",
        "options": [
            "231.72",
            "320.73",
            "222.88",
            "229.90",
            "241.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 341 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            8,
            54,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            9,
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a laptop in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 13 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            52,
            45,
            40,
            23,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Max consumes 526 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Coleman is 20 years old. How much calories should Coleman consume?",
        "answer": 1052,
        "options": [
            301,
            144,
            139,
            1052,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaylen consumes 987 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Wayne is 28 years old. How much calories should Wayne consume?",
        "answer": 1974,
        "options": [
            524,
            236,
            259,
            343,
            1974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tanner and Harley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tanner consumes 1688 calories per day whereas Harley consumes 2502 calories per day. Tanner is more weight than Harley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Beckham is younger than Rene by 1 years. 11 years ago Rene was 30 years old. What is Beckham 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "66",
            "64",
            "65",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            20,
            18,
            8,
            1979,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 320 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 312,
        "options": [
            292,
            312,
            60,
            604,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            64,
            "15",
            "Not possible",
            37,
            68,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "5940",
            "100",
            "219",
            "192",
            "136"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell consumes 714 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Forest is 33 years old. How much calories should Forest consume?",
        "answer": 1428,
        "options": [
            1428,
            200,
            268,
            390,
            179
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron cast ?",
        "answer": "4994",
        "options": [
            "177",
            "295",
            "126",
            "4994",
            "219"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damon consumes 574 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Ulises is 38 years old. How much calories should Ulises consume?",
        "answer": 1148,
        "options": [
            211,
            320,
            181,
            1148,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pablo consumes 650 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Terrence is 30 years old. How much calories should Terrence consume?",
        "answer": 1300,
        "options": [
            1300,
            166,
            249,
            204,
            348
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 5 watt charger charges a airpods in 59 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            7,
            41,
            59,
            22,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber gum ?",
        "answer": "1550",
        "options": [
            "205",
            "167",
            "320",
            "319",
            "1550"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            94,
            84,
            100,
            7,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            39,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            27,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 491 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            89,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            18,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            66,
            67,
            64,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles sold a book to Jedidiah at a price of 736 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1226.67",
        "options": [
            "1226.67",
            "566.15",
            "557.58",
            "525.71",
            "613.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            136,
            117,
            105,
            116,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rocco and Keith are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rocco consumes 1731 calories per day whereas Keith consumes 2129 calories per day. Rocco is less weight than Keith.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nickel ?",
        "answer": "6040",
        "options": [
            "239",
            "6040",
            "158",
            "188",
            "161"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaden and Yehuda are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaden consumes 2067 calories per day whereas Yehuda consumes 2945 calories per day. Jaden is bulkier than Yehuda.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hendrix and Benicio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hendrix consumes 1531 calories per day whereas Benicio consumes 2518 calories per day. Hendrix is weaker than Benicio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Seth and Jaziel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Seth consumes 2545 calories per day whereas Jaziel consumes 1934 calories per day. Seth is heavier than Jaziel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Knox sold a book to Douglas at a price of 145 after giving 16 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "172.62",
        "options": [
            "134.26",
            "128.55",
            "125.00",
            "172.62",
            "129.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            -13,
            -22,
            0,
            -4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malachi consumes 850 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Elon is 36 years old. How much calories should Elon consume?",
        "answer": 1700,
        "options": [
            439,
            191,
            1700,
            227,
            301
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than William by 5 years. 13 years ago William was 25 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "43",
            "46",
            "28",
            "28",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patrick sold a book to Marcel at a price of 179 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "436.59",
        "options": [
            "124.09",
            "112.58",
            "121.60",
            "138.22",
            "436.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            4969,
            3471,
            142,
            4130,
            3447
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximilian and Isaias are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximilian consumes 2429 calories per day whereas Isaias consumes 2316 calories per day. Maximilian is heavier than Isaias.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            81,
            100,
            77,
            84,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 26 watt charger charges a laptop in 38 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            52,
            4,
            31,
            10,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            646,
            620,
            508,
            690,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            9,
            -10,
            20,
            2,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rylan sold a book to Braylon at a price of 468 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "472.73",
        "options": [
            "465.67",
            "463.37",
            "464.52",
            "464.29",
            "472.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 227 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 219,
        "options": [
            82,
            395,
            219,
            378,
            275
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            35,
            54,
            38,
            10,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damian consumes 942 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Kendall is 32 years old. How much calories should Kendall consume?",
        "answer": 1884,
        "options": [
            1884,
            203,
            258,
            349,
            517
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            72,
            "Not possible",
            63,
            54,
            58,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than James by 5 years. 5 years ago James was 32 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "27",
            "32",
            "32",
            "42",
            "22"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            23,
            154,
            238,
            173,
            206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 182 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            "11",
            65,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            46,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 422 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            55,
            72,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            58,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            95,
            91,
            87,
            88,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 399 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            48,
            "75",
            "Not possible",
            11,
            7,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton sold a book to Dariel at a price of 467 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "591.14",
        "options": [
            "591.14",
            "403.46",
            "399.83",
            "422.62",
            "385.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronin and Quincy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronin consumes 2610 calories per day whereas Quincy consumes 2143 calories per day. Ronin is weaker than Quincy.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            2550,
            2131,
            12,
            3010,
            3429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 14 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            8,
            -1,
            13,
            11,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Anthony and Ralph are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Anthony consumes 2765 calories per day whereas Ralph consumes 1789 calories per day. Anthony is weaker than Ralph.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            24,
            29,
            50,
            34,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathaniel sold a book to Alessandro at a price of 801 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1013.92",
        "options": [
            "692.01",
            "661.98",
            "724.89",
            "1013.92",
            "685.79"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 292 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "93",
        "options": [
            16,
            8,
            "Not possible",
            44,
            "93",
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 49 * 46. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "30*31",
        "options": [
            "89*70",
            "92*61",
            "73*91",
            "73*66",
            "30*31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            100,
            102,
            95,
            105,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            1,
            14,
            28,
            29,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 31 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "27*34",
        "options": [
            "45*82",
            "63*82",
            "40*51",
            "27*34",
            "51*67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 117 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            74,
            47,
            48,
            10,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 121 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            174,
            69,
            105,
            120,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Deacon sold a book to Lian at a price of 283 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "332.94",
        "options": [
            "332.94",
            "263.26",
            "246.09",
            "252.68",
            "254.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James sold a book to Skylar at a price of 355 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "724.49",
        "options": [
            "724.49",
            "235.10",
            "282.87",
            "256.78",
            "252.13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zion runs at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Kaiser 's place which is 189 km away?",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "81.00",
            "108.00",
            "81.00",
            "54.00",
            "27.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 113 minutes. What is the temperature after 113 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            4,
            15,
            7,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zaiden and Cassius are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zaiden consumes 2444 calories per day whereas Cassius consumes 2458 calories per day. Zaiden is heavier than Cassius.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            22,
            21,
            12,
            26,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            24,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            75,
            "21",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lucas consumes 703 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Deangelo is 32 years old. How much calories should Deangelo consume?",
        "answer": 1406,
        "options": [
            266,
            1406,
            184,
            216,
            397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both River and Rey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. River consumes 2183 calories per day whereas Rey consumes 2368 calories per day. River is stronger than Rey.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaleb and Boston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaleb consumes 2956 calories per day whereas Boston consumes 2674 calories per day. Kaleb is weaker than Boston.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 310 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "101",
        "options": [
            "101",
            91,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            52,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 233 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 231,
        "options": [
            44,
            405,
            231,
            268,
            260
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given cats ? 49 49 32 48 11 18 15 30 5 3 6 4 45 36 15 15 14 19 27 3 29 ",
        "answer": "22.52",
        "options": [
            "45.04",
            "67.56",
            "22.52",
            "90.08",
            "67.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            17,
            22,
            6,
            18,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximilian consumes 958 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Tony is 34 years old. How much calories should Tony consume?",
        "answer": 1916,
        "options": [
            512,
            1916,
            343,
            223,
            282
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 87 minutes. What is the temperature after 87 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            33,
            48,
            40,
            66,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            137,
            124,
            105,
            126,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            92,
            114,
            114,
            104,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan consumes 660 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Davian is 30 years old. How much calories should Davian consume?",
        "answer": 1320,
        "options": [
            257,
            1320,
            359,
            149,
            195
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            -12,
            -11,
            18,
            -3,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kameron is younger than Valentino by 5 years. 14 years ago Valentino was 30 years old. What is Kameron 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "73",
            "59",
            "54",
            "54",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 46 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            78,
            71,
            2,
            44,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 140 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 135,
        "options": [
            129,
            210,
            153,
            135,
            214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 40. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "34*27",
        "options": [
            "51*60",
            "34*27",
            "69*58",
            "55*45",
            "63*42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joshua and Mauricio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joshua consumes 2508 calories per day whereas Mauricio consumes 2216 calories per day. Joshua is weaker than Mauricio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            10,
            -8,
            19,
            5,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caden sold a book to Roy at a price of 621 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "697.75",
        "options": [
            "559.46",
            "570.77",
            "573.67",
            "697.75",
            "588.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4827",
            "343",
            "10655",
            "5848",
            "2823"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both James and Reyansh are of same age. Both do same physical activity. James consumes 1992 calories per day whereas Reyansh consumes 2015 calories per day. James is lighter than Reyansh.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmanuel consumes 735 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Javion is 35 years old. How much calories should Javion consume?",
        "answer": 1470,
        "options": [
            1470,
            275,
            199,
            172,
            390
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jameson consumes 883 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Rocky is 31 years old. How much calories should Rocky consume?",
        "answer": 1766,
        "options": [
            490,
            239,
            324,
            1766,
            195
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Christopher and Tristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Christopher consumes 1689 calories per day whereas Tristian consumes 2396 calories per day. Christopher is weaker than Tristian.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a phone in 23 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            84,
            7,
            43,
            26,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 272 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 268,
        "options": [
            267,
            215,
            268,
            171,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given kangaroos ? 20 19 12 2 24 50 31 1 37 8 7 34 47 8 4 43 49 3 11 1 27 39 50 17 33 41 15 45 8 28 36 7 33 42 7 ",
        "answer": "23.97",
        "options": [
            "119.85",
            "23.97",
            "71.91",
            "71.91",
            "119.85"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 39 minutes. What is the temperature after 39 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            74,
            71,
            68,
            72,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            0,
            -5,
            14,
            -12,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Emmett and Terrell are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Emmett consumes 1713 calories per day whereas Terrell consumes 2283 calories per day. Emmett is weaker than Terrell.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Xavier and Trent are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Xavier consumes 2058 calories per day whereas Trent consumes 2475 calories per day. Xavier is stronger than Trent.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 100, 30, 50. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in ivory is 3010. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10885",
            "3620",
            "10056",
            "343",
            "4401"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reid sold a book to Boone at a price of 875 after giving 75 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3500.00",
        "options": [
            "560.00",
            "546.88",
            "636.36",
            "3500.00",
            "500.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ellis consumes 618 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Trace is 32 years old. How much calories should Trace consume?",
        "answer": 1236,
        "options": [
            240,
            1236,
            133,
            168,
            357
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dominic is younger than Cory by 3 years. 7 years ago Cory was 26 years old. What is Dominic 's age today?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            "30",
            "56",
            "46",
            "36",
            "36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall is younger than Shiloh by 1 years. 15 years ago Shiloh was 28 years old. What is Marshall 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "42",
            "75",
            "44",
            "76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nash consumes 586 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Mohammad is 25 years old. How much calories should Mohammad consume?",
        "answer": 1172,
        "options": [
            147,
            218,
            1172,
            322,
            182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than William by 2 years. 12 years ago William was 33 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            "51",
            "43",
            "47",
            "51",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given cats ? 46 1 46 48 14 41 23 31 48 38 8 24 49 17 49 34 40 4 45 2 17 31 4 48 10 10 21 24 21 31 4 15 1 34 23 46 25 14 35 45 42 38 ",
        "answer": "27.31",
        "options": [
            "136.55",
            "54.62",
            "109.24",
            "27.31",
            "81.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            83,
            77,
            85,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            33,
            46,
            60,
            41,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maddox consumes 817 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Jairo is 27 years old. How much calories should Jairo consume?",
        "answer": 1634,
        "options": [
            205,
            215,
            1634,
            294,
            436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hector and Marley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hector consumes 1985 calories per day whereas Marley consumes 1898 calories per day. Hector is lighter than Marley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "335",
            "233",
            "205",
            "119",
            "5100"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace sold a book to Bobby at a price of 808 after giving 29 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1138.03",
        "options": [
            "705.68",
            "626.36",
            "663.66",
            "1138.03",
            "655.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bentley and Kase are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bentley consumes 2982 calories per day whereas Kase consumes 2957 calories per day. Bentley is heavier than Kase.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            115,
            104,
            103,
            100,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 110 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            19,
            106,
            42,
            46,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            56,
            53,
            51,
            79,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyle sold a book to Westin at a price of 903 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1672.22",
        "options": [
            "618.49",
            "734.15",
            "1672.22",
            "660.09",
            "671.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Amir sold a book to Castiel at a price of 639 after giving 2 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "652.04",
        "options": [
            "652.04",
            "626.47",
            "629.56",
            "632.67",
            "628.94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 79, 44, 57. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Javier consumes 783 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Fletcher is 27 years old. How much calories should Fletcher consume?",
        "answer": 1566,
        "options": [
            234,
            198,
            276,
            1566,
            426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 491 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            19,
            18,
            80,
            80,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Owen and Raphael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Owen consumes 1546 calories per day whereas Raphael consumes 1564 calories per day. Owen is bulkier than Raphael.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            12,
            38,
            22,
            27,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gunnar and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gunnar consumes 1726 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 1999 calories per day. Gunnar is weaker than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in copper annealed is 4760. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4294",
            "7865",
            "11930",
            "5324",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Iker and Jerome are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Iker consumes 1654 calories per day whereas Jerome consumes 2363 calories per day. Iker is more weight than Jerome.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaxon and Coen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaxon consumes 2072 calories per day whereas Coen consumes 2190 calories per day. Jaxon is weaker than Coen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a tablet in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            99,
            99,
            25,
            68,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Roman and Houston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Roman consumes 2755 calories per day whereas Houston consumes 1733 calories per day. Roman is less weight than Houston.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a airpods in 43 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            90,
            46,
            54,
            14,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brady consumes 696 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Zev is 40 years old. How much calories should Zev consume?",
        "answer": 1392,
        "options": [
            281,
            152,
            1392,
            192,
            398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12482",
            "12312",
            "343",
            "3094",
            "12579"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 328 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            72,
            "Not possible",
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in diamond is 12000. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11063",
            "12525",
            "9422",
            "11335",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            77,
            99,
            93,
            59,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 289 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "167",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            63,
            94,
            77,
            93,
            "167"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 191 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 187,
        "options": [
            185,
            140,
            19,
            187,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nico drives at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Ricky 's place which is 149 km away?",
        "answer": "7.84",
        "options": [
            "15.68",
            "15.68",
            "31.37",
            "39.21",
            "7.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given dogs ? 35 17 19 34 13 18 5 49 6 34 23 33 41 23 39 17 14 15 50 13 11 39 14 30 22 2 44 4 47 15 18 46 18 50 39 40 ",
        "answer": "22.50",
        "options": [
            "30.00",
            "5.00",
            "34.00",
            "39.00",
            "22.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 259 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 249,
        "options": [
            269,
            452,
            366,
            342,
            249
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 455 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            40,
            60,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in ivory is 3010. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2083",
            "7937",
            "13253",
            "10731",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 47 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "40*31",
        "options": [
            "40*31",
            "95*47",
            "61*63",
            "68*57",
            "86*55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tristan and Titan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tristan consumes 2394 calories per day whereas Titan consumes 2333 calories per day. Tristan is lighter than Titan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 59. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "33*31",
        "options": [
            "33*31",
            "61*91",
            "53*103",
            "54*116",
            "68*107"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            102,
            114,
            143,
            118,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caleb and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caleb consumes 2877 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 2677 calories per day. Caleb is lighter than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in slate ?",
        "answer": "4510",
        "options": [
            "139",
            "228",
            "4510",
            "246",
            "219"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "3960",
            "162",
            "246",
            "172",
            "267"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            42,
            22,
            50,
            37,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Easton consumes 610 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Julio is 23 years old. How much calories should Julio consume?",
        "answer": 1220,
        "options": [
            138,
            164,
            239,
            1220,
            328
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            63,
            77,
            65,
            51,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            149,
            128,
            115,
            123,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jett consumes 940 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Harry is 21 years old. How much calories should Harry consume?",
        "answer": 1880,
        "options": [
            208,
            342,
            481,
            1880,
            259
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            4,
            11,
            3,
            10,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 299 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 298,
        "options": [
            492,
            31,
            298,
            402,
            420
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11607",
            "9582",
            "2543",
            "343",
            "4625"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 490 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            "Not possible",
            73,
            60,
            92,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            51,
            88,
            9,
            "Not possible",
            32,
            "21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            72,
            83,
            84,
            83,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Armando and Valentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Armando consumes 2493 calories per day whereas Valentin consumes 2607 calories per day. Armando is bulkier than Valentin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Lincoln drives at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Saint 's place which is 160 km away?",
        "answer": "16.00",
        "options": [
            "64.00",
            "48.00",
            "64.00",
            "80.00",
            "16.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Austin and Landyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Austin consumes 2470 calories per day whereas Landyn consumes 1880 calories per day. Austin is bulkier than Landyn.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            91,
            96,
            104,
            101,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lead rolled is 1960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12986",
            "12338",
            "11909",
            "11737",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 188 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            7,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "Not possible",
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given human ? 39 39 6 9 14 39 16 13 27 46 1 27 27 12 4 46 14 46 39 39 28 6 42 12 23 41 13 47 29 9 37 20 5 13 27 19 15 39 40 36 8 35 46 12 27 41 29 ",
        "answer": "25.57",
        "options": [
            "76.71",
            "76.71",
            "102.28",
            "102.28",
            "25.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 51 minutes. What is the temperature after 51 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            116,
            112,
            115,
            114,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 91 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            92,
            105,
            119,
            98,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 365 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            53,
            "Not possible",
            63,
            35,
            91,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2977,
            3,
            6,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 286 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            74,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            64,
            57,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            73,
            64,
            69,
            69,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 327 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 316,
        "options": [
            227,
            230,
            296,
            58,
            316
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 77 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            89,
            46,
            136,
            68,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brayden sold a book to Gerald at a price of 472 after giving 34 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "715.15",
        "options": [
            "371.07",
            "352.24",
            "376.10",
            "715.15",
            "403.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 20 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            26,
            17,
            12,
            13,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 32, 43, 105. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            7,
            -15,
            4,
            -4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 240 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 238,
        "options": [
            238,
            302,
            299,
            74,
            475
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 130 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            79,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            88,
            "Not possible",
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Amir and Kellan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Amir consumes 2842 calories per day whereas Kellan consumes 1789 calories per day. Amir is weaker than Kellan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "260",
            "122",
            "111",
            "270",
            "3350"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bryan and Franco are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bryan consumes 2634 calories per day whereas Franco consumes 2910 calories per day. Bryan is heavier than Franco.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 916 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3664,
        "options": [
            6412,
            "3664",
            7328,
            4580,
            4580
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a laptop in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 15 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            90,
            73,
            82,
            94,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a phone in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 12 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            59,
            75,
            69,
            37,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            102,
            86,
            65,
            62,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 77, 34, 69. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            1304,
            1870,
            3,
            1941,
            1844
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            102,
            101,
            127,
            114,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Theo walks at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Santana 's place which is 161 km away?",
        "answer": "8.47",
        "options": [
            "33.89",
            "16.95",
            "8.47",
            "42.37",
            "33.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jared consumes 991 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Mustafa is 36 years old. How much calories should Mustafa consume?",
        "answer": 1982,
        "options": [
            370,
            262,
            540,
            245,
            1982
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joaquin consumes 967 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Raul is 26 years old. How much calories should Raul consume?",
        "answer": 1934,
        "options": [
            280,
            339,
            203,
            1934,
            528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 32 17 35 14 28 27 39 35 38 35 46 5 49 47 40 20 9 7 49 16 46 50 37 36 45 1 4 29 33 29 13 ",
        "answer": "29.39",
        "options": [
            "117.56",
            "58.78",
            "146.95",
            "29.39",
            "88.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliot consumes 803 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Blaze is 24 years old. How much calories should Blaze consume?",
        "answer": 1606,
        "options": [
            200,
            222,
            1606,
            443,
            299
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 224 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            85,
            88,
            20,
            25,
            "37",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 253 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            72,
            75,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            "Not possible",
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in diamond ?",
        "answer": "12000",
        "options": [
            "321",
            "12000",
            "217",
            "301",
            "288"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pedro sold a book to Camdyn at a price of 712 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1206.78",
        "options": [
            "544.55",
            "590.87",
            "536.14",
            "504.96",
            "1206.78"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            24,
            29,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 102 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            108,
            108,
            104,
            100,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gage and Alberto are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gage consumes 1585 calories per day whereas Alberto consumes 1963 calories per day. Gage is weaker than Alberto.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 191 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            17,
            70,
            "Not possible",
            78,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a tablet in 12 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            7,
            3,
            19,
            8,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William consumes 524 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Aydin is 24 years old. How much calories should Aydin consume?",
        "answer": 1048,
        "options": [
            1048,
            202,
            142,
            301,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jude sold a book to Yousef at a price of 685 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2075.76",
        "options": [
            "455.91",
            "513.11",
            "410.18",
            "2075.76",
            "445.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cyrus and Darwin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cyrus consumes 1598 calories per day whereas Darwin consumes 2446 calories per day. Cyrus is heavier than Darwin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian consumes 642 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Trace is 39 years old. How much calories should Trace consume?",
        "answer": 1284,
        "options": [
            153,
            196,
            243,
            1284,
            342
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 444 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            63,
            "Not possible",
            96,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Juan sold a book to Stefan at a price of 452 after giving 47 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "852.83",
        "options": [
            "852.83",
            "328.49",
            "307.48",
            "334.20",
            "365.99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 5 minutes. What is the temperature after 5 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            112,
            125,
            139,
            155,
            149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 149 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            88,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bentley sold a book to Saul at a price of 756 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1400.00",
        "options": [
            "517.81",
            "552.63",
            "614.63",
            "562.08",
            "1400.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in molybdenum is 6250. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6075",
            "13727",
            "343",
            "997",
            "14776"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in diamond ?",
        "answer": "12000",
        "options": [
            "12000",
            "250",
            "144",
            "330",
            "332"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tristan and Taylor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tristan consumes 2340 calories per day whereas Taylor consumes 1869 calories per day. Tristan is lighter than Taylor.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            63,
            96,
            93,
            "23",
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 478 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            63,
            76,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sebastian sold a book to Roland at a price of 655 after giving 23 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "850.65",
        "options": [
            "532.52",
            "850.65",
            "553.21",
            "587.44",
            "558.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            5,
            1009,
            2,
            1,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given kangaroos ? 9 23 28 34 32 25 50 14 5 48 9 34 19 31 30 45 37 40 28 14 ",
        "answer": "29.00",
        "options": [
            "48.00",
            "29.00",
            "32.00",
            "25.00",
            "5.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phoenix sold a book to Forrest at a price of 903 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1062.35",
        "options": [
            "1062.35",
            "806.25",
            "785.22",
            "811.69",
            "840.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 295 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            12,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            "Not possible",
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 170 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            93,
            53,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 188 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "305",
        "options": [
            95,
            37,
            "305",
            43,
            "Not possible",
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thomas consumes 936 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Rayan is 40 years old. How much calories should Rayan consume?",
        "answer": 1872,
        "options": [
            504,
            1872,
            245,
            209,
            323
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 21 34 31 41 35 25 34 20 29 47 4 4 21 44 8 10 1 24 1 44 6 5 ",
        "answer": "22.23",
        "options": [
            "22.23",
            "44.46",
            "66.69",
            "88.92",
            "44.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Royce and Joziah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Royce consumes 2355 calories per day whereas Joziah consumes 2633 calories per day. Royce is less weight than Joziah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 206 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 205,
        "options": [
            277,
            205,
            32,
            231,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nasir and Jerry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nasir consumes 2901 calories per day whereas Jerry consumes 2743 calories per day. Nasir is lighter than Jerry.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brycen and Will are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brycen consumes 1798 calories per day whereas Will consumes 1805 calories per day. Brycen is lighter than Will.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Noel and Watson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Noel consumes 2320 calories per day whereas Watson consumes 2496 calories per day. Noel is stronger than Watson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Legend sold a book to Saul at a price of 939 after giving 19 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1159.26",
        "options": [
            "1159.26",
            "821.88",
            "857.53",
            "815.10",
            "789.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 440 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            66,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            90,
            98,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Keegan and Nathanael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Keegan consumes 1735 calories per day whereas Nathanael consumes 2168 calories per day. Keegan is weaker than Nathanael.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "2620",
            "166",
            "122",
            "121",
            "162"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "August consumes 888 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Misael is 31 years old. How much calories should Misael consume?",
        "answer": 1776,
        "options": [
            203,
            472,
            1776,
            345,
            233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 89,
        "options": [
            110,
            106,
            113,
            89,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            112,
            134,
            125,
            138,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 163 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 160,
        "options": [
            93,
            141,
            221,
            318,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            123,
            99,
            105,
            109,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given dogs ? 49 46 37 41 49 17 50 39 38 21 16 44 42 ",
        "answer": "37.62",
        "options": [
            "150.48",
            "112.86",
            "188.10",
            "37.62",
            "112.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            68,
            58,
            46,
            71,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            37,
            31,
            11,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 343 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "109",
        "options": [
            75,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            "109",
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peter walks at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Orlando 's place which is 172 km away?",
        "answer": "17.20",
        "options": [
            "17.20",
            "34.40",
            "68.80",
            "68.80",
            "68.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            4914,
            4506,
            12,
            4217,
            3654
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 305 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            51,
            99,
            62,
            75,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 88 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 352,
        "options": [
            704,
            792,
            "352",
            880,
            528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matteo and Skylar are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matteo consumes 2062 calories per day whereas Skylar consumes 2822 calories per day. Matteo is bulkier than Skylar.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "101",
        "options": [
            7,
            82,
            "101",
            95,
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "20*28",
        "options": [
            "20*28",
            "47*65",
            "70*49",
            "55*90",
            "63*70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caiden sold a book to Darius at a price of 918 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "4172.73",
        "options": [
            "579.18",
            "4172.73",
            "565.27",
            "515.73",
            "660.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 108 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            59,
            121,
            183,
            104,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ian consumes 627 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Randy is 21 years old. How much calories should Randy consume?",
        "answer": 1254,
        "options": [
            220,
            1254,
            187,
            167,
            343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 431 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            14,
            "Not possible",
            34,
            48,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 915 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3660,
        "options": [
            4575,
            7320,
            9150,
            "3660",
            9150
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 456 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            54,
            "Not possible",
            32,
            65,
            80,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 93, 37, 50. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 344 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 340,
        "options": [
            260,
            226,
            273,
            390,
            340
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryan sold a book to Reece at a price of 471 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2140.91",
        "options": [
            "297.16",
            "290.02",
            "264.61",
            "338.85",
            "2140.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            112,
            99,
            113,
            130,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            80,
            50,
            70,
            71,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12846",
            "343",
            "11386",
            "5235",
            "12746"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            104,
            115,
            131,
            112,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 16 watt charger charges a phone in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            18,
            6,
            46,
            21,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaden and Ariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaden consumes 2433 calories per day whereas Ariel consumes 2198 calories per day. Kaden is lighter than Ariel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 297 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 287,
        "options": [
            287,
            254,
            323,
            230,
            229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given tigers ? 12 19 33 1 8 50 8 34 25 34 24 46 48 21 2 38 15 41 2 6 17 40 32 20 42 36 9 32 6 19 35 31 18 47 42 7 42 21 49 31 45 9 36 ",
        "answer": "31.00",
        "options": [
            "31.00",
            "42.00",
            "34.00",
            "42.00",
            "40.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            77,
            73,
            74,
            67,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noel consumes 652 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Nixon is 32 years old. How much calories should Nixon consume?",
        "answer": 1304,
        "options": [
            1304,
            207,
            342,
            258,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a laptop in 20 minutes. How much time will it take for a 17 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            84,
            74,
            50,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam sold a book to Curtis at a price of 742 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "764.95",
        "options": [
            "764.95",
            "731.03",
            "725.67",
            "724.61",
            "720.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            4,
            21,
            -14,
            -5,
            -20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            105,
            102,
            100,
            123,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Albert consumes 819 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Jericho is 28 years old. How much calories should Jericho consume?",
        "answer": 1638,
        "options": [
            1638,
            206,
            438,
            239,
            306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 357 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            46,
            "Not possible",
            22,
            44,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Everett consumes 803 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Harlem is 22 years old. How much calories should Harlem consume?",
        "answer": 1606,
        "options": [
            420,
            292,
            237,
            1606,
            172
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            5684,
            4567,
            3,
            4248,
            5752
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milo sold a book to Yehuda at a price of 174 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "669.23",
        "options": [
            "111.90",
            "100.00",
            "109.30",
            "669.23",
            "127.01"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyler consumes 680 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Braylon is 25 years old. How much calories should Braylon consume?",
        "answer": 1360,
        "options": [
            157,
            1360,
            208,
            367,
            270
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            74,
            143,
            2977,
            228,
            265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 433 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            "Not possible",
            55,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack consumes 831 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Musa is 20 years old. How much calories should Musa consume?",
        "answer": 1662,
        "options": [
            192,
            240,
            325,
            435,
            1662
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Donovan and Jairo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Donovan consumes 2522 calories per day whereas Jairo consumes 2806 calories per day. Donovan is lighter than Jairo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            38,
            49,
            56,
            36,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 288 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "269",
        "options": [
            80,
            "269",
            "Not possible",
            60,
            57,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 250 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            20,
            "Not possible",
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given dogs ? 7 28 15 40 26 1 31 37 43 27 41 20 46 7 34 39 11 42 48 5 16 15 3 29 12 16 22 7 44 30 47 45 33 11 22 4 ",
        "answer": "26.50",
        "options": [
            "7.00",
            "15.00",
            "7.00",
            "4.00",
            "26.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            72,
            58,
            66,
            54,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Killian and Kole are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Killian consumes 1743 calories per day whereas Kole consumes 2321 calories per day. Killian is more weight than Kole.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            97,
            99,
            88,
            119,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            71,
            72,
            73,
            69,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brandon and Bronson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brandon consumes 2656 calories per day whereas Bronson consumes 1976 calories per day. Brandon is lighter than Bronson.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Camden and Madden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Camden consumes 1807 calories per day whereas Madden consumes 2291 calories per day. Camden is less weight than Madden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander consumes 910 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Judson is 39 years old. How much calories should Judson consume?",
        "answer": 1820,
        "options": [
            1820,
            346,
            465,
            273,
            225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 440 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            62,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            77,
            39,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in manganese is 4660. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10362",
            "6597",
            "343",
            "7564",
            "2863"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 112 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            112,
            211,
            107,
            159,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 122 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            76,
            "11",
            48,
            60,
            "Not possible",
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 141 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 133,
        "options": [
            242,
            222,
            235,
            133,
            256
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            86,
            59,
            "Not possible",
            41,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colton and Benton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colton consumes 2129 calories per day whereas Benton consumes 1542 calories per day. Colton is less weight than Benton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            2,
            10,
            21,
            3,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 56 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "33*20",
        "options": [
            "66*51",
            "108*35",
            "33*20",
            "112*41",
            "98*34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Orion consumes 679 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Terrence is 32 years old. How much calories should Terrence consume?",
        "answer": 1358,
        "options": [
            273,
            207,
            1358,
            361,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lincoln consumes 998 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Camilo is 33 years old. How much calories should Camilo consume?",
        "answer": 1996,
        "options": [
            210,
            285,
            533,
            374,
            1996
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pablo and Jimmy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pablo consumes 2527 calories per day whereas Jimmy consumes 1723 calories per day. Pablo is more weight than Jimmy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Prince and Axl are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Prince consumes 1535 calories per day whereas Axl consumes 1950 calories per day. Prince is less weight than Axl.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Solomon and Roger are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Solomon consumes 2005 calories per day whereas Roger consumes 2578 calories per day. Solomon is heavier than Roger.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Wyatt sold a book to Kylen at a price of 986 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1972.00",
        "options": [
            "657.33",
            "717.09",
            "704.29",
            "1972.00",
            "788.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "335",
            "157",
            "283",
            "180",
            "5640"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 155 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "33",
            10,
            44,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 49 * 50. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "24*42",
        "options": [
            "24*42",
            "66*64",
            "75*55",
            "90*86",
            "50*69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lucite is 2680. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4080",
            "13060",
            "343",
            "9268",
            "14307"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            -2,
            -11,
            -8,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Henry and Maurice are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Henry consumes 2996 calories per day whereas Maurice consumes 1998 calories per day. Henry is bulkier than Maurice.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 47 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            35,
            55,
            65,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vincent sold a book to Baker at a price of 925 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1813.73",
        "options": [
            "664.51",
            "1813.73",
            "676.42",
            "620.81",
            "742.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 275 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            23,
            2,
            86,
            47,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zaiden drives at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Callum 's place which is 136 km away?",
        "answer": "19.43",
        "options": [
            "19.43",
            "38.86",
            "97.14",
            "38.86",
            "77.71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            11,
            40,
            38,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 271 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 269,
        "options": [
            269,
            175,
            533,
            330,
            474
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cash and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cash consumes 2547 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 2211 calories per day. Cash is stronger than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Noah by 1 years. 10 years ago Noah was 28 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "39",
            "37",
            "35",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ashton and Forrest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ashton consumes 2724 calories per day whereas Forrest consumes 1615 calories per day. Ashton is less weight than Forrest.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Princeton sold a book to Ares at a price of 131 after giving 57 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "304.65",
        "options": [
            "91.77",
            "83.44",
            "304.65",
            "89.97",
            "101.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            106,
            109,
            86,
            106,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given dogs ? 12 2 30 42 3 49 20 6 2 22 12 5 30 4 25 14 13 47 33 38 12 13 23 16 48 22 33 18 4 33 48 22 5 8 25 16 15 43 6 46 32 27 ",
        "answer": "21.00",
        "options": [
            "21.00",
            "12.00",
            "15.00",
            "12.00",
            "33.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2977,
            550,
            1325,
            1567,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            114,
            137,
            99,
            119,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayce sold a book to Lewis at a price of 889 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1389.06",
        "options": [
            "700.00",
            "753.39",
            "1389.06",
            "690.22",
            "653.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 154 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            35,
            94,
            54,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 82 . We turned on the cooler for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            85,
            93,
            87,
            69,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 73 minutes. What is the temperature after 73 minutes?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            13,
            8,
            11,
            5,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than William by 5 years. 7 years ago William was 34 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "50",
            "40",
            "31",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 458 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            85,
            "Not possible",
            21,
            "Not possible",
            3,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 455 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1820,
        "options": [
            2730,
            "1820",
            3185,
            4095,
            4550
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a airpods in 28 minutes. How much time will it take for a 2 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            58,
            28,
            52,
            20,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 63, 49, 68. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 346 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            52,
            70,
            84,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a airpods in 21 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            20,
            39,
            8,
            21,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zander consumes 752 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Alfonso is 26 years old. How much calories should Alfonso consume?",
        "answer": 1504,
        "options": [
            285,
            206,
            392,
            1504,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 282 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 271,
        "options": [
            520,
            258,
            277,
            76,
            271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marcos consumes 732 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Rogelio is 25 years old. How much calories should Rogelio consume?",
        "answer": 1464,
        "options": [
            396,
            260,
            1464,
            183,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1009,
            3,
            14,
            8,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            75,
            80,
            74,
            56,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 14 . We turned on the heater for 11 minutes. What is the temperature after 11 minutes?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            5,
            -25,
            11,
            5,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "155",
            "2180",
            "141",
            "138",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eden and Vicente are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eden consumes 2510 calories per day whereas Vicente consumes 2431 calories per day. Eden is heavier than Vicente.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Orion sold a book to Skylar at a price of 367 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "398.91",
        "options": [
            "352.88",
            "339.81",
            "344.92",
            "346.23",
            "398.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "149",
            "291",
            "3960",
            "339",
            "199"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 82, 50, 48. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 139 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 134,
        "options": [
            134,
            126,
            181,
            197,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in annealed tungsten is 5220. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8924",
            "11296",
            "14749",
            "343",
            "13542"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 270 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 265,
        "options": [
            451,
            97,
            290,
            527,
            265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 485 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            "57",
            "Not possible",
            4,
            97,
            71,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ismael sold a book to Brodie at a price of 827 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2017.07",
        "options": [
            "638.61",
            "2017.07",
            "573.31",
            "561.82",
            "520.13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cruz and Westley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cruz consumes 2193 calories per day whereas Westley consumes 1834 calories per day. Cruz is more weight than Westley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Levi consumes 730 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Raylan is 21 years old. How much calories should Raylan consume?",
        "answer": 1460,
        "options": [
            1460,
            205,
            159,
            408,
            289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paxton drives at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Blaze 's place which is 106 km away?",
        "answer": "15.14",
        "options": [
            "15.14",
            "30.29",
            "75.71",
            "45.43",
            "60.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bodhi and Kyree are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bodhi consumes 2659 calories per day whereas Kyree consumes 1574 calories per day. Bodhi is more weight than Kyree.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Arthur is younger than Yael by 3 years. 11 years ago Yael was 27 years old. What is Arthur 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "47",
            "69",
            "47",
            "55",
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            94,
            83,
            90,
            94,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            50,
            77,
            65,
            55,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Timothy consumes 851 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Saint is 26 years old. How much calories should Saint consume?",
        "answer": 1702,
        "options": [
            452,
            319,
            202,
            240,
            1702
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            431,
            2977,
            696,
            485,
            497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 140 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            243,
            218,
            1,
            90,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 169 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            14,
            15,
            22,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "John consumes 950 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Jamari is 32 years old. How much calories should Jamari consume?",
        "answer": 1900,
        "options": [
            1900,
            350,
            253,
            204,
            515
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Asher consumes 921 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Zeke is 27 years old. How much calories should Zeke consume?",
        "answer": 1842,
        "options": [
            207,
            500,
            272,
            1842,
            350
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            80,
            80,
            92,
            73,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 49 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            10,
            83,
            67,
            43,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            73,
            61,
            62,
            60,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "881",
        "options": [
            37,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            93,
            "881",
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a airpods in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            77,
            81,
            72,
            23,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Seth and Damari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Seth consumes 1702 calories per day whereas Damari consumes 2377 calories per day. Seth is less weight than Damari.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Alvin at a price of 232 after giving 29 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "326.76",
        "options": [
            "190.55",
            "326.76",
            "188.31",
            "179.84",
            "202.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the cooler for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            87,
            69,
            78,
            57,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 69, 53, 58. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cesar and Thaddeus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cesar consumes 2569 calories per day whereas Thaddeus consumes 2815 calories per day. Cesar is less weight than Thaddeus.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 175 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 164,
        "options": [
            204,
            164,
            261,
            304,
            296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohamed consumes 566 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Shepherd is 24 years old. How much calories should Shepherd consume?",
        "answer": 1132,
        "options": [
            309,
            1132,
            161,
            134,
            231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cork is 518. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "10908",
            "3857",
            "10500",
            "10797"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "3350",
            "160",
            "110",
            "312",
            "241"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rylan consumes 866 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Shiloh is 30 years old. How much calories should Shiloh consume?",
        "answer": 1732,
        "options": [
            323,
            264,
            457,
            222,
            1732
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            80,
            71,
            70,
            73,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 125 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            121,
            3,
            200,
            170,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 5 years. 6 years ago Noah was 32 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "29",
            "33",
            "43",
            "23",
            "29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Juan sold a book to Dario at a price of 430 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "914.89",
        "options": [
            "307.69",
            "281.05",
            "914.89",
            "301.97",
            "339.92"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 263 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            65,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            64,
            "Not possible",
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given dogs ? 10 42 6 6 45 23 9 3 16 16 29 6 15 19 30 46 24 18 45 43 27 39 8 2 13 18 26 16 41 18 8 14 17 2 32 ",
        "answer": "18.00",
        "options": [
            "18.00",
            "15.00",
            "2.00",
            "18.00",
            "6.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ethan and Jacoby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ethan consumes 2987 calories per day whereas Jacoby consumes 2158 calories per day. Ethan is weaker than Jacoby.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ari and Ramon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ari consumes 2607 calories per day whereas Ramon consumes 2142 calories per day. Ari is weaker than Ramon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given cats ? 3 32 4 31 15 22 32 32 49 42 25 35 17 26 40 ",
        "answer": "31.00",
        "options": [
            "32.00",
            "17.00",
            "35.00",
            "31.00",
            "32.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adriel and Byron are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adriel consumes 2588 calories per day whereas Byron consumes 2304 calories per day. Adriel is stronger than Byron.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 95, 37, 48. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            27,
            47,
            43,
            45,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dominick and Lachlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dominick consumes 1525 calories per day whereas Lachlan consumes 2858 calories per day. Dominick is more weight than Lachlan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 99, 44, 37. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elias consumes 707 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Sonny is 23 years old. How much calories should Sonny consume?",
        "answer": 1414,
        "options": [
            189,
            162,
            247,
            1414,
            395
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iridium is 4790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9187",
            "3002",
            "343",
            "3618",
            "12368"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given cats ? 46 21 40 8 49 39 17 23 44 24 36 26 27 39 44 4 49 35 41 28 40 24 7 17 19 ",
        "answer": "28.00",
        "options": [
            "35.00",
            "49.00",
            "17.00",
            "28.00",
            "17.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesus consumes 532 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Curtis is 23 years old. How much calories should Curtis consume?",
        "answer": 1064,
        "options": [
            200,
            123,
            1064,
            170,
            278
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 338 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            88,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            58,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the cooler for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            56,
            89,
            46,
            58,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            36,
            14,
            37,
            45,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawson and Flynn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawson consumes 2844 calories per day whereas Flynn consumes 2193 calories per day. Lawson is more weight than Flynn.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            705,
            693,
            649,
            376,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradley consumes 829 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Emery is 28 years old. How much calories should Emery consume?",
        "answer": 1658,
        "options": [
            306,
            236,
            215,
            431,
            1658
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Royce is younger than Kenzo by 1 years. 5 years ago Kenzo was 26 years old. What is Royce 's age today?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "37",
            "43",
            "32",
            "30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            4585,
            3173,
            5582,
            5509,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            81,
            78,
            91,
            80,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bodhi and Jabari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bodhi consumes 2838 calories per day whereas Jabari consumes 2929 calories per day. Bodhi is less weight than Jabari.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a tablet in 56 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            11,
            57,
            5,
            52,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a powerbank in 31 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            35,
            43,
            5,
            68,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 3 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Traingle",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 65, 38, 77. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luciano cycles at a speed of 6 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Deandre 's place which is 108 km away?",
        "answer": "18.00",
        "options": [
            "36.00",
            "18.00",
            "90.00",
            "72.00",
            "72.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 262 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            10,
            22,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            14,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bowen and Landry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bowen consumes 2587 calories per day whereas Landry consumes 2924 calories per day. Bowen is bulkier than Landry.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham sold a book to Gatlin at a price of 378 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1145.45",
        "options": [
            "1145.45",
            "246.09",
            "226.35",
            "251.58",
            "283.15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 246 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            91,
            20,
            59,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1009,
            5893,
            3937,
            4976,
            3771
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 339 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            24,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            11,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Legend and Vance are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Legend consumes 1620 calories per day whereas Vance consumes 1654 calories per day. Legend is stronger than Vance.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 232 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 230,
        "options": [
            177,
            335,
            230,
            418,
            460
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kevin and Rayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kevin consumes 2593 calories per day whereas Rayan consumes 2926 calories per day. Kevin is weaker than Rayan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 344 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 338,
        "options": [
            338,
            394,
            547,
            69,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            41,
            35,
            52,
            61,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corey sold a book to Casen at a price of 203 after giving 32 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "298.53",
        "options": [
            "163.71",
            "175.00",
            "153.79",
            "298.53",
            "161.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in aluminium ?",
        "answer": "6420",
        "options": [
            "234",
            "341",
            "240",
            "109",
            "6420"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 109 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            120,
            114,
            114,
            108,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            2,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            69,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kevin and Kaysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kevin consumes 1924 calories per day whereas Kaysen consumes 1977 calories per day. Kevin is more weight than Kaysen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Troy and Jaxx are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Troy consumes 1797 calories per day whereas Jaxx consumes 1774 calories per day. Troy is more weight than Jaxx.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nicolas and Jamir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nicolas consumes 1532 calories per day whereas Jamir consumes 2921 calories per day. Nicolas is weaker than Jamir.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 46 * 43. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "38*41",
        "options": [
            "50*44",
            "38*41",
            "68*47",
            "66*52",
            "94*47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the cooler for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            56,
            62,
            53,
            61,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 112 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "13",
            "Not possible",
            7,
            17,
            23,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in slate is 4510. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5392",
            "343",
            "9583",
            "1110",
            "4436"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 286 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 279,
        "options": [
            279,
            347,
            291,
            478,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            100,
            95,
            88,
            104,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            4196,
            1009,
            3851,
            3008,
            3569
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            116,
            100,
            124,
            116,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 199 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "45",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "45",
            24,
            100,
            24,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            4580,
            23,
            3571,
            5761,
            3730
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 103 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            30,
            186,
            119,
            97,
            153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given human ? 16 8 4 4 18 42 10 13 40 21 17 47 34 18 33 43 44 38 39 2 10 45 11 9 23 28 16 36 33 43 15 27 48 11 45 23 5 49 13 45 19 41 30 9 27 9 43 48 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "25.00",
            "21.00",
            "41.00",
            "45.00",
            "4.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            34,
            23,
            17,
            43,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Titus and Julien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Titus consumes 1869 calories per day whereas Julien consumes 1695 calories per day. Titus is heavier than Julien.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximiliano and Raphael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximiliano consumes 2264 calories per day whereas Raphael consumes 2392 calories per day. Maximiliano is bulkier than Raphael.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 34 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            24,
            19,
            22,
            31,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            97,
            26,
            81,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tyson and Aydin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tyson consumes 2681 calories per day whereas Aydin consumes 2169 calories per day. Tyson is stronger than Aydin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 59 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            85,
            57,
            21,
            43,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker sold a book to Douglas at a price of 735 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1470.00",
        "options": [
            "588.00",
            "525.00",
            "534.55",
            "490.00",
            "1470.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 315 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "55",
        "options": [
            75,
            40,
            "55",
            66,
            "Not possible",
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Deacon and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Deacon consumes 1507 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 2462 calories per day. Deacon is stronger than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 95 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            98,
            116,
            93,
            104,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 285 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 275,
        "options": [
            481,
            414,
            255,
            275,
            410
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zane consumes 830 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Wilder is 28 years old. How much calories should Wilder consume?",
        "answer": 1660,
        "options": [
            1660,
            325,
            200,
            443,
            231
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            41,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            85,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polyethylene ?",
        "answer": "1250",
        "options": [
            "134",
            "1250",
            "102",
            "158",
            "282"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson consumes 808 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Brennan is 40 years old. How much calories should Brennan consume?",
        "answer": 1616,
        "options": [
            196,
            1616,
            425,
            292,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            11,
            13,
            -1,
            4,
            -4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 286 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 280,
        "options": [
            372,
            36,
            280,
            157,
            362
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 63 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            63,
            40,
            66,
            31,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Drew and Jedidiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Drew consumes 2364 calories per day whereas Jedidiah consumes 2656 calories per day. Drew is stronger than Jedidiah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 438 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "197",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            52,
            43,
            "197",
            8,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jase and Saint are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jase consumes 2818 calories per day whereas Saint consumes 2311 calories per day. Jase is heavier than Saint.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Anderson and Benedict are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Anderson consumes 2961 calories per day whereas Benedict consumes 2344 calories per day. Anderson is less weight than Benedict.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Weston sold a book to Azariah at a price of 476 after giving 19 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "587.65",
        "options": [
            "434.70",
            "587.65",
            "416.63",
            "413.19",
            "400.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "River sold a book to Deangelo at a price of 737 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1364.81",
        "options": [
            "599.19",
            "504.79",
            "1364.81",
            "538.74",
            "547.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Griffin is younger than Cannon by 2 years. 10 years ago Cannon was 29 years old. What is Griffin 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "51",
            "37",
            "41",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 56, 52, 72. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            17,
            31,
            23,
            10,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole consumes 544 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Ronnie is 25 years old. How much calories should Ronnie consume?",
        "answer": 1088,
        "options": [
            216,
            311,
            166,
            1088,
            146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given tigers ? 46 41 40 22 10 37 32 10 13 35 1 31 23 30 25 12 49 46 34 25 17 24 35 49 18 47 41 38 40 23 40 38 29 45 15 30 50 14 34 47 1 22 21 48 12 17 ",
        "answer": "30.50",
        "options": [
            "40.00",
            "30.50",
            "1.00",
            "13.00",
            "49.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 172 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            73,
            75,
            "39",
            39,
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 59 * 48. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "50*36",
        "options": [
            "50*36",
            "89*70",
            "85*63",
            "109*84",
            "81*49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 46, 49, 85. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            58,
            67,
            43,
            67,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            5175,
            12,
            3783,
            3646,
            3254
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            111,
            114,
            125,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            57,
            36,
            78,
            44,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erik and Moshe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erik consumes 2750 calories per day whereas Moshe consumes 2569 calories per day. Erik is more weight than Moshe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam sold a book to Maxim at a price of 168 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "233.33",
        "options": [
            "147.37",
            "137.25",
            "138.84",
            "131.25",
            "233.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            51,
            40,
            44,
            53,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 150 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "29",
            27,
            96,
            7,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 279 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "519",
        "options": [
            82,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            66,
            81,
            "519"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            40,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            91,
            82,
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Drake sold a book to Markus at a price of 974 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1094.38",
        "options": [
            "895.22",
            "877.48",
            "1094.38",
            "923.22",
            "899.77"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "218",
            "2180",
            "126",
            "331",
            "277"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mathias and Justus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mathias consumes 1693 calories per day whereas Justus consumes 2592 calories per day. Mathias is stronger than Justus.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph sold a book to Madden at a price of 783 after giving 66 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2302.94",
        "options": [
            "512.43",
            "588.72",
            "2302.94",
            "471.69",
            "523.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beckett sold a book to Harlan at a price of 699 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1370.59",
        "options": [
            "511.15",
            "1370.59",
            "469.13",
            "502.16",
            "561.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given cats ? 39 36 49 45 13 44 11 36 3 43 15 41 17 47 35 20 2 34 43 2 27 14 26 35 35 8 8 20 50 26 47 46 20 36 35 ",
        "answer": "35.00",
        "options": [
            "13.00",
            "27.00",
            "15.00",
            "3.00",
            "35.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oakley sold a book to Ryland at a price of 402 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "820.41",
        "options": [
            "320.32",
            "266.23",
            "290.78",
            "285.51",
            "820.41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brycen consumes 955 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Zev is 24 years old. How much calories should Zev consume?",
        "answer": 1910,
        "options": [
            215,
            365,
            278,
            1910,
            510
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            27,
            27,
            26,
            12,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawrence and Zakai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawrence consumes 2047 calories per day whereas Zakai consumes 1580 calories per day. Lawrence is less weight than Zakai.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Julian is younger than Marley by 3 years. 13 years ago Marley was 25 years old. What is Julian 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "70",
            "44",
            "54",
            "35",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 40 38 27 1 8 47 ",
        "answer": "26.83",
        "options": [
            "134.15",
            "107.32",
            "26.83",
            "53.66",
            "53.66"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker consumes 883 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Makai is 23 years old. How much calories should Makai consume?",
        "answer": 1766,
        "options": [
            315,
            225,
            247,
            465,
            1766
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given tigers ? 42 24 9 8 2 7 12 47 10 25 1 29 17 39 3 4 43 6 4 44 41 4 43 43 24 44 39 34 37 24 2 30 42 24 8 ",
        "answer": "23.29",
        "options": [
            "69.87",
            "116.45",
            "23.29",
            "93.16",
            "46.58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            392,
            821,
            1979,
            652,
            673
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Steven consumes 955 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Mitchell is 26 years old. How much calories should Mitchell consume?",
        "answer": 1910,
        "options": [
            493,
            1910,
            351,
            254,
            232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 463 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            55,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ari consumes 842 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Sincere is 24 years old. How much calories should Sincere consume?",
        "answer": 1684,
        "options": [
            212,
            432,
            1684,
            314,
            248
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Silas and Kenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Silas consumes 2093 calories per day whereas Kenzo consumes 2861 calories per day. Silas is weaker than Kenzo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "George consumes 706 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Bode is 25 years old. How much calories should Bode consume?",
        "answer": 1412,
        "options": [
            191,
            254,
            152,
            1412,
            397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Thiago and Sam are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Thiago consumes 2216 calories per day whereas Sam consumes 2087 calories per day. Thiago is lighter than Sam.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmett consumes 541 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Madden is 20 years old. How much calories should Madden consume?",
        "answer": 1082,
        "options": [
            1082,
            298,
            168,
            217,
            138
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "277",
            "319",
            "143",
            "227",
            "2620"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            49,
            25,
            41,
            46,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Corey and Reginald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Corey consumes 2681 calories per day whereas Reginald consumes 1876 calories per day. Corey is weaker than Reginald.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Tate consumes 501 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Landry is 34 years old. How much calories should Landry consume?",
        "answer": 1002,
        "options": [
            134,
            187,
            1002,
            158,
            290
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malakai and Moshe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malakai consumes 2686 calories per day whereas Moshe consumes 2257 calories per day. Malakai is heavier than Moshe.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given human ? 8 11 6 26 47 44 26 50 14 44 5 14 25 30 19 30 24 15 34 22 2 33 29 34 37 6 25 5 26 47 27 6 21 34 33 26 5 34 27 49 2 40 32 ",
        "answer": "26.00",
        "options": [
            "34.00",
            "47.00",
            "26.00",
            "29.00",
            "19.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a tablet in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            38,
            40,
            55,
            10,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            2,
            -16,
            4,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 48 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            1,
            31,
            76,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 4 watt charger charges a airpods in 51 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            57,
            61,
            73,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton sold a book to Kamdyn at a price of 776 after giving 12 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "881.82",
        "options": [
            "708.03",
            "711.93",
            "881.82",
            "692.86",
            "732.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clayton and Wesson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clayton consumes 1951 calories per day whereas Wesson consumes 1987 calories per day. Clayton is less weight than Wesson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 290 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            56,
            "Not possible",
            29,
            25,
            "17",
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lane walks at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Hugh 's place which is 135 km away?",
        "answer": "7.50",
        "options": [
            "7.50",
            "37.50",
            "22.50",
            "22.50",
            "15.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 147 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            19,
            12,
            21,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 283 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 272,
        "options": [
            272,
            128,
            278,
            99,
            262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 26 watt charger charges a phone in 18 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            50,
            12,
            14,
            10,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marcus and Felipe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marcus consumes 2641 calories per day whereas Felipe consumes 2950 calories per day. Marcus is less weight than Felipe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given kangaroos ? 46 50 33 11 17 7 34 45 42 34 2 39 38 10 35 12 4 17 39 15 40 2 18 12 11 45 30 9 35 36 19 19 22 27 22 34 20 13 24 16 48 18 25 27 41 49 6 11 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "10.00",
            "13.00",
            "11.00",
            "12.00",
            "23.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            -4,
            1,
            1,
            -5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Oliver by 5 years. 11 years ago Oliver was 27 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "44",
            "28",
            "23",
            "34",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Felix sold a book to Ronnie at a price of 550 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1833.33",
        "options": [
            "323.53",
            "407.41",
            "352.56",
            "360.66",
            "1833.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 257 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 253,
        "options": [
            335,
            253,
            25,
            289,
            398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            -3,
            16,
            22,
            6,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 492 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            37,
            84,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            3,
            5,
            4,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gunner and Jagger are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gunner consumes 2053 calories per day whereas Jagger consumes 2545 calories per day. Gunner is heavier than Jagger.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 220 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            47,
            15,
            12,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jacob and Jaxx are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jacob consumes 1632 calories per day whereas Jaxx consumes 2170 calories per day. Jacob is less weight than Jaxx.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 126 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            41,
            94,
            "Not possible",
            50,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Steven and Yahir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Steven consumes 1664 calories per day whereas Yahir consumes 2956 calories per day. Steven is more weight than Yahir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 161 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            151,
            102,
            239,
            262,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maverick sold a book to Branson at a price of 899 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3210.71",
        "options": [
            "570.43",
            "583.77",
            "3210.71",
            "522.67",
            "661.03"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 154 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            82,
            "Not possible",
            31,
            11,
            97,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adonis and Mordechai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adonis consumes 2341 calories per day whereas Mordechai consumes 2454 calories per day. Adonis is less weight than Mordechai.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "277",
            "325",
            "5940",
            "323",
            "254"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caden and Joziah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caden consumes 1663 calories per day whereas Joziah consumes 1844 calories per day. Caden is bulkier than Joziah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a powerbank in 43 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            41,
            41,
            29,
            14,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            124,
            130,
            118,
            106,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            66,
            82,
            70,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 372 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            10,
            16,
            16,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sage sold a book to Samir at a price of 271 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "376.39",
        "options": [
            "223.97",
            "221.41",
            "237.72",
            "376.39",
            "211.72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Benjamin by 5 years. 13 years ago Benjamin was 28 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "39",
            "52",
            "26",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than James by 3 years. 15 years ago James was 34 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            "58",
            "58",
            "46",
            "55",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 363 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            97,
            "49",
            1,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            -4,
            35,
            15,
            27,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 96 minutes. What is the temperature after 96 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            117,
            140,
            144,
            104,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            2581,
            1009,
            2226,
            3944,
            3762
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            47,
            26,
            38,
            36,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            -1,
            26,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Josiah and Deangelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Josiah consumes 1762 calories per day whereas Deangelo consumes 2954 calories per day. Josiah is lighter than Deangelo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott consumes 750 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Gatlin is 36 years old. How much calories should Gatlin consume?",
        "answer": 1500,
        "options": [
            294,
            392,
            177,
            199,
            1500
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cesar sold a book to Terrell at a price of 681 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3095.45",
        "options": [
            "429.65",
            "3095.45",
            "382.58",
            "419.33",
            "489.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kai and Marlon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kai consumes 1993 calories per day whereas Marlon consumes 2995 calories per day. Kai is lighter than Marlon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhys and Jaziel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhys consumes 2902 calories per day whereas Jaziel consumes 1600 calories per day. Rhys is weaker than Jaziel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in manganese ?",
        "answer": "4660",
        "options": [
            "258",
            "4660",
            "286",
            "229",
            "163"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given elephants ? 31 31 30 11 1 4 3 40 17 29 27 50 18 29 44 37 22 35 24 25 21 16 27 25 30 10 37 38 48 49 21 8 10 1 16 35 14 22 8 23 46 ",
        "answer": "24.71",
        "options": [
            "49.42",
            "49.42",
            "123.55",
            "24.71",
            "74.13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "5950",
            "271",
            "207",
            "225",
            "132"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barrett is younger than Xzavier by 5 years. 11 years ago Xzavier was 34 years old. What is Barrett 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "72",
            "72",
            "40",
            "55",
            "60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            118,
            94,
            92,
            87,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 619 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2476,
        "options": [
            3714,
            "2476",
            4333,
            6190,
            4952
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 406 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            72,
            "51",
            61,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            130,
            101,
            102,
            93,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Roberto and Dane are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Roberto consumes 1904 calories per day whereas Dane consumes 2656 calories per day. Roberto is heavier than Dane.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 297 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 293,
        "options": [
            293,
            330,
            21,
            364,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            24,
            29,
            18,
            25,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 308 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 306,
        "options": [
            135,
            164,
            306,
            445,
            372
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Silas and Alfredo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Silas consumes 2405 calories per day whereas Alfredo consumes 2792 calories per day. Silas is more weight than Alfredo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            86,
            89,
            92,
            88,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            134,
            86,
            64,
            354,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kolton consumes 917 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Lachlan is 29 years old. How much calories should Lachlan consume?",
        "answer": 1834,
        "options": [
            271,
            205,
            340,
            503,
            1834
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronald is younger than Kobe by 2 years. 7 years ago Kobe was 32 years old. What is Ronald 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "57",
            "45",
            "37",
            "45",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 486 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1944,
        "options": [
            4374,
            3888,
            "1944",
            2430,
            4374
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marcus sold a book to Bridger at a price of 507 after giving 26 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "685.14",
        "options": [
            "402.38",
            "419.70",
            "685.14",
            "448.67",
            "424.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in duralumin ?",
        "answer": "6320",
        "options": [
            "173",
            "131",
            "6320",
            "200",
            "322"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 109 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            58,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            16,
            77,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kashton consumes 730 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Kaiser is 36 years old. How much calories should Kaiser consume?",
        "answer": 1460,
        "options": [
            174,
            1460,
            293,
            226,
            385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Quinn sold a book to Kole at a price of 712 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3236.36",
        "options": [
            "400.00",
            "512.23",
            "449.21",
            "3236.36",
            "438.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 31 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            13,
            30,
            16,
            30,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            91,
            109,
            97,
            92,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass silicate flint ?",
        "answer": "3980",
        "options": [
            "155",
            "192",
            "200",
            "230",
            "3980"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 173 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            6,
            67,
            56,
            "35",
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 198 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            54,
            97,
            48,
            "21",
            44,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 118 . We turned on the cooler for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 114,
        "options": [
            130,
            119,
            114,
            120,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan consumes 773 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Orlando is 28 years old. How much calories should Orlando consume?",
        "answer": 1546,
        "options": [
            404,
            167,
            268,
            238,
            1546
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 137 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 134,
        "options": [
            134,
            1,
            250,
            220,
            175
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jake consumes 531 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Draven is 40 years old. How much calories should Draven consume?",
        "answer": 1062,
        "options": [
            1062,
            206,
            129,
            170,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kenneth and Terry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kenneth consumes 2317 calories per day whereas Terry consumes 2834 calories per day. Kenneth is less weight than Terry.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 182 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            34,
            15,
            86,
            "15",
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 414 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            51,
            67,
            98,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            "31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both King and Saul are of same age. Both do same physical activity. King consumes 1622 calories per day whereas Saul consumes 2833 calories per day. King is less weight than Saul.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 223 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 219,
        "options": [
            91,
            161,
            409,
            13,
            219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            39,
            29,
            61,
            43,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a laptop in 31 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            60,
            16,
            61,
            79,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 459 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            48,
            51,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            28,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 490 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            17,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            99,
            "51",
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martin consumes 642 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Aden is 28 years old. How much calories should Aden consume?",
        "answer": 1284,
        "options": [
            205,
            168,
            347,
            257,
            1284
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 293 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 284,
        "options": [
            284,
            31,
            276,
            515,
            303
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the cooler for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            69,
            66,
            85,
            68,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a laptop in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 15 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            97,
            52,
            70,
            85,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a powerbank in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            97,
            81,
            33,
            17,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Anthony and Zaid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Anthony consumes 1870 calories per day whereas Zaid consumes 1855 calories per day. Anthony is less weight than Zaid.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 54, 56, 70. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 188 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 181,
        "options": [
            181,
            1,
            211,
            281,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Uriel and Cannon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Uriel consumes 2573 calories per day whereas Cannon consumes 2620 calories per day. Uriel is lighter than Cannon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "23",
            79,
            10,
            27,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            60,
            30,
            77,
            59,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            10,
            7,
            2,
            354,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 30 watt charger charges a laptop in 59 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            46,
            21,
            13,
            45,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 410 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            31,
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "Not possible",
            72,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 207 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 206,
        "options": [
            204,
            61,
            405,
            163,
            206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 330 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            67,
            "Not possible",
            53,
            "29",
            8,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            53,
            61,
            36,
            42,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in annealed tungsten is 5220. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11143",
            "14902",
            "7954",
            "343",
            "3768"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pedro and Maddux are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pedro consumes 2428 calories per day whereas Maddux consumes 1615 calories per day. Pedro is more weight than Maddux.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            63,
            39,
            47,
            42,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 363 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1452,
        "options": [
            2178,
            "1452",
            2904,
            2178,
            3267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 204 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            "47",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            78,
            31,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Troy and Nikolas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Troy consumes 1961 calories per day whereas Nikolas consumes 2653 calories per day. Troy is less weight than Nikolas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the cooler for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            69,
            61,
            37,
            59,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lorenzo and Colson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lorenzo consumes 1559 calories per day whereas Colson consumes 2869 calories per day. Lorenzo is lighter than Colson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            83,
            90,
            100,
            95,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nikolai and Marvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nikolai consumes 2889 calories per day whereas Marvin consumes 2374 calories per day. Nikolai is more weight than Marvin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 92 . We turned on the cooler for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            103,
            108,
            128,
            115,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Armando and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Armando consumes 1820 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 1562 calories per day. Armando is heavier than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            1979,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ruben and Benicio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ruben consumes 1872 calories per day whereas Benicio consumes 2513 calories per day. Ruben is weaker than Benicio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant drives at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Felipe 's place which is 136 km away?",
        "answer": "7.16",
        "options": [
            "14.32",
            "7.16",
            "28.63",
            "28.63",
            "35.79"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kamden and Reyansh are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kamden consumes 2340 calories per day whereas Reyansh consumes 2709 calories per day. Kamden is lighter than Reyansh.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 69, 40, 71. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 905 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3620,
        "options": [
            8145,
            "3620",
            5430,
            6335,
            4525
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 248 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            2,
            32,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 87 . We turned on the cooler for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            100,
            90,
            89,
            97,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            91,
            82,
            75,
            86,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the cooler for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            60,
            78,
            62,
            58,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9407",
            "13040",
            "343",
            "3087",
            "11151"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            624,
            356,
            393,
            462,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in monel ?",
        "answer": "5350",
        "options": [
            "164",
            "289",
            "316",
            "130",
            "5350"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Franklin consumes 583 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Vicente is 26 years old. How much calories should Vicente consume?",
        "answer": 1166,
        "options": [
            304,
            1166,
            166,
            165,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 104 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            7,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            70,
            "7",
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wesley and Jordy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wesley consumes 2058 calories per day whereas Jordy consumes 2469 calories per day. Wesley is lighter than Jordy.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hudson and Bobby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hudson consumes 2194 calories per day whereas Bobby consumes 1994 calories per day. Hudson is more weight than Bobby.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 347 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            6,
            "Not possible",
            7,
            56,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            4,
            142,
            2,
            5,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lucite ?",
        "answer": "2680",
        "options": [
            "156",
            "290",
            "281",
            "2680",
            "297"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than William by 2 years. 8 years ago William was 27 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "29",
            "37",
            "33",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5670",
            "1757",
            "9231",
            "343",
            "12101"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            71,
            83,
            "41",
            33,
            "Not possible",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a laptop in 18 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            6,
            17,
            6,
            13,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            8,
            20,
            26,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Arlo and Nixon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Arlo consumes 2862 calories per day whereas Nixon consumes 2133 calories per day. Arlo is heavier than Nixon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2977,
            1316,
            1204,
            403,
            1834
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Arthur and Alfredo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Arthur consumes 1888 calories per day whereas Alfredo consumes 2396 calories per day. Arthur is heavier than Alfredo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cadmium is 2780. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11748",
            "1746",
            "10674",
            "343",
            "11405"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 165 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            11,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 320 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            86,
            75,
            56,
            "35",
            25,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 47 * 36. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "43*35",
        "options": [
            "43*35",
            "55*51",
            "75*64",
            "51*40",
            "75*42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 59, 41, 80. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 60 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "46*21",
        "options": [
            "67*70",
            "46*21",
            "120*45",
            "88*56",
            "106*43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dylan and Salvador are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dylan consumes 2659 calories per day whereas Salvador consumes 2622 calories per day. Dylan is more weight than Salvador.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the cooler for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            66,
            53,
            53,
            56,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Porter and Bentlee are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Porter consumes 2964 calories per day whereas Bentlee consumes 1641 calories per day. Porter is stronger than Bentlee.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 428 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            "31",
            "Not possible",
            19,
            50,
            44,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cash and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cash consumes 2922 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 1921 calories per day. Cash is heavier than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            74,
            72,
            86,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 430 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            71,
            27,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Royal and Alec are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Royal consumes 2212 calories per day whereas Alec consumes 1695 calories per day. Royal is weaker than Alec.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 189 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            178,
            266,
            148,
            184,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14013",
            "14274",
            "9425",
            "343",
            "9228"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given elephants ? 22 37 9 18 6 3 50 33 9 29 9 34 31 5 5 1 41 34 14 17 12 15 33 38 47 44 25 30 42 6 46 24 ",
        "answer": "24.03",
        "options": [
            "72.09",
            "72.09",
            "48.06",
            "48.06",
            "24.03"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 149 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            85,
            80,
            "37",
            35,
            78,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah cycles at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Toby 's place which is 200 km away?",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "50.00",
            "50.00",
            "25.00",
            "75.00",
            "50.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Matthias sold a book to Orlando at a price of 415 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1092.11",
        "options": [
            "1092.11",
            "316.79",
            "277.41",
            "283.28",
            "256.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayn and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayn consumes 2315 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 2339 calories per day. Zayn is weaker than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Finnegan and Brentley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Finnegan consumes 2335 calories per day whereas Brentley consumes 1714 calories per day. Finnegan is heavier than Brentley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Evan and Franco are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Evan consumes 2845 calories per day whereas Franco consumes 2304 calories per day. Evan is lighter than Franco.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Benson walks at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Ishaan 's place which is 187 km away?",
        "answer": "9.84",
        "options": [
            "19.68",
            "19.68",
            "29.53",
            "9.84",
            "29.53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4832",
            "13451",
            "3473",
            "12333",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            59,
            70,
            61,
            66,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marcos consumes 787 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Clay is 25 years old. How much calories should Clay consume?",
        "answer": 1574,
        "options": [
            237,
            205,
            416,
            1574,
            280
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            117,
            112,
            99,
            140,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 405 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "97",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            71,
            "97",
            85,
            4,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in aluminium ?",
        "answer": "6420",
        "options": [
            "6420",
            "187",
            "208",
            "246",
            "291"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brian sold a book to Scott at a price of 824 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1753.19",
        "options": [
            "651.38",
            "538.56",
            "589.62",
            "578.65",
            "1753.19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 323 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            34,
            "49",
            75,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 216 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 212,
        "options": [
            422,
            212,
            325,
            393,
            309
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 153 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            42,
            5,
            88,
            "Not possible",
            21,
            "9"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass light crown is 5100. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2082",
            "4268",
            "1619",
            "343",
            "3543"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 6 watt charger charges a powerbank in 21 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            23,
            11,
            40,
            82,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caden cycles at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Kareem 's place which is 139 km away?",
        "answer": "17.38",
        "options": [
            "34.75",
            "17.38",
            "69.50",
            "34.75",
            "52.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 299 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 289,
        "options": [
            267,
            408,
            263,
            32,
            289
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kenneth is younger than Bobby by 4 years. 9 years ago Bobby was 31 years old. What is Kenneth 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "53",
            "53",
            "57",
            "66",
            "36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alejandro sold a book to Zayd at a price of 455 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "910.00",
        "options": [
            "364.00",
            "910.00",
            "330.91",
            "325.00",
            "303.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cesar consumes 713 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Harley is 26 years old. How much calories should Harley consume?",
        "answer": 1426,
        "options": [
            174,
            399,
            287,
            188,
            1426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a laptop in 27 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            64,
            39,
            82,
            17,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a phone in 50 minutes. How much time will it take for a 2 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            21,
            35,
            21,
            53,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 48 30 40 15 37 ",
        "answer": "37.00",
        "options": [
            "48.00",
            "30.00",
            "30.00",
            "37.00",
            "40.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 316 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 306,
        "options": [
            365,
            306,
            128,
            483,
            313
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah consumes 609 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Bishop is 30 years old. How much calories should Bishop consume?",
        "answer": 1218,
        "options": [
            320,
            196,
            1218,
            227,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 294 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            26,
            54,
            10,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 292 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            95,
            30,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            -1,
            3,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            46,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            "13",
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 338 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 335,
        "options": [
            139,
            335,
            262,
            560,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Messiah sold a book to Guillermo at a price of 797 after giving 64 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2213.89",
        "options": [
            "2213.89",
            "538.51",
            "485.98",
            "527.12",
            "603.79"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamison consumes 961 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Kalel is 35 years old. How much calories should Kalel consume?",
        "answer": 1922,
        "options": [
            518,
            206,
            348,
            1922,
            271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 44 * 55. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "26*48",
        "options": [
            "83*110",
            "68*99",
            "26*48",
            "87*62",
            "52*100"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            145,
            133,
            121,
            122,
            123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 1 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            -29,
            -21,
            -17,
            -3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 119 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            41,
            47,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            74,
            74,
            59,
            54,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 278 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            14,
            50,
            "25",
            90,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aaron and Jeffery are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aaron consumes 2560 calories per day whereas Jeffery consumes 2551 calories per day. Aaron is weaker than Jeffery.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 290 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            2,
            27,
            46,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 39 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "19*49",
        "options": [
            "19*49",
            "58*85",
            "48*99",
            "49*60",
            "73*73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaylen and Davis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaylen consumes 1727 calories per day whereas Davis consumes 2935 calories per day. Jaylen is less weight than Davis.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 35, 49, 96. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thiago consumes 847 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Gibson is 25 years old. How much calories should Gibson consume?",
        "answer": 1694,
        "options": [
            325,
            182,
            446,
            1694,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 48 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            38,
            31,
            29,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Andy and Casen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Andy consumes 1961 calories per day whereas Casen consumes 2403 calories per day. Andy is less weight than Casen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 177 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            81,
            99,
            92,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            66,
            58,
            83,
            65,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erick and Khari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erick consumes 1955 calories per day whereas Khari consumes 2380 calories per day. Erick is lighter than Khari.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Evan is younger than Jagger by 2 years. 14 years ago Jagger was 25 years old. What is Evan 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "69",
            "41",
            "45",
            "55",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 277 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "53",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            17,
            "53",
            94,
            98,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 135 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            34,
            19,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            51,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caleb and Arian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caleb consumes 2551 calories per day whereas Arian consumes 2232 calories per day. Caleb is weaker than Arian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezra consumes 723 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Vance is 28 years old. How much calories should Vance consume?",
        "answer": 1446,
        "options": [
            216,
            1446,
            187,
            374,
            287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 65 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            42,
            125,
            82,
            44,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 143 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            88,
            "21",
            7,
            44,
            14,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 382 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            65,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            35,
            77,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 473 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "149",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            65,
            57,
            99,
            65,
            "149"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Israel and Zev are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Israel consumes 2441 calories per day whereas Zev consumes 1911 calories per day. Israel is weaker than Zev.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Elian sold a book to Gibson at a price of 702 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "888.61",
        "options": [
            "888.61",
            "601.03",
            "580.17",
            "606.48",
            "635.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 137 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            14,
            "Not possible",
            30,
            47,
            "Not possible",
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            89,
            81,
            76,
            96,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 22 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            9,
            14,
            19,
            16,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 235 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 227,
        "options": [
            87,
            245,
            178,
            411,
            227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kendrick and Deshawn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kendrick consumes 1904 calories per day whereas Deshawn consumes 2746 calories per day. Kendrick is bulkier than Deshawn.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kingston and Marcelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kingston consumes 2016 calories per day whereas Marcelo consumes 2037 calories per day. Kingston is less weight than Marcelo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Landen sold a book to Huxley at a price of 497 after giving 73 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1840.74",
        "options": [
            "321.16",
            "287.28",
            "1840.74",
            "364.10",
            "313.76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sullivan and Ridge are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sullivan consumes 2887 calories per day whereas Ridge consumes 2035 calories per day. Sullivan is lighter than Ridge.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 190 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            "25",
            75,
            27,
            90,
            46,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhys and Izaiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhys consumes 2080 calories per day whereas Izaiah consumes 1600 calories per day. Rhys is more weight than Izaiah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 320 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            4,
            61,
            83,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tantalium is 3350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8835",
            "13417",
            "4449",
            "12842",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            122,
            110,
            125,
            95,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 87 minutes. What is the temperature after 87 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            97,
            92,
            58,
            78,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jeremiah and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jeremiah consumes 2765 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 2375 calories per day. Jeremiah is stronger than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            6,
            10,
            -1,
            5,
            -20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a airpods in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 12 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            28,
            21,
            41,
            62,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            63,
            72,
            72,
            49,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            1,
            5,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 130 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            15,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moses and Genesis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moses consumes 1814 calories per day whereas Genesis consumes 1743 calories per day. Moses is less weight than Genesis.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Josue and Huxley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Josue consumes 1656 calories per day whereas Huxley consumes 2907 calories per day. Josue is less weight than Huxley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakota consumes 950 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Maison is 30 years old. How much calories should Maison consume?",
        "answer": 1900,
        "options": [
            235,
            517,
            332,
            258,
            1900
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Liam by 5 years. 15 years ago Liam was 28 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "53",
            "53",
            "48",
            "53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4051",
            "12543",
            "343",
            "12100",
            "3626"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a phone in 26 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            66,
            14,
            88,
            66,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given martians ? 8 30 40 16 9 22 1 24 8 36 36 34 46 32 16 1 2 24 48 50 14 35 1 5 3 10 10 37 11 2 17 37 39 38 17 9 45 48 ",
        "answer": "19.50",
        "options": [
            "11.00",
            "32.00",
            "19.50",
            "17.00",
            "5.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 348 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            91,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a airpods in 31 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            19,
            23,
            6,
            22,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakota runs at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Payton 's place which is 108 km away?",
        "answer": "5.68",
        "options": [
            "28.42",
            "22.74",
            "5.68",
            "28.42",
            "22.74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "261",
            "246",
            "122",
            "3350",
            "129"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10710",
            "343",
            "6504",
            "14302",
            "12595"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 102 . We turned on the cooler for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            134,
            115,
            104,
            100,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erik and Westley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erik consumes 2142 calories per day whereas Westley consumes 1824 calories per day. Erik is stronger than Westley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            26,
            20,
            31,
            11,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 334 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 329,
        "options": [
            329,
            300,
            658,
            75,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 73, 34, 73. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dax and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dax consumes 2348 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 2572 calories per day. Dax is less weight than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            56,
            41,
            45,
            41,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            149,
            124,
            119,
            116,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3416",
            "1219",
            "343",
            "4767",
            "8460"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 137 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            29,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            51,
            33,
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 262 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            30,
            63,
            31,
            3,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaden consumes 992 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Kaison is 26 years old. How much calories should Kaison consume?",
        "answer": 1984,
        "options": [
            524,
            277,
            1984,
            216,
            344
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 628 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2512,
        "options": [
            3140,
            3140,
            3140,
            "2512",
            3140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4937",
            "5621",
            "2025",
            "343",
            "2893"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 117 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            127,
            22,
            52,
            113,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber butyl ?",
        "answer": "1830",
        "options": [
            "208",
            "1830",
            "113",
            "202",
            "110"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 252 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 241,
        "options": [
            193,
            241,
            46,
            435,
            283
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaac sold a book to Zayd at a price of 368 after giving 37 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "584.13",
        "options": [
            "310.55",
            "288.06",
            "268.61",
            "283.95",
            "584.13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 33 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            27,
            39,
            32,
            26,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 287 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 277,
        "options": [
            341,
            367,
            277,
            470,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ali and Dangelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ali consumes 1874 calories per day whereas Dangelo consumes 1999 calories per day. Ali is less weight than Dangelo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 70 minutes. What is the temperature after 70 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            119,
            103,
            120,
            126,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 14 watt charger charges a phone in 50 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            57,
            87,
            75,
            70,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Keegan and Kaison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Keegan consumes 1741 calories per day whereas Kaison consumes 2347 calories per day. Keegan is less weight than Kaison.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 323 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 318,
        "options": [
            339,
            459,
            318,
            94,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pedro and Apollo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pedro consumes 2156 calories per day whereas Apollo consumes 2747 calories per day. Pedro is weaker than Apollo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Finley consumes 695 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Cayson is 32 years old. How much calories should Cayson consume?",
        "answer": 1390,
        "options": [
            277,
            182,
            201,
            1390,
            369
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 325 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            93,
            70,
            67,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 324 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible",
            24,
            84,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dante sold a book to Lionel at a price of 403 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "407.07",
        "options": [
            "399.80",
            "400.00",
            "401.00",
            "407.07",
            "399.01"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given cats ? 2 46 19 47 31 46 43 18 25 20 47 32 28 41 20 20 46 32 ",
        "answer": "31.28",
        "options": [
            "93.84",
            "62.56",
            "93.84",
            "62.56",
            "31.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 12 41 15 24 3 31 29 24 37 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "3.00",
            "24.00",
            "12.00",
            "24.00",
            "24.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 42 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            39,
            32,
            35,
            46,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 11 35 10 45 46 41 37 3 39 5 3 40 14 20 24 22 30 48 43 49 25 17 46 2 26 43 48 32 4 41 13 16 6 38 22 43 34 ",
        "answer": "27.59",
        "options": [
            "110.36",
            "55.18",
            "82.77",
            "82.77",
            "27.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Easton sold a book to Otis at a price of 989 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1030.21",
        "options": [
            "1030.21",
            "960.19",
            "969.61",
            "958.33",
            "950.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 465 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            33,
            1,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            21,
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benson sold a book to Boone at a price of 461 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "823.21",
        "options": [
            "377.87",
            "823.21",
            "346.62",
            "340.98",
            "320.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 70 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            77,
            106,
            91,
            67,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kieran sold a book to Tatum at a price of 452 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1221.62",
        "options": [
            "277.30",
            "300.53",
            "306.96",
            "343.73",
            "1221.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 265 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 261,
        "options": [
            106,
            261,
            267,
            284,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 108 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            188,
            102,
            49,
            186,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            72,
            63,
            69,
            58,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca sold a book to Carl at a price of 376 after giving 22 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "482.05",
        "options": [
            "322.75",
            "482.05",
            "319.73",
            "308.20",
            "338.74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            11,
            6,
            2,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            18,
            142,
            9,
            17,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kayden and Byron are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kayden consumes 1522 calories per day whereas Byron consumes 2977 calories per day. Kayden is weaker than Byron.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dexter and Damari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dexter consumes 1854 calories per day whereas Damari consumes 2262 calories per day. Dexter is lighter than Damari.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 532 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2128,
        "options": [
            3192,
            "2128",
            3724,
            3724,
            2660
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lucite ?",
        "answer": "2680",
        "options": [
            "273",
            "2680",
            "298",
            "148",
            "140"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angelo drives at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Duke 's place which is 182 km away?",
        "answer": "16.55",
        "options": [
            "16.55",
            "49.64",
            "49.64",
            "66.18",
            "33.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hugo consumes 948 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Emory is 32 years old. How much calories should Emory consume?",
        "answer": 1896,
        "options": [
            515,
            342,
            231,
            273,
            1896
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 299 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            3,
            "Not possible",
            18,
            31,
            "Not possible",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            58,
            60,
            64,
            29,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given kangaroos ? 8 5 1 42 16 4 37 ",
        "answer": "16.14",
        "options": [
            "64.56",
            "64.56",
            "64.56",
            "16.14",
            "48.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Antonio and Jermaine are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Antonio consumes 2355 calories per day whereas Jermaine consumes 2485 calories per day. Antonio is weaker than Jermaine.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hector and Kendall are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hector consumes 1627 calories per day whereas Kendall consumes 2287 calories per day. Hector is heavier than Kendall.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson consumes 596 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Jasiah is 24 years old. How much calories should Jasiah consume?",
        "answer": 1192,
        "options": [
            344,
            161,
            1192,
            241,
            162
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a laptop in 20 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            16,
            1,
            4,
            18,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Barrett and Payton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Barrett consumes 2084 calories per day whereas Payton consumes 2642 calories per day. Barrett is less weight than Payton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny runs at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jeffery 's place which is 190 km away?",
        "answer": "17.27",
        "options": [
            "17.27",
            "34.55",
            "51.82",
            "51.82",
            "51.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Omar consumes 621 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Duncan is 29 years old. How much calories should Duncan consume?",
        "answer": 1242,
        "options": [
            1242,
            174,
            144,
            357,
            239
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker sold a book to Keenan at a price of 875 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1988.64",
        "options": [
            "560.90",
            "604.28",
            "683.59",
            "616.20",
            "1988.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 238 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            75,
            73,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 268 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 261,
        "options": [
            149,
            116,
            14,
            261,
            438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            123,
            121,
            108,
            115,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason is younger than Thatcher by 3 years. 10 years ago Thatcher was 25 years old. What is Jason 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "32",
            "38",
            "61",
            "48",
            "51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 63 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            59,
            79,
            56,
            61,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carlos and Orlando are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carlos consumes 2704 calories per day whereas Orlando consumes 2086 calories per day. Carlos is heavier than Orlando.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Eduardo consumes 550 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Kaiser is 25 years old. How much calories should Kaiser consume?",
        "answer": 1100,
        "options": [
            133,
            1100,
            317,
            160,
            230
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 251 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "453",
        "options": [
            96,
            "Not possible",
            39,
            63,
            30,
            "453"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            79,
            64,
            86,
            111,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in steel is 5940. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3286",
            "343",
            "2165",
            "13037",
            "6608"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 72, 36, 72. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            32,
            24,
            26,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            106,
            120,
            115,
            109,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 418 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "247",
        "options": [
            48,
            85,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            88,
            "247"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 459 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            39,
            53,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tungsten carbide is 6655. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5831",
            "8689",
            "964",
            "10983",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            68,
            46,
            86,
            72,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 187 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            82,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            35,
            "Not possible",
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 342 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            2,
            "Not possible",
            47,
            54,
            "15",
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 30 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            29,
            33,
            28,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            26,
            8,
            15,
            34,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joel sold a book to Korbyn at a price of 901 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2047.73",
        "options": [
            "577.56",
            "634.51",
            "703.91",
            "622.24",
            "2047.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 231 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            62,
            4,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            72,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nash sold a book to Dakari at a price of 949 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "978.35",
        "options": [
            "928.12",
            "978.35",
            "926.76",
            "921.36",
            "934.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            -8,
            12,
            0,
            -10,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 183 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "279",
        "options": [
            "279",
            "Not possible",
            36,
            57,
            27,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            11,
            5,
            7,
            142,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than William by 1 years. 6 years ago William was 29 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "38",
            "36",
            "46",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 156 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "79",
        "options": [
            80,
            15,
            "79",
            62,
            "Not possible",
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 326 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1304,
        "options": [
            1630,
            "1304",
            1630,
            1956,
            1630
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            22,
            "17",
            14,
            55,
            56,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo sold a book to Zakai at a price of 603 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1370.45",
        "options": [
            "424.65",
            "1370.45",
            "471.09",
            "416.44",
            "386.54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            20,
            47,
            51,
            56,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 361 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            34,
            "Not possible",
            17,
            74,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jamison and Tristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jamison consumes 2257 calories per day whereas Tristian consumes 2738 calories per day. Jamison is bulkier than Tristian.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Emanuel and Stanley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Emanuel consumes 2692 calories per day whereas Stanley consumes 2840 calories per day. Emanuel is bulkier than Stanley.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            28,
            68,
            76,
            "17",
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oliver and Ray are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oliver consumes 2892 calories per day whereas Ray consumes 1960 calories per day. Oliver is less weight than Ray.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 74, 47, 59. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 268 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            52,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            74,
            "Not possible",
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a phone in 47 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            15,
            44,
            57,
            43,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin consumes 507 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Ernest is 30 years old. How much calories should Ernest consume?",
        "answer": 1014,
        "options": [
            1014,
            132,
            140,
            296,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the cooler for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            72,
            72,
            84,
            63,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber gum ?",
        "answer": "1550",
        "options": [
            "189",
            "161",
            "119",
            "323",
            "1550"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gregory walks at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Braylon 's place which is 160 km away?",
        "answer": "11.43",
        "options": [
            "45.71",
            "57.14",
            "11.43",
            "34.29",
            "22.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 266 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "251",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            92,
            24,
            85,
            "251",
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            59,
            64,
            80,
            41,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 346 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 342,
        "options": [
            101,
            438,
            342,
            326,
            332
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 494 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "463",
        "options": [
            30,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            96,
            "463",
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Paxton and Duke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Paxton consumes 2022 calories per day whereas Duke consumes 2220 calories per day. Paxton is more weight than Duke.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Kieran consumes 902 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Kohen is 21 years old. How much calories should Kohen consume?",
        "answer": 1804,
        "options": [
            215,
            495,
            347,
            1804,
            262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cristian consumes 895 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Onyx is 27 years old. How much calories should Onyx consume?",
        "answer": 1790,
        "options": [
            1790,
            486,
            257,
            212,
            320
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 60 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            1,
            44,
            47,
            53,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jensen and Cayson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jensen consumes 2323 calories per day whereas Cayson consumes 2168 calories per day. Jensen is heavier than Cayson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 498 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            59,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            72,
            61,
            75,
            64,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tucker and Melvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tucker consumes 1839 calories per day whereas Melvin consumes 2365 calories per day. Tucker is less weight than Melvin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            60,
            66,
            74,
            59,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "3810",
            "317",
            "314",
            "278",
            "321"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 303 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            82,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            79,
            46,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colt and Draven are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colt consumes 1672 calories per day whereas Draven consumes 1609 calories per day. Colt is stronger than Draven.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 360 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "333",
        "options": [
            "333",
            66,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luka and Keaton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luka consumes 2905 calories per day whereas Keaton consumes 2259 calories per day. Luka is weaker than Keaton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 10 watt charger charges a airpods in 19 minutes. How much time will it take for a 13 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            53,
            79,
            64,
            65,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 231 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            17,
            56,
            12,
            "Not possible",
            "25",
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            35,
            54,
            26,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Manuel sold a book to Sam at a price of 298 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "377.22",
        "options": [
            "257.45",
            "269.68",
            "255.14",
            "377.22",
            "246.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 179 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            96,
            60,
            "27",
            7,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 60 * 58. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "42*33",
        "options": [
            "42*33",
            "88*104",
            "91*111",
            "72*96",
            "78*91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 202 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 191,
        "options": [
            212,
            111,
            348,
            114,
            191
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 67, 41, 72. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            96,
            99,
            103,
            101,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a powerbank in 47 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            22,
            32,
            14,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 551 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2204,
        "options": [
            5510,
            3857,
            4408,
            4408,
            "2204"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 115 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            106,
            138,
            52,
            182,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dominick sold a book to Rene at a price of 628 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2242.86",
        "options": [
            "407.79",
            "2242.86",
            "461.76",
            "398.48",
            "365.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Peyton and Zev are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Peyton consumes 2156 calories per day whereas Zev consumes 1760 calories per day. Peyton is stronger than Zev.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Cameron consumes 661 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Fisher is 20 years old. How much calories should Fisher consume?",
        "answer": 1322,
        "options": [
            268,
            350,
            143,
            1322,
            182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ian and Boden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ian consumes 1525 calories per day whereas Boden consumes 1588 calories per day. Ian is stronger than Boden.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 47. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "22*45",
        "options": [
            "66*49",
            "77*74",
            "22*45",
            "44*56",
            "75*84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finn consumes 593 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Eddie is 29 years old. How much calories should Eddie consume?",
        "answer": 1186,
        "options": [
            182,
            341,
            1186,
            246,
            157
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 46 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            39,
            29,
            44,
            47,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Thiago and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Thiago consumes 1575 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2200 calories per day. Thiago is bulkier than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Jonas is younger than Ayaan by 4 years. 6 years ago Ayaan was 30 years old. What is Jonas 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "32",
            "52",
            "60",
            "48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 466 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            56,
            71,
            "27",
            73,
            "Not possible",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zachariah and Aryan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zachariah consumes 1760 calories per day whereas Aryan consumes 2094 calories per day. Zachariah is bulkier than Aryan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kayden and Raylan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kayden consumes 2657 calories per day whereas Raylan consumes 1526 calories per day. Kayden is lighter than Raylan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 231 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 222,
        "options": [
            407,
            370,
            369,
            222,
            411
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mateo and Fisher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mateo consumes 1515 calories per day whereas Fisher consumes 1808 calories per day. Mateo is stronger than Fisher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 53 minutes. What is the temperature after 53 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            38,
            18,
            43,
            47,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 104 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            117,
            103,
            16,
            132,
            190
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            44,
            40,
            37,
            32,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 192 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            13,
            "11",
            50,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 320 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 310,
        "options": [
            125,
            11,
            310,
            572,
            166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pablo sold a book to Magnus at a price of 197 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "820.83",
        "options": [
            "122.51",
            "142.75",
            "111.93",
            "125.48",
            "820.83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass light crown is 5100. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2065",
            "4551",
            "5056",
            "12082",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dominick sold a book to Ford at a price of 725 after giving 48 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1394.23",
        "options": [
            "1394.23",
            "523.84",
            "533.09",
            "489.86",
            "584.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            39,
            41,
            26,
            35,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 273 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 272,
        "options": [
            269,
            343,
            8,
            429,
            272
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a airpods in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            90,
            76,
            69,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny consumes 729 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Lyle is 38 years old. How much calories should Lyle consume?",
        "answer": 1458,
        "options": [
            383,
            290,
            1458,
            202,
            172
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lucite is 2680. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6532",
            "343",
            "5860",
            "12895",
            "12641"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 349 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "67",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "67",
            78,
            92,
            54,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mario and Harry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mario consumes 2847 calories per day whereas Harry consumes 2389 calories per day. Mario is heavier than Harry.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a phone in 42 minutes. How much time will it take for a 25 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            61,
            55,
            51,
            97,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maxwell and Ariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maxwell consumes 2194 calories per day whereas Ariel consumes 2828 calories per day. Maxwell is stronger than Ariel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 809 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3236,
        "options": [
            8090,
            4045,
            "3236",
            6472,
            4854
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            26,
            12,
            37,
            2,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rory is younger than Ulises by 3 years. 14 years ago Ulises was 31 years old. What is Rory 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "48",
            "54",
            "51",
            "65",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 184 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            27,
            "15",
            57,
            66,
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 187 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 182,
        "options": [
            273,
            32,
            288,
            240,
            182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            130,
            109,
            118,
            96,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a powerbank in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            48,
            95,
            88,
            29,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both River and Kabir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. River consumes 2583 calories per day whereas Kabir consumes 2924 calories per day. River is weaker than Kabir.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Levi consumes 696 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Marcelo is 20 years old. How much calories should Marcelo consume?",
        "answer": 1392,
        "options": [
            198,
            379,
            265,
            184,
            1392
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaiden sold a book to Jaxen at a price of 344 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "358.33",
        "options": [
            "358.33",
            "337.25",
            "330.77",
            "333.33",
            "333.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kayden and Scott are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kayden consumes 2450 calories per day whereas Scott consumes 2038 calories per day. Kayden is weaker than Scott.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 450 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            15,
            "Not possible",
            44,
            38,
            "Not possible",
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 133 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "19",
            "Not possible",
            37,
            52,
            4,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Daniel and Cassius are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Daniel consumes 2901 calories per day whereas Cassius consumes 1795 calories per day. Daniel is lighter than Cassius.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 48 * 46. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "41*33",
        "options": [
            "59*75",
            "68*59",
            "41*33",
            "52*66",
            "98*72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan is younger than Ryland by 3 years. 8 years ago Ryland was 35 years old. What is Donovan 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "68",
            "40",
            "52",
            "62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malcolm consumes 591 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Benedict is 38 years old. How much calories should Benedict consume?",
        "answer": 1182,
        "options": [
            197,
            1182,
            316,
            233,
            145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Daxton and Callen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Daxton consumes 2247 calories per day whereas Callen consumes 1572 calories per day. Daxton is weaker than Callen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Theo and Yael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Theo consumes 2348 calories per day whereas Yael consumes 1928 calories per day. Theo is stronger than Yael.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            76,
            97,
            86,
            105,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander sold a book to Anders at a price of 136 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "251.85",
        "options": [
            "93.15",
            "99.42",
            "101.12",
            "251.85",
            "110.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "45",
        "options": [
            31,
            50,
            94,
            71,
            "45",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            83,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            "Not possible",
            50,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malakai and Chaim are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malakai consumes 3000 calories per day whereas Chaim consumes 2695 calories per day. Malakai is bulkier than Chaim.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 308 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            42,
            45,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than James by 4 years. 10 years ago James was 27 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "43",
            "45",
            "49",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gael is younger than Kyng by 1 years. 9 years ago Kyng was 31 years old. What is Gael 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "60",
            "39",
            "60",
            "50",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 387 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "147",
        "options": [
            97,
            35,
            97,
            "147",
            40,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillip sold a book to Creed at a price of 361 after giving 25 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "481.33",
        "options": [
            "288.80",
            "300.83",
            "304.00",
            "320.89",
            "481.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given human ? 16 32 34 11 50 32 28 29 11 50 7 33 2 49 1 48 41 35 14 38 27 48 28 10 29 16 11 20 43 1 25 4 22 23 11 19 19 39 5 1 17 13 37 24 32 47 50 5 17 25 ",
        "answer": "24.58",
        "options": [
            "98.32",
            "122.90",
            "24.58",
            "73.74",
            "49.16"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 292 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            17,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            29,
            "25",
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jake and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jake consumes 1660 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 2095 calories per day. Jake is lighter than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jett and Benton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jett consumes 2122 calories per day whereas Benton consumes 2115 calories per day. Jett is more weight than Benton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckham and Coen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckham consumes 2125 calories per day whereas Coen consumes 2274 calories per day. Beckham is stronger than Coen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryker consumes 989 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Marcel is 36 years old. How much calories should Marcel consume?",
        "answer": 1978,
        "options": [
            531,
            1978,
            373,
            244,
            276
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 94 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            17,
            176,
            88,
            171,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 442 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            "37",
            "Not possible",
            63,
            26,
            85,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            61,
            66,
            62,
            61,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 311 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 307,
        "options": [
            307,
            424,
            371,
            506,
            158
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            9,
            12,
            19,
            10,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            -6,
            22,
            0,
            2,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 170 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            86,
            29,
            "Not possible",
            68,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            22,
            2,
            18,
            1009,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kieran sold a book to Elisha at a price of 600 after giving 55 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1333.33",
        "options": [
            "387.10",
            "424.78",
            "470.59",
            "1333.33",
            "416.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            -9,
            -4,
            1,
            -2,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            51,
            62,
            48,
            46,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Garrett and Jacoby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Garrett consumes 2234 calories per day whereas Jacoby consumes 1816 calories per day. Garrett is weaker than Jacoby.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 397 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            25,
            62,
            8,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 253 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 244,
        "options": [
            68,
            315,
            142,
            466,
            244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            -5,
            10,
            5,
            -6,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marcos sold a book to Langston at a price of 805 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "981.71",
        "options": [
            "738.53",
            "703.67",
            "981.71",
            "709.25",
            "682.20"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            15,
            3,
            1979,
            4,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 364 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            47,
            98,
            68,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Axel and Kylen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Axel consumes 2018 calories per day whereas Kylen consumes 2338 calories per day. Axel is more weight than Kylen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 120 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            66,
            59,
            68,
            59,
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in water is 1496. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9422",
            "8755",
            "343",
            "6947",
            "7175"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given human ? 14 17 29 7 21 21 15 42 33 20 31 15 44 47 25 43 39 36 25 7 35 31 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "44.00",
            "20.00",
            "25.00",
            "27.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca is younger than Marc by 2 years. 13 years ago Marc was 27 years old. What is Luca 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "59",
            "68",
            "70",
            "44",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            296,
            1979,
            171,
            128,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin consumes 701 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Byron is 32 years old. How much calories should Byron consume?",
        "answer": 1402,
        "options": [
            1402,
            248,
            387,
            218,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given tigers ? 43 39 45 3 23 11 24 4 45 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "24.00",
            "45.00",
            "24.00",
            "45.00",
            "43.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Karter is younger than Jaxen by 4 years. 14 years ago Jaxen was 29 years old. What is Karter 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "47",
            "75",
            "69",
            "61"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kenneth and Aries are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kenneth consumes 1887 calories per day whereas Aries consumes 2622 calories per day. Kenneth is less weight than Aries.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 177 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            66,
            46,
            "47",
            "Not possible",
            2,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 792 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3168,
        "options": [
            "3168",
            3960,
            4752,
            4752,
            6336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malachi and Carl are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malachi consumes 2811 calories per day whereas Carl consumes 2762 calories per day. Malachi is lighter than Carl.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            31,
            39,
            30,
            34,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            57,
            54,
            62,
            83,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 53 minutes. What is the temperature after 53 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            46,
            28,
            37,
            52,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            93,
            82,
            68,
            74,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ezra and Fletcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ezra consumes 2109 calories per day whereas Fletcher consumes 2990 calories per day. Ezra is bulkier than Fletcher.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            63,
            81,
            70,
            65,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 168 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 166,
        "options": [
            166,
            97,
            53,
            160,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 64, 40, 76. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaylen sold a book to Kyree at a price of 478 after giving 7 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "513.98",
        "options": [
            "513.98",
            "446.73",
            "461.84",
            "452.65",
            "454.16"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Damien and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Damien consumes 2811 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 1996 calories per day. Damien is stronger than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Emanuel sold a book to Benton at a price of 662 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1742.11",
        "options": [
            "442.51",
            "451.88",
            "1742.11",
            "505.34",
            "408.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            37,
            31,
            25,
            37,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Michael and Mohammed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Michael consumes 2759 calories per day whereas Mohammed consumes 2210 calories per day. Michael is lighter than Mohammed.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            111,
            106,
            101,
            99,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Fabian and Jesiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Fabian consumes 2846 calories per day whereas Jesiah consumes 1754 calories per day. Fabian is more weight than Jesiah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            123,
            124,
            150,
            105,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Julian and Karsyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Julian consumes 2499 calories per day whereas Karsyn consumes 2485 calories per day. Julian is weaker than Karsyn.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14536",
            "343",
            "10669",
            "2291",
            "9943"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 923 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3692,
        "options": [
            9230,
            9230,
            "3692",
            9230,
            4615
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luis and Kylen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luis consumes 2783 calories per day whereas Kylen consumes 2339 calories per day. Luis is more weight than Kylen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Bodhi is younger than Layne by 1 years. 9 years ago Layne was 25 years old. What is Bodhi 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "35",
            "46",
            "33",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 226 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            62,
            56,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            111,
            115,
            101,
            102,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William sold a book to Idris at a price of 654 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2515.38",
        "options": [
            "477.37",
            "2515.38",
            "410.80",
            "420.58",
            "375.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            38,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            77,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 299 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 32 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            46,
            14,
            27,
            15,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 896 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3584,
        "options": [
            8064,
            "3584",
            8064,
            4480,
            4480
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 452 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "23",
            69,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            18,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Killian and Aries are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Killian consumes 1885 calories per day whereas Aries consumes 2441 calories per day. Killian is stronger than Aries.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            61,
            59,
            54,
            65,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than James by 5 years. 6 years ago James was 32 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "40",
            "43",
            "45",
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brick is 4200. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5549",
            "343",
            "14168",
            "13658",
            "5873"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kian and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kian consumes 1776 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 2259 calories per day. Kian is weaker than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            112,
            110,
            107,
            140,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cyrus and Fisher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cyrus consumes 2567 calories per day whereas Fisher consumes 2925 calories per day. Cyrus is heavier than Fisher.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 157 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            110,
            295,
            151,
            185,
            182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the heater for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            48,
            59,
            48,
            48,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            79,
            103,
            68,
            73,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            93,
            43,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            66,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maverick and Kalel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maverick consumes 2586 calories per day whereas Kalel consumes 2050 calories per day. Maverick is weaker than Kalel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 142 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            49,
            26,
            "27",
            7,
            68,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayden sold a book to Elisha at a price of 401 after giving 77 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1743.48",
        "options": [
            "289.53",
            "226.55",
            "254.20",
            "1743.48",
            "248.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Drew sold a book to Makai at a price of 157 after giving 33 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "234.33",
        "options": [
            "124.21",
            "134.76",
            "118.05",
            "125.85",
            "234.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker consumes 521 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Dillon is 23 years old. How much calories should Dillon consume?",
        "answer": 1042,
        "options": [
            129,
            289,
            1042,
            209,
            149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 145 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 136,
        "options": [
            43,
            168,
            178,
            205,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "122",
            "155",
            "5950",
            "181",
            "230"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Francis and Taylor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Francis consumes 2646 calories per day whereas Taylor consumes 2525 calories per day. Francis is heavier than Taylor.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 228 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "17",
            57,
            "Not possible",
            88,
            25,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in manganese ?",
        "answer": "4660",
        "options": [
            "4660",
            "159",
            "112",
            "237",
            "137"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Oliver by 5 years. 9 years ago Oliver was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "47",
            "44",
            "47",
            "42",
            "29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            25,
            7,
            3,
            25,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            66,
            106,
            82,
            95,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 240 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 233,
        "options": [
            383,
            21,
            94,
            356,
            233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than William by 2 years. 13 years ago William was 29 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "53",
            "44",
            "49",
            "62",
            "64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 328 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            51,
            11,
            "39",
            60,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 18 watt charger charges a powerbank in 25 minutes. How much time will it take for a 10 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            9,
            15,
            15,
            7,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mohamed and Rayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mohamed consumes 2615 calories per day whereas Rayan consumes 2465 calories per day. Mohamed is weaker than Rayan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            5,
            3,
            4,
            3,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 29 22 11 18 42 11 17 2 40 46 33 39 10 22 7 41 39 36 41 26 7 36 16 37 2 ",
        "answer": "26.00",
        "options": [
            "11.00",
            "26.00",
            "37.00",
            "42.00",
            "11.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Parker and Genesis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Parker consumes 2787 calories per day whereas Genesis consumes 2276 calories per day. Parker is less weight than Genesis.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 111 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            20,
            "11",
            86,
            79,
            34,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hank and Kingsley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hank consumes 2788 calories per day whereas Kingsley consumes 1504 calories per day. Hank is lighter than Kingsley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luke and Jeffery are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luke consumes 2774 calories per day whereas Jeffery consumes 2706 calories per day. Luke is heavier than Jeffery.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 53 * 32. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "32*23",
        "options": [
            "56*51",
            "87*46",
            "32*23",
            "75*61",
            "100*50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            27,
            24,
            22,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace consumes 544 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Madden is 28 years old. How much calories should Madden consume?",
        "answer": 1088,
        "options": [
            1088,
            194,
            302,
            168,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 264 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            79,
            37,
            59,
            14,
            "Not possible",
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            75,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kameron and Shiloh are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kameron consumes 2482 calories per day whereas Shiloh consumes 2375 calories per day. Kameron is heavier than Shiloh.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Noel consumes 762 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Brixton is 39 years old. How much calories should Brixton consume?",
        "answer": 1524,
        "options": [
            411,
            304,
            224,
            188,
            1524
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            8,
            10,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            61,
            59,
            66,
            44,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a airpods in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            86,
            45,
            14,
            72,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber neoprene ?",
        "answer": "1600",
        "options": [
            "1600",
            "154",
            "304",
            "134",
            "174"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 257 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            66,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            61,
            "Not possible",
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 241 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            99,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            28,
            "Not possible",
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 7 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Heptagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Juan consumes 760 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. London is 30 years old. How much calories should London consume?",
        "answer": 1520,
        "options": [
            192,
            416,
            1520,
            207,
            295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Everett consumes 722 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Callum is 23 years old. How much calories should Callum consume?",
        "answer": 1444,
        "options": [
            182,
            259,
            228,
            1444,
            397
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Miguel and Dane are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Miguel consumes 2905 calories per day whereas Dane consumes 2832 calories per day. Miguel is stronger than Dane.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 409 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            100,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            76,
            "Not possible",
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 109,
        "options": [
            109,
            133,
            113,
            123,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 107 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            93,
            86,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "Not possible",
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Edgar and Asa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Edgar consumes 2417 calories per day whereas Asa consumes 2956 calories per day. Edgar is heavier than Asa.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 87 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            126,
            64,
            84,
            99,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Orion and Heath are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Orion consumes 2068 calories per day whereas Heath consumes 1960 calories per day. Orion is lighter than Heath.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given cats ? 27 11 39 5 34 44 39 45 47 12 23 36 40 17 11 32 47 46 1 15 35 13 35 41 45 6 38 2 2 21 18 31 36 4 12 25 32 7 46 47 6 16 26 31 19 37 19 38 1 45 ",
        "answer": "29.00",
        "options": [
            "41.00",
            "26.00",
            "6.00",
            "29.00",
            "47.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Logan and Ray are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Logan consumes 1541 calories per day whereas Ray consumes 2337 calories per day. Logan is lighter than Ray.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Caden consumes 625 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Nikolas is 29 years old. How much calories should Nikolas consume?",
        "answer": 1250,
        "options": [
            345,
            178,
            238,
            161,
            1250
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Louis and Azariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Louis consumes 1698 calories per day whereas Azariah consumes 2945 calories per day. Louis is weaker than Azariah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moises and Harlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moises consumes 1595 calories per day whereas Harlan consumes 2229 calories per day. Moises is heavier than Harlan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            19,
            59,
            51,
            38,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 156 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 145,
        "options": [
            162,
            88,
            64,
            145,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling sold a book to Valentino at a price of 943 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1683.93",
        "options": [
            "697.49",
            "654.86",
            "709.02",
            "1683.93",
            "772.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 227,
        "options": [
            188,
            220,
            119,
            16,
            227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakota sold a book to Marcelo at a price of 874 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1748.00",
        "options": [
            "624.29",
            "635.64",
            "699.20",
            "1748.00",
            "582.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 419 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            30,
            "Not possible",
            "27",
            22,
            45,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaleb sold a book to Rudy at a price of 718 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1527.66",
        "options": [
            "504.21",
            "1527.66",
            "513.77",
            "469.28",
            "567.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwin consumes 654 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Yael is 38 years old. How much calories should Yael consume?",
        "answer": 1308,
        "options": [
            346,
            234,
            1308,
            193,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Levi and Marcel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Levi consumes 1537 calories per day whereas Marcel consumes 2130 calories per day. Levi is bulkier than Marcel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 34 . We turned on the heater for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            17,
            42,
            32,
            24,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Omar and Anson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Omar consumes 2069 calories per day whereas Anson consumes 2316 calories per day. Omar is weaker than Anson.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joel and Johan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joel consumes 1709 calories per day whereas Johan consumes 2325 calories per day. Joel is weaker than Johan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moises and Wilder are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moises consumes 1639 calories per day whereas Wilder consumes 2572 calories per day. Moises is stronger than Wilder.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            67,
            32,
            52,
            52,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 276 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1104,
        "options": [
            2760,
            2208,
            1656,
            1380,
            "1104"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 346 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 341,
        "options": [
            238,
            546,
            578,
            341,
            468
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 37. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "29*19",
        "options": [
            "37*53",
            "72*42",
            "59*68",
            "29*19",
            "71*43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "261",
            "2620",
            "181",
            "189",
            "142"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 255 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 247,
        "options": [
            247,
            41,
            310,
            71,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            12,
            62,
            27,
            22,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            52,
            62,
            78,
            34,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 310 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            12,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            69,
            10,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brantley sold a book to Jaxtyn at a price of 714 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2975.00",
        "options": [
            "2975.00",
            "444.03",
            "454.78",
            "517.39",
            "405.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 473 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "61",
        "options": [
            23,
            55,
            12,
            "Not possible",
            "61",
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Damian and Dustin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Damian consumes 1712 calories per day whereas Dustin consumes 2553 calories per day. Damian is weaker than Dustin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Cade consumes 634 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Howard is 40 years old. How much calories should Howard consume?",
        "answer": 1268,
        "options": [
            158,
            204,
            252,
            351,
            1268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Victor and Maddux are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Victor consumes 1898 calories per day whereas Maddux consumes 1750 calories per day. Victor is stronger than Maddux.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a tablet in 27 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            67,
            16,
            24,
            15,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silica fused ?",
        "answer": "5968",
        "options": [
            "5968",
            "269",
            "198",
            "312",
            "140"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 26 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            46,
            5,
            46,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Greyson is younger than Kaiser by 3 years. 7 years ago Kaiser was 30 years old. What is Greyson 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "50",
            "46",
            "53",
            "50",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alexander and Gibson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alexander consumes 2098 calories per day whereas Gibson consumes 2502 calories per day. Alexander is more weight than Gibson.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 205 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 195,
        "options": [
            195,
            51,
            73,
            268,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            -4,
            -23,
            -2,
            2,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 258 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 255,
        "options": [
            334,
            287,
            255,
            215,
            226
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            22,
            26,
            26,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 457 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "33",
            84,
            "Not possible",
            87,
            18,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 49 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 196,
        "options": [
            490,
            294,
            "196",
            392,
            490
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            32,
            38,
            28,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gunnar and Merrick are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gunnar consumes 1848 calories per day whereas Merrick consumes 2405 calories per day. Gunnar is lighter than Merrick.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            124,
            138,
            112,
            117,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            1372,
            1930,
            1886,
            1364,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in mercury ?",
        "answer": "1540",
        "options": [
            "1540",
            "214",
            "213",
            "176",
            "158"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            354,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given cats ? 19 20 16 2 4 46 8 10 19 18 29 36 22 48 42 25 25 12 49 21 ",
        "answer": "20.50",
        "options": [
            "20.50",
            "22.00",
            "16.00",
            "4.00",
            "19.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 46 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            37,
            34,
            41,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Preston and Deandre are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Preston consumes 2095 calories per day whereas Deandre consumes 2217 calories per day. Preston is bulkier than Deandre.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 225 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            65,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            10,
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 486 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "181",
        "options": [
            28,
            "181",
            64,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dallas and Fletcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dallas consumes 2280 calories per day whereas Fletcher consumes 2412 calories per day. Dallas is lighter than Fletcher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a powerbank in 49 minutes. How much time will it take for a 29 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            58,
            97,
            50,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 90 . We turned on the cooler for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            92,
            98,
            83,
            92,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            77,
            56,
            54,
            49,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adonis consumes 670 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Anakin is 31 years old. How much calories should Anakin consume?",
        "answer": 1340,
        "options": [
            194,
            180,
            356,
            1340,
            252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 212 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 205,
        "options": [
            205,
            396,
            37,
            154,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jorge and Baker are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jorge consumes 1900 calories per day whereas Baker consumes 2386 calories per day. Jorge is less weight than Baker.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 105 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            73,
            "Not possible",
            56,
            14,
            46,
            "9"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            37,
            24,
            35,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Amir and Kace are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Amir consumes 2311 calories per day whereas Kace consumes 2049 calories per day. Amir is less weight than Kace.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mathias and Konnor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mathias consumes 2471 calories per day whereas Konnor consumes 2894 calories per day. Mathias is heavier than Konnor.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Walter and Wesson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Walter consumes 2730 calories per day whereas Wesson consumes 1728 calories per day. Walter is stronger than Wesson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Kairo sold a book to Alexzander at a price of 196 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "700.00",
        "options": [
            "700.00",
            "124.37",
            "144.12",
            "127.27",
            "113.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            35,
            29,
            49,
            34,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andre sold a book to Kylan at a price of 721 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "810.11",
        "options": [
            "662.68",
            "810.11",
            "683.41",
            "649.55",
            "666.05"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 240 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            94,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            62,
            "Not possible",
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 358 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            59,
            96,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            30,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 333 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "47",
            38,
            98,
            12,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given kangaroos ? 34 5 25 25 20 9 23 2 28 23 23 27 44 34 38 38 31 45 2 26 35 43 43 33 4 40 25 14 31 15 16 16 17 44 25 4 39 18 19 31 3 36 27 ",
        "answer": "25.12",
        "options": [
            "50.24",
            "75.36",
            "25.12",
            "125.60",
            "75.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Quinn sold a book to Joziah at a price of 501 after giving 23 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "650.65",
        "options": [
            "449.33",
            "407.32",
            "427.29",
            "650.65",
            "423.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 215 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 207,
        "options": [
            255,
            197,
            207,
            386,
            360
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cork is 518. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12735",
            "5216",
            "1319",
            "343",
            "13844"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 488 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            75,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            84,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 102 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            79,
            140,
            98,
            100,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            73,
            60,
            90,
            91,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a tablet in 18 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            32,
            24,
            18,
            52,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 30, 33, 117. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 31 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "16*24",
        "options": [
            "61*56",
            "16*24",
            "56*49",
            "44*49",
            "63*67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael sold a book to Willie at a price of 549 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "930.51",
        "options": [
            "419.89",
            "389.36",
            "455.60",
            "413.40",
            "930.51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            36,
            49,
            26,
            44,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gabriel and Thatcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gabriel consumes 2369 calories per day whereas Thatcher consumes 2359 calories per day. Gabriel is heavier than Thatcher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given dogs ? 26 3 11 19 30 13 1 50 9 35 5 9 28 28 3 22 10 31 34 11 20 17 26 22 ",
        "answer": "19.29",
        "options": [
            "19.29",
            "96.45",
            "38.58",
            "77.16",
            "38.58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 116 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            57,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            18,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 290 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            83,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            84,
            "Not possible",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 254 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            91,
            52,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cayden runs at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Randy 's place which is 135 km away?",
        "answer": "16.88",
        "options": [
            "50.62",
            "16.88",
            "84.38",
            "67.50",
            "33.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 228,
        "options": [
            9,
            259,
            228,
            126,
            294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "43",
            78,
            83,
            67,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kolton and Niko are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kolton consumes 2956 calories per day whereas Niko consumes 2821 calories per day. Kolton is less weight than Niko.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Waylon walks at a speed of 9 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Abdullah 's place which is 153 km away?",
        "answer": "17.00",
        "options": [
            "51.00",
            "68.00",
            "34.00",
            "17.00",
            "51.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kingston and Musa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kingston consumes 2026 calories per day whereas Musa consumes 1697 calories per day. Kingston is weaker than Musa.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 118 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            113,
            119,
            120,
            146,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 54 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            22,
            65,
            43,
            2,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 17 50 33 14 28 32 36 45 5 7 34 21 28 47 23 26 20 34 23 25 10 25 12 4 17 38 15 10 8 26 31 15 18 50 37 40 15 14 40 10 46 41 45 36 4 25 16 45 23 ",
        "answer": "25.80",
        "options": [
            "129.00",
            "77.40",
            "103.20",
            "25.80",
            "77.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 76, 49, 55. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 109,
        "options": [
            119,
            117,
            128,
            109,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            79,
            35,
            20,
            "Not possible",
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benson sold a book to Emmitt at a price of 507 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "582.76",
        "options": [
            "448.67",
            "582.76",
            "461.96",
            "459.24",
            "476.06"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Muhammad and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Muhammad consumes 1522 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 2602 calories per day. Muhammad is more weight than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Finnegan consumes 992 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Curtis is 25 years old. How much calories should Curtis consume?",
        "answer": 1984,
        "options": [
            276,
            208,
            523,
            1984,
            345
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emiliano consumes 978 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Emmitt is 26 years old. How much calories should Emmitt consume?",
        "answer": 1956,
        "options": [
            255,
            374,
            531,
            1956,
            226
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gael and Eddie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gael consumes 1503 calories per day whereas Eddie consumes 1961 calories per day. Gael is less weight than Eddie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            46,
            30,
            2,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayn and Cannon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayn consumes 2670 calories per day whereas Cannon consumes 1989 calories per day. Zayn is lighter than Cannon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 118 . We turned on the cooler for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 109,
        "options": [
            142,
            142,
            126,
            109,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 86, 52, 42. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ali and Zaid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ali consumes 2884 calories per day whereas Zaid consumes 1787 calories per day. Ali is bulkier than Zaid.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            57,
            45,
            51,
            35,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Romeo and Brycen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Romeo consumes 2452 calories per day whereas Brycen consumes 1591 calories per day. Romeo is lighter than Brycen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron cast is 4994. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6021",
            "343",
            "11284",
            "453",
            "13295"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "1447",
            "6917",
            "12619",
            "11137"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a laptop in 50 minutes. How much time will it take for a 24 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            66,
            93,
            57,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            133,
            106,
            108,
            98,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Drake sold a book to Keanu at a price of 301 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "345.98",
        "options": [
            "345.98",
            "274.26",
            "282.63",
            "272.64",
            "266.37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 472 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "55",
        "options": [
            13,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            3,
            "55",
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            50,
            28,
            98,
            56,
            1979
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 194 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            56,
            81,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            70,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 397 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            90,
            23,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 96 minutes. What is the temperature after 96 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            77,
            80,
            75,
            96,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 431 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marco and Darren are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marco consumes 1695 calories per day whereas Darren consumes 1625 calories per day. Marco is heavier than Darren.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Adriel sold a book to Keanu at a price of 767 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1180.00",
        "options": [
            "599.22",
            "652.77",
            "568.15",
            "607.52",
            "1180.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 336 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "615",
        "options": [
            61,
            "Not possible",
            "615",
            90,
            62,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 96 minutes. What is the temperature after 96 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            124,
            130,
            106,
            125,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 25 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            27,
            24,
            23,
            21,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14121",
            "7299",
            "7474",
            "12813",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            122,
            139,
            127,
            138,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 92 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            82,
            118,
            104,
            103,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Diego and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Diego consumes 2458 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 2666 calories per day. Diego is less weight than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 228 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            40,
            "Not possible",
            "47",
            82,
            87,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            145,
            118,
            107,
            118,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesse sold a book to Draven at a price of 324 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "549.15",
        "options": [
            "247.80",
            "549.15",
            "229.79",
            "268.88",
            "243.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            24,
            21,
            29,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            78,
            63,
            59,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 89 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            80,
            67,
            137,
            86,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 5 13 22 42 24 17 32 40 22 32 20 13 22 36 46 26 26 48 25 46 12 44 26 44 47 40 18 32 42 42 12 36 9 ",
        "answer": "29.12",
        "options": [
            "58.24",
            "29.12",
            "145.60",
            "87.36",
            "116.48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Declan and Ira are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Declan consumes 2129 calories per day whereas Ira consumes 2085 calories per day. Declan is weaker than Ira.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 53 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            73,
            16,
            48,
            54,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            16,
            22,
            42,
            26,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 438 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "207",
        "options": [
            94,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            64,
            "207",
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given elephants ? 16 29 5 7 24 11 47 22 26 21 22 6 19 12 ",
        "answer": "19.07",
        "options": [
            "57.21",
            "19.07",
            "38.14",
            "57.21",
            "38.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jase and Thatcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jase consumes 1958 calories per day whereas Thatcher consumes 2074 calories per day. Jase is weaker than Thatcher.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            -14,
            3,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caiden and Raul are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caiden consumes 2248 calories per day whereas Raul consumes 1612 calories per day. Caiden is less weight than Raul.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 134 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            2,
            "7",
            "Not possible",
            49,
            89,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gianni and Henrik are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gianni consumes 2878 calories per day whereas Henrik consumes 2045 calories per day. Gianni is less weight than Henrik.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 346 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            37,
            49,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            "Not possible",
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            54,
            6,
            41,
            62,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a laptop in 56 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            8,
            40,
            9,
            19,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 15 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            4,
            6,
            2,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 307 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            37,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            "17",
            52,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lucas consumes 857 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Makai is 29 years old. How much calories should Makai consume?",
        "answer": 1714,
        "options": [
            1714,
            224,
            199,
            449,
            324
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 314 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            63,
            27,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            120,
            92,
            352,
            2977,
            336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaylen consumes 743 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Billy is 24 years old. How much calories should Billy consume?",
        "answer": 1486,
        "options": [
            169,
            1486,
            275,
            228,
            392
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Prince and Kenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Prince consumes 2141 calories per day whereas Kenzo consumes 2963 calories per day. Prince is bulkier than Kenzo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            14,
            98,
            14,
            21,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cole and Junior are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cole consumes 2910 calories per day whereas Junior consumes 2910 calories per day. Cole is stronger than Junior.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": "Can't say"
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 40 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "36*35",
        "options": [
            "65*85",
            "43*63",
            "36*35",
            "79*89",
            "61*67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in molybdenum ?",
        "answer": "6250",
        "options": [
            "136",
            "336",
            "314",
            "125",
            "6250"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            70,
            26,
            42,
            36,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Francis and Elisha are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Francis consumes 2591 calories per day whereas Elisha consumes 2993 calories per day. Francis is lighter than Elisha.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexis sold a book to Ernest at a price of 133 after giving 5 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "140.00",
        "options": [
            "127.88",
            "129.76",
            "140.00",
            "128.19",
            "126.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            20,
            "Not possible",
            78,
            48,
            "19",
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Phillip and Casey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Phillip consumes 1862 calories per day whereas Casey consumes 1796 calories per day. Phillip is stronger than Casey.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than James by 2 years. 11 years ago James was 31 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "60",
            "58",
            "44",
            "60",
            "58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            104,
            63,
            93,
            89,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 236 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            20,
            68,
            "Not possible",
            75,
            93,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given dogs ? 38 50 21 47 36 18 11 37 11 35 8 11 9 20 11 43 34 21 21 14 47 44 32 33 ",
        "answer": "26.50",
        "options": [
            "26.50",
            "44.00",
            "32.00",
            "38.00",
            "47.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            610,
            631,
            670,
            142,
            378
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            "7",
            92,
            41,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adrian is younger than Koa by 5 years. 10 years ago Koa was 29 years old. What is Adrian 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "64",
            "34",
            "74",
            "74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 102 . We turned on the cooler for 70 minutes. What is the temperature after 70 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            135,
            105,
            112,
            135,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 354 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "705",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            27,
            22,
            82,
            8,
            "705"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            108,
            116,
            102,
            114,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "929",
            "5260",
            "343",
            "1869",
            "355"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 14 45 50 23 6 1 16 1 19 47 23 1 2 29 32 49 34 34 31 32 6 38 30 38 32 40 50 3 44 43 2 12 38 3 5 17 24 20 5 46 4 25 12 9 ",
        "answer": "23.50",
        "options": [
            "47.00",
            "23.50",
            "49.00",
            "19.00",
            "31.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 3 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Traingle",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 129 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 119,
        "options": [
            119,
            127,
            134,
            10,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kendrick consumes 554 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Wilder is 26 years old. How much calories should Wilder consume?",
        "answer": 1108,
        "options": [
            157,
            197,
            306,
            130,
            1108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Uriel runs at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Joe 's place which is 163 km away?",
        "answer": "13.58",
        "options": [
            "54.33",
            "40.75",
            "67.92",
            "13.58",
            "27.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            82,
            62,
            93,
            78,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyle consumes 946 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Ramon is 40 years old. How much calories should Ramon consume?",
        "answer": 1892,
        "options": [
            489,
            349,
            1892,
            266,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given human ? 26 29 40 39 27 8 24 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "27.00",
            "27.00",
            "26.00",
            "8.00",
            "27.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 98 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            95,
            129,
            101,
            109,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 7 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Heptagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 421 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "381",
        "options": [
            83,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            29,
            "381",
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 233 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 227,
        "options": [
            143,
            184,
            157,
            240,
            227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given tigers ? 28 25 15 33 8 14 26 6 31 48 33 49 27 41 ",
        "answer": "27.50",
        "options": [
            "27.00",
            "25.00",
            "33.00",
            "27.50",
            "48.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malcolm drives at a speed of 9 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Gordon 's place which is 194 km away?",
        "answer": "21.56",
        "options": [
            "64.67",
            "107.78",
            "86.22",
            "21.56",
            "64.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Francisco sold a book to Lucca at a price of 671 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1048.44",
        "options": [
            "568.64",
            "528.35",
            "493.38",
            "1048.44",
            "520.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            94,
            97,
            86,
            72,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in mercury is 1540. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "6257",
            "2613",
            "7391",
            "9852"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            2,
            -8,
            7,
            0,
            -6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cadmium is 2780. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "389",
            "9061",
            "4137",
            "2322",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hudson and Eugene are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hudson consumes 1664 calories per day whereas Eugene consumes 2710 calories per day. Hudson is less weight than Eugene.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Evan and Adrien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Evan consumes 2810 calories per day whereas Adrien consumes 2836 calories per day. Evan is weaker than Adrien.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 44 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "42*22",
        "options": [
            "52*77",
            "61*73",
            "42*22",
            "81*62",
            "78*63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 101 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            74,
            44,
            62,
            61,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 430 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            20,
            31,
            53,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 344 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "23",
            88,
            62,
            35,
            7,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beau consumes 687 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Arian is 31 years old. How much calories should Arian consume?",
        "answer": 1374,
        "options": [
            1374,
            269,
            209,
            392,
            186
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 5 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Pentagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            17,
            39,
            -5,
            21,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            85,
            70,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given dogs ? 36 48 17 46 3 37 3 29 20 31 24 10 25 16 28 2 41 28 20 8 29 39 23 37 19 39 19 49 41 47 44 11 10 20 46 ",
        "answer": "28.00",
        "options": [
            "10.00",
            "47.00",
            "48.00",
            "28.00",
            "28.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Major consumes 931 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Ridge is 35 years old. How much calories should Ridge consume?",
        "answer": 1862,
        "options": [
            218,
            325,
            243,
            1862,
            477
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            73,
            101,
            86,
            111,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luca and Rayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luca consumes 1599 calories per day whereas Rayan consumes 1832 calories per day. Luca is less weight than Rayan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given dogs ? 35 50 14 41 45 30 6 34 23 9 23 13 50 11 12 3 21 39 27 26 2 1 23 35 8 22 48 34 9 26 36 18 25 41 6 9 47 46 15 25 47 17 5 14 ",
        "answer": "24.34",
        "options": [
            "24.34",
            "121.70",
            "97.36",
            "73.02",
            "121.70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polyethylene ?",
        "answer": "1250",
        "options": [
            "244",
            "251",
            "1250",
            "154",
            "154"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            -9,
            0,
            -3,
            1,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 333 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            53,
            65,
            75,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clayton and Ralph are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clayton consumes 2252 calories per day whereas Ralph consumes 2975 calories per day. Clayton is weaker than Ralph.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Warren and Mohammad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Warren consumes 2378 calories per day whereas Mohammad consumes 1723 calories per day. Warren is weaker than Mohammad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 117 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            36,
            "7",
            "Not possible",
            29,
            62,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 136 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 133,
        "options": [
            133,
            103,
            243,
            211,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 369 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            86,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            90,
            75,
            "17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emerson sold a book to Louie at a price of 692 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1412.24",
        "options": [
            "500.54",
            "1412.24",
            "551.39",
            "458.28",
            "491.48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            89,
            70,
            104,
            67,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 147 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            65,
            60,
            84,
            23,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 136 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 126,
        "options": [
            79,
            234,
            236,
            36,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 56, 44, 80. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in constantan ?",
        "answer": "5177",
        "options": [
            "330",
            "105",
            "277",
            "5177",
            "158"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston consumes 776 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Jad is 29 years old. How much calories should Jad consume?",
        "answer": 1552,
        "options": [
            405,
            1552,
            213,
            166,
            300
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 351 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            62,
            "27",
            1,
            81,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaylen and Saint are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaylen consumes 2190 calories per day whereas Saint consumes 2854 calories per day. Jaylen is more weight than Saint.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Landon and Elon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Landon consumes 2493 calories per day whereas Elon consumes 1625 calories per day. Landon is heavier than Elon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper annealed ?",
        "answer": "4760",
        "options": [
            "229",
            "250",
            "4760",
            "291",
            "123"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 447 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            35,
            57,
            74,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 290 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "263",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "263",
            99,
            6,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1289,
            1730,
            1979,
            1064,
            348
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 52 * 31. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "36*15",
        "options": [
            "95*64",
            "36*15",
            "81*62",
            "93*62",
            "79*53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 341 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            80,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both George and Harold are of same age. Both do same physical activity. George consumes 2611 calories per day whereas Harold consumes 2289 calories per day. George is more weight than Harold.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eduardo and Layne are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eduardo consumes 1659 calories per day whereas Layne consumes 1737 calories per day. Eduardo is lighter than Layne.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 265 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "53",
        "options": [
            "53",
            42,
            4,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in steel ?",
        "answer": "5940",
        "options": [
            "5940",
            "254",
            "224",
            "169",
            "258"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            32,
            43,
            24,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Legend and Achilles are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Legend consumes 2912 calories per day whereas Achilles consumes 2111 calories per day. Legend is lighter than Achilles.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            62,
            78,
            65,
            57,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Armani consumes 706 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Canaan is 33 years old. How much calories should Canaan consume?",
        "answer": 1412,
        "options": [
            157,
            1412,
            203,
            399,
            281
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 500 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "331",
        "options": [
            10,
            "331",
            "Not possible",
            69,
            53,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gabriel consumes 778 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Issac is 27 years old. How much calories should Issac consume?",
        "answer": 1556,
        "options": [
            301,
            413,
            218,
            1556,
            196
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            -5,
            1,
            -18,
            14,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 244 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 235,
        "options": [
            7,
            383,
            315,
            176,
            235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 43 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            16,
            33,
            49,
            1,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cyrus and Tripp are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cyrus consumes 1791 calories per day whereas Tripp consumes 2522 calories per day. Cyrus is more weight than Tripp.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            17,
            19,
            19,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maddox sold a book to Jad at a price of 697 after giving 34 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1056.06",
        "options": [
            "595.73",
            "555.38",
            "1056.06",
            "520.15",
            "547.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            25,
            25,
            69,
            "7",
            "Not possible",
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin consumes 966 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Kannon is 28 years old. How much calories should Kannon consume?",
        "answer": 1932,
        "options": [
            256,
            509,
            341,
            1932,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 237 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            42,
            34,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            61,
            65,
            65,
            71,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tantalium is 3350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1416",
            "7351",
            "10440",
            "14911",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 269 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            74,
            70,
            "Not possible",
            40,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            "31",
            84,
            "Not possible",
            71,
            28,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 218 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            36,
            70,
            45,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jacob and Lyric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jacob consumes 1996 calories per day whereas Lyric consumes 2050 calories per day. Jacob is weaker than Lyric.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kai and Jeremias are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kai consumes 2077 calories per day whereas Jeremias consumes 2971 calories per day. Kai is heavier than Jeremias.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a airpods in 59 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            100,
            84,
            23,
            87,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            63,
            71,
            45,
            50,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 243 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            12,
            30,
            "35",
            93,
            30,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 310 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            79,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jude sold a book to Skylar at a price of 123 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "150.00",
        "options": [
            "150.00",
            "104.24",
            "108.37",
            "112.84",
            "107.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hayes and Ray are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hayes consumes 2411 calories per day whereas Ray consumes 1880 calories per day. Hayes is stronger than Ray.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a airpods in 27 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            40,
            41,
            97,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 272 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 261,
        "options": [
            269,
            375,
            261,
            115,
            476
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 306 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "61",
        "options": [
            74,
            25,
            "61",
            36,
            "Not possible",
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 404 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "759",
        "options": [
            1,
            "759",
            87,
            2,
            49,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Oliver by 5 years. 9 years ago Oliver was 30 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "44",
            "47",
            "42",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "3810",
            "183",
            "338",
            "121",
            "315"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 113 minutes. What is the temperature after 113 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            29,
            30,
            49,
            32,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 2 18 24 24 23 43 17 20 35 7 47 28 12 40 20 5 16 10 27 43 21 9 31 11 18 25 44 8 34 41 27 3 29 38 37 44 11 23 2 35 ",
        "answer": "23.80",
        "options": [
            "71.40",
            "119.00",
            "23.80",
            "71.40",
            "95.20"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Atlas runs at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Finnley 's place which is 127 km away?",
        "answer": "9.07",
        "options": [
            "45.36",
            "27.21",
            "27.21",
            "9.07",
            "45.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brass is 4700. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4377",
            "7492",
            "7566",
            "5972",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tristan consumes 737 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Keith is 33 years old. How much calories should Keith consume?",
        "answer": 1474,
        "options": [
            1474,
            288,
            396,
            234,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            1,
            -8,
            2,
            29,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 375 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            3,
            47,
            "Not possible",
            "35",
            78,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joshua and Jaxtyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joshua consumes 2863 calories per day whereas Jaxtyn consumes 2248 calories per day. Joshua is bulkier than Jaxtyn.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 108 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            172,
            99,
            198,
            35,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Archer and Mack are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Archer consumes 1934 calories per day whereas Mack consumes 2931 calories per day. Archer is heavier than Mack.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Fernando and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Fernando consumes 2460 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 2665 calories per day. Fernando is stronger than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 226 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 220,
        "options": [
            220,
            271,
            27,
            86,
            239
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 380 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            25,
            31,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            88,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamison drives at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Benicio 's place which is 173 km away?",
        "answer": "21.62",
        "options": [
            "64.88",
            "21.62",
            "43.25",
            "86.50",
            "64.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in silica fused is 5968. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7121",
            "3130",
            "14476",
            "343",
            "1687"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            18,
            18,
            18,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than James by 5 years. 11 years ago James was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "41",
            "48",
            "42",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 287 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "141",
        "options": [
            77,
            "141",
            17,
            56,
            "Not possible",
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nathan and Anders are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nathan consumes 1702 calories per day whereas Anders consumes 2266 calories per day. Nathan is heavier than Anders.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            -6,
            1,
            4,
            -8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            126,
            134,
            131,
            102,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 88, 53, 39. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 322 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 319,
        "options": [
            319,
            547,
            244,
            599,
            609
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in concrete is 3700. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8435",
            "12835",
            "10298",
            "343",
            "8943"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 465 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            "Not possible",
            91,
            60,
            "Not possible",
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eduardo is younger than Reuben by 4 years. 6 years ago Reuben was 32 years old. What is Eduardo 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "58",
            "34",
            "58",
            "62",
            "56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            68,
            49,
            50,
            65,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            2432,
            12,
            2624,
            2643,
            3785
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruben consumes 852 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Reese is 23 years old. How much calories should Reese consume?",
        "answer": 1704,
        "options": [
            324,
            185,
            1704,
            443,
            259
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tantalium is 3350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5779",
            "10603",
            "13489",
            "343",
            "450"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            93,
            57,
            76,
            73,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Holden and Gerardo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Holden consumes 1674 calories per day whereas Gerardo consumes 1672 calories per day. Holden is heavier than Gerardo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            50,
            55,
            47,
            48,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            22,
            25,
            26,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Josue and Brennan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Josue consumes 1925 calories per day whereas Brennan consumes 1501 calories per day. Josue is bulkier than Brennan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Rhett consumes 558 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Brodie is 25 years old. How much calories should Brodie consume?",
        "answer": 1116,
        "options": [
            174,
            1116,
            201,
            307,
            152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harvey and Alvaro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harvey consumes 1587 calories per day whereas Alvaro consumes 2708 calories per day. Harvey is heavier than Alvaro.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 211 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 200,
        "options": [
            316,
            256,
            200,
            304,
            246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 282 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 280,
        "options": [
            280,
            233,
            304,
            36,
            336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            66,
            46,
            65,
            66,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 51 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "50*25",
        "options": [
            "50*25",
            "54*36",
            "69*45",
            "100*40",
            "61*64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ismael consumes 911 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Cannon is 25 years old. How much calories should Cannon consume?",
        "answer": 1822,
        "options": [
            473,
            322,
            243,
            211,
            1822
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 111 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "13",
            53,
            73,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given cats ? 12 35 50 35 46 35 27 44 46 23 32 ",
        "answer": "35.00",
        "options": [
            "35.00",
            "140.00",
            "105.00",
            "105.00",
            "105.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 333 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            51,
            81,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            "25",
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Atticus and Roland are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Atticus consumes 2794 calories per day whereas Roland consumes 2181 calories per day. Atticus is weaker than Roland.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            24,
            38,
            19,
            24,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Frank and Quentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Frank consumes 1688 calories per day whereas Quentin consumes 1700 calories per day. Frank is less weight than Quentin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            79,
            86,
            81,
            84,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eduardo and Brett are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eduardo consumes 2394 calories per day whereas Brett consumes 2559 calories per day. Eduardo is lighter than Brett.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 269 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            13,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            95,
            "Not possible",
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            78,
            8,
            89,
            64,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark walks at a speed of 16 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Niko 's place which is 192 km away?",
        "answer": "12.00",
        "options": [
            "12.00",
            "48.00",
            "60.00",
            "36.00",
            "60.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rafael consumes 551 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Gerald is 27 years old. How much calories should Gerald consume?",
        "answer": 1102,
        "options": [
            158,
            1102,
            219,
            181,
            322
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Liam by 2 years. 5 years ago Liam was 33 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "34",
            "44",
            "41",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            99,
            84,
            70,
            104,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 64, 46, 70. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 264 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            81,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adriel sold a book to Zakai at a price of 359 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "454.43",
        "options": [
            "307.36",
            "454.43",
            "296.69",
            "324.89",
            "310.15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 18 watt charger charges a tablet in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            60,
            9,
            45,
            80,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9063",
            "11648",
            "3836",
            "10381",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 109 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            31,
            54,
            "35",
            50,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 75 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            100,
            113,
            71,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both William and Anders are of same age. Both do same physical activity. William consumes 1677 calories per day whereas Anders consumes 2037 calories per day. William is heavier than Anders.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 132 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            56,
            130,
            256,
            185,
            236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            54,
            58,
            99,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            105,
            106,
            107,
            136,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 248 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            39,
            98,
            85,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 116 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            158,
            193,
            158,
            110,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Iker and Kylen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Iker consumes 2223 calories per day whereas Kylen consumes 2991 calories per day. Iker is stronger than Kylen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 15 years ago Benjamin was 25 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "61",
            "37",
            "52",
            "43",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "5950",
            "339",
            "214",
            "261",
            "141"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 2 watt charger charges a powerbank in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 2 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            54,
            42,
            60,
            50,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            62,
            36,
            63,
            76,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 145 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 143,
        "options": [
            64,
            187,
            202,
            143,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lorenzo and Idris are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lorenzo consumes 2090 calories per day whereas Idris consumes 1920 calories per day. Lorenzo is weaker than Idris.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 248 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "159",
        "options": [
            43,
            "Not possible",
            "159",
            34,
            33,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eden drives at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Colby 's place which is 137 km away?",
        "answer": "8.06",
        "options": [
            "40.29",
            "8.06",
            "40.29",
            "40.29",
            "32.24"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tin rolled ?",
        "answer": "3320",
        "options": [
            "122",
            "102",
            "314",
            "158",
            "3320"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Judah and Roland are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Judah consumes 1727 calories per day whereas Roland consumes 2023 calories per day. Judah is lighter than Roland.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Omar is younger than Kannon by 2 years. 9 years ago Kannon was 26 years old. What is Omar 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "55",
            "39",
            "33",
            "55",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 43 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "35*41",
        "options": [
            "53*96",
            "75*90",
            "71*61",
            "69*85",
            "35*41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lukas sold a book to Apollo at a price of 486 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "747.69",
        "options": [
            "360.00",
            "413.62",
            "747.69",
            "384.95",
            "379.69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyler consumes 890 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Aarav is 37 years old. How much calories should Aarav consume?",
        "answer": 1780,
        "options": [
            193,
            234,
            1780,
            312,
            495
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beckett consumes 867 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Baker is 40 years old. How much calories should Baker consume?",
        "answer": 1734,
        "options": [
            449,
            216,
            323,
            1734,
            244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in antimony ?",
        "answer": "3400",
        "options": [
            "3400",
            "249",
            "232",
            "158",
            "250"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            398,
            359,
            3,
            380,
            675
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 322 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            65,
            16,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 104 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 416,
        "options": [
            624,
            520,
            "416",
            832,
            520
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1060,
            1079,
            1979,
            1763,
            1463
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 311 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            10,
            33,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 218 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "121",
        "options": [
            49,
            47,
            39,
            92,
            "Not possible",
            "121"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 56 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "30*31",
        "options": [
            "99*45",
            "61*46",
            "79*51",
            "105*52",
            "30*31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "55",
        "options": [
            34,
            39,
            "Not possible",
            6,
            "55",
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Manuel and Willie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Manuel consumes 2855 calories per day whereas Willie consumes 1967 calories per day. Manuel is weaker than Willie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul consumes 658 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Vihaan is 22 years old. How much calories should Vihaan consume?",
        "answer": 1316,
        "options": [
            339,
            250,
            177,
            168,
            1316
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 291 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            39,
            61,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            83,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brayden and Khari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brayden consumes 2874 calories per day whereas Khari consumes 2498 calories per day. Brayden is less weight than Khari.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14114",
            "356",
            "4809",
            "343",
            "9510"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 180 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 173,
        "options": [
            89,
            46,
            53,
            344,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 22 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            21,
            16,
            23,
            6,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "77",
        "options": [
            11,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            "77",
            79,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Theo and Onyx are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Theo consumes 2714 calories per day whereas Onyx consumes 1688 calories per day. Theo is lighter than Onyx.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            6,
            2,
            -8,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lincoln consumes 934 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Marcelo is 32 years old. How much calories should Marcelo consume?",
        "answer": 1868,
        "options": [
            1868,
            359,
            498,
            204,
            278
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 41 * 39. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "32*30",
        "options": [
            "32*30",
            "45*78",
            "42*47",
            "56*64",
            "53*56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jamison and Roy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jamison consumes 2583 calories per day whereas Roy consumes 2448 calories per day. Jamison is lighter than Roy.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maverick and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maverick consumes 2009 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 1725 calories per day. Maverick is heavier than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 25 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            23,
            22,
            36,
            7,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 30. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "30*26",
        "options": [
            "48*38",
            "51*51",
            "30*26",
            "42*39",
            "42*42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kason and Kelvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kason consumes 2760 calories per day whereas Kelvin consumes 1709 calories per day. Kason is lighter than Kelvin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            73,
            66,
            85,
            70,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 303 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 295,
        "options": [
            46,
            446,
            291,
            295,
            525
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bennett and Rayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bennett consumes 2487 calories per day whereas Rayan consumes 1632 calories per day. Bennett is heavier than Rayan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a powerbank in 36 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            60,
            43,
            67,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            304,
            349,
            896,
            1979,
            425
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeremy drives at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Cullen 's place which is 108 km away?",
        "answer": "7.71",
        "options": [
            "38.57",
            "23.14",
            "7.71",
            "38.57",
            "30.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryce sold a book to Braylon at a price of 795 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3312.50",
        "options": [
            "506.37",
            "451.70",
            "494.40",
            "3312.50",
            "576.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            27,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            89,
            33,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo sold a book to Tripp at a price of 417 after giving 69 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1345.16",
        "options": [
            "1345.16",
            "274.79",
            "246.75",
            "310.04",
            "268.69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 5 watt charger charges a phone in 16 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            57,
            58,
            33,
            80,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            57,
            64,
            57,
            49,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 468 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            30,
            90,
            2,
            "Not possible",
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 102 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            168,
            101,
            198,
            162,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12729",
            "7761",
            "9598",
            "4380"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            39,
            28,
            46,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            138,
            109,
            107,
            108,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 56 * 48. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "54*32",
        "options": [
            "107*49",
            "113*56",
            "54*32",
            "109*59",
            "114*95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lennox and Augustine are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lennox consumes 2971 calories per day whereas Augustine consumes 2084 calories per day. Lennox is weaker than Augustine.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaxton and Eliseo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaxton consumes 2134 calories per day whereas Eliseo consumes 2314 calories per day. Jaxton is stronger than Eliseo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 317 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            72,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            "43",
            14,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 11 minutes. What is the temperature after 11 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            16,
            19,
            15,
            27,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 251 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            12,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            "69",
            42,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brandon consumes 940 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Yael is 36 years old. How much calories should Yael consume?",
        "answer": 1880,
        "options": [
            334,
            496,
            1880,
            211,
            268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 87 minutes. What is the temperature after 87 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            41,
            40,
            46,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sullivan and Koa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sullivan consumes 2194 calories per day whereas Koa consumes 2403 calories per day. Sullivan is weaker than Koa.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dominick and Eddie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dominick consumes 2049 calories per day whereas Eddie consumes 2111 calories per day. Dominick is bulkier than Eddie.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            65,
            68,
            80,
            62,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given elephants ? 42 18 28 35 50 32 10 46 6 34 5 40 42 32 25 30 46 22 17 16 20 38 11 20 6 22 39 7 42 32 40 14 29 21 32 8 40 16 8 36 42 26 39 20 21 22 34 28 ",
        "answer": "26.85",
        "options": [
            "80.55",
            "107.40",
            "134.25",
            "26.85",
            "53.70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            0,
            -5,
            2,
            -10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Travis and Mohammad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Travis consumes 2883 calories per day whereas Mohammad consumes 2001 calories per day. Travis is bulkier than Mohammad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Jose consumes 910 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Korbyn is 26 years old. How much calories should Korbyn consume?",
        "answer": 1820,
        "options": [
            226,
            274,
            335,
            1820,
            497
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Otto is younger than Casen by 3 years. 11 years ago Casen was 31 years old. What is Otto 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "70",
            "39",
            "70",
            "45",
            "59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean consumes 518 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Roger is 31 years old. How much calories should Roger consume?",
        "answer": 1036,
        "options": [
            202,
            1036,
            122,
            287,
            179
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesse consumes 692 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Mekhi is 40 years old. How much calories should Mekhi consume?",
        "answer": 1384,
        "options": [
            374,
            172,
            240,
            206,
            1384
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angelo sold a book to Mordechai at a price of 790 after giving 19 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "975.31",
        "options": [
            "685.76",
            "663.87",
            "691.47",
            "975.31",
            "721.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            104,
            107,
            113,
            116,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jorge and Leighton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jorge consumes 2325 calories per day whereas Leighton consumes 1673 calories per day. Jorge is lighter than Leighton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Victor and Harlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Victor consumes 2557 calories per day whereas Harlan consumes 2081 calories per day. Victor is weaker than Harlan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jasper and Avi are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jasper consumes 2691 calories per day whereas Avi consumes 1990 calories per day. Jasper is less weight than Avi.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in titanium ?",
        "answer": "6070",
        "options": [
            "310",
            "189",
            "6070",
            "138",
            "284"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 222 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            66,
            91,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 297 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 294,
        "options": [
            294,
            516,
            530,
            282,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a phone in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            5,
            7,
            63,
            3,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 212 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "139",
        "options": [
            50,
            12,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            "139",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo consumes 863 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Douglas is 28 years old. How much calories should Douglas consume?",
        "answer": 1726,
        "options": [
            182,
            448,
            323,
            252,
            1726
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given human ? 36 18 19 1 38 5 3 34 34 32 10 5 37 42 28 33 19 41 7 22 7 12 21 17 37 45 18 10 9 28 23 42 8 31 ",
        "answer": "22.71",
        "options": [
            "68.13",
            "68.13",
            "45.42",
            "22.71",
            "90.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malik is younger than Jaxen by 2 years. 15 years ago Jaxen was 25 years old. What is Malik 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "74",
            "38",
            "74",
            "72",
            "76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Odin consumes 937 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Zaid is 32 years old. How much calories should Zaid consume?",
        "answer": 1874,
        "options": [
            266,
            490,
            201,
            1874,
            326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cooper and Aydin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cooper consumes 2842 calories per day whereas Aydin consumes 1970 calories per day. Cooper is heavier than Aydin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax runs at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Stefan 's place which is 142 km away?",
        "answer": "7.47",
        "options": [
            "29.89",
            "7.47",
            "37.37",
            "22.42",
            "37.37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hank and Lachlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hank consumes 1944 calories per day whereas Lachlan consumes 2624 calories per day. Hank is weaker than Lachlan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Derrick and Cayson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Derrick consumes 1607 calories per day whereas Cayson consumes 2828 calories per day. Derrick is bulkier than Cayson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 50 34 11 42 4 42 34 ",
        "answer": "31.00",
        "options": [
            "93.00",
            "62.00",
            "62.00",
            "155.00",
            "31.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            101,
            96,
            101,
            106,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 50, 45, 85. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ian and Landry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ian consumes 1838 calories per day whereas Landry consumes 2188 calories per day. Ian is stronger than Landry.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 224 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 219,
        "options": [
            41,
            219,
            333,
            246,
            438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant consumes 863 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Bridger is 33 years old. How much calories should Bridger consume?",
        "answer": 1726,
        "options": [
            233,
            301,
            1726,
            452,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "2180",
            "312",
            "122",
            "303",
            "221"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 18 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            1,
            8,
            12,
            12,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Javier sold a book to Case at a price of 292 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "973.33",
        "options": [
            "171.76",
            "973.33",
            "187.18",
            "191.48",
            "216.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            81,
            82,
            72,
            92,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 269 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            9,
            11,
            51,
            "Not possible",
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oakley and Kylo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oakley consumes 2274 calories per day whereas Kylo consumes 1857 calories per day. Oakley is stronger than Kylo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "46*30",
        "options": [
            "78*85",
            "67*88",
            "46*30",
            "60*90",
            "85*59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a phone in 14 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            4,
            54,
            13,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronan is younger than Nelson by 1 years. 9 years ago Nelson was 33 years old. What is Ronan 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "62",
            "41",
            "61",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 93, 44, 43. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 494 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "99",
        "options": [
            89,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            "99",
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 31, 56, 93. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 318 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            37,
            91,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            16,
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alijah consumes 971 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Moshe is 36 years old. How much calories should Moshe consume?",
        "answer": 1942,
        "options": [
            369,
            228,
            260,
            513,
            1942
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            12,
            3542,
            4474,
            4241,
            4390
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Chase and Alaric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Chase consumes 2320 calories per day whereas Alaric consumes 1817 calories per day. Chase is bulkier than Alaric.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Louis and Tripp are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Louis consumes 2889 calories per day whereas Tripp consumes 1739 calories per day. Louis is heavier than Tripp.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 449 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1796,
        "options": [
            4041,
            3592,
            2245,
            "1796",
            4490
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruben consumes 845 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Darren is 32 years old. How much calories should Darren consume?",
        "answer": 1690,
        "options": [
            445,
            330,
            1690,
            253,
            219
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 33 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            25,
            25,
            25,
            6,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            86,
            93,
            90,
            74,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Antonio and Payton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Antonio consumes 1596 calories per day whereas Payton consumes 2620 calories per day. Antonio is less weight than Payton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Adan cycles at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Darian 's place which is 180 km away?",
        "answer": "16.36",
        "options": [
            "32.73",
            "32.73",
            "16.36",
            "32.73",
            "81.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 82 . We turned on the cooler for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            88,
            83,
            103,
            75,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given elephants ? 25 39 36 3 30 27 43 50 33 8 22 17 27 48 46 20 38 17 38 49 17 5 46 49 42 2 18 21 28 8 24 18 35 34 11 19 41 8 41 37 13 44 24 ",
        "answer": "27.93",
        "options": [
            "55.86",
            "111.72",
            "27.93",
            "83.79",
            "139.65"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            1255,
            1264,
            1812,
            7,
            1013
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 102 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            87,
            49,
            101,
            134,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            64,
            53,
            88,
            51,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 435 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "99",
        "options": [
            36,
            "99",
            27,
            5,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston consumes 780 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Westley is 27 years old. How much calories should Westley consume?",
        "answer": 1560,
        "options": [
            190,
            420,
            1560,
            209,
            305
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling sold a book to Douglas at a price of 164 after giving 42 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "282.76",
        "options": [
            "115.49",
            "124.71",
            "282.76",
            "135.54",
            "122.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Charles and Kyng are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Charles consumes 2648 calories per day whereas Kyng consumes 2093 calories per day. Charles is less weight than Kyng.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 413 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            6,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            64,
            90,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sage cycles at a speed of 13 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Danny 's place which is 143 km away?",
        "answer": "11.00",
        "options": [
            "55.00",
            "11.00",
            "22.00",
            "33.00",
            "55.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luka consumes 641 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Salvador is 22 years old. How much calories should Salvador consume?",
        "answer": 1282,
        "options": [
            253,
            1282,
            161,
            200,
            347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            111,
            121,
            112,
            112,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in copper annealed is 4760. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12580",
            "11423",
            "12282",
            "5566"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 920 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3680,
        "options": [
            4600,
            7360,
            7360,
            "3680",
            4600
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            17,
            13,
            2,
            1979,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 368 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            25,
            "Not possible",
            80,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead rolled ?",
        "answer": "1960",
        "options": [
            "255",
            "1960",
            "106",
            "152",
            "264"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 52 * 36. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "48*31",
        "options": [
            "74*55",
            "94*62",
            "96*39",
            "71*39",
            "48*31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 7 years ago Benjamin was 29 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "47",
            "37",
            "39",
            "27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 218 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            7,
            52,
            92,
            89,
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jasper is younger than Yosef by 3 years. 13 years ago Yosef was 32 years old. What is Jasper 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "64",
            "42",
            "51",
            "64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 120 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            "25",
            85,
            63,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 491 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            96,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            9,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "154",
            "120",
            "160",
            "309",
            "3960"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Oliver by 4 years. 8 years ago Oliver was 30 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "42",
            "46",
            "34",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a laptop in 17 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            89,
            20,
            72,
            10,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 79 . We turned on the cooler for 73 minutes. What is the temperature after 73 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            106,
            83,
            82,
            82,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 264 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            72,
            "Not possible",
            7,
            46,
            "43",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Myles and Karsyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Myles consumes 1928 calories per day whereas Karsyn consumes 2104 calories per day. Myles is heavier than Karsyn.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton consumes 527 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Ernest is 31 years old. How much calories should Ernest consume?",
        "answer": 1054,
        "options": [
            174,
            1054,
            220,
            139,
            280
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            118,
            100,
            134,
            109,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Keegan and Marley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Keegan consumes 2212 calories per day whereas Marley consumes 2606 calories per day. Keegan is bulkier than Marley.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 395 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            40,
            "Not possible",
            6,
            "23",
            79,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            -1,
            19,
            -1,
            10,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Theodore runs at a speed of 6 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Dash 's place which is 160 km away?",
        "answer": "26.67",
        "options": [
            "106.67",
            "133.33",
            "26.67",
            "80.00",
            "53.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper annealed ?",
        "answer": "4760",
        "options": [
            "279",
            "4760",
            "186",
            "337",
            "243"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Connor consumes 678 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Dayton is 38 years old. How much calories should Dayton consume?",
        "answer": 1356,
        "options": [
            160,
            182,
            1356,
            256,
            355
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 422 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            97,
            74,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 187 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            29,
            "9",
            87,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andres is younger than Alberto by 2 years. 11 years ago Alberto was 29 years old. What is Andres 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "42",
            "68",
            "57",
            "68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 25 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            18,
            32,
            -2,
            23,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber neoprene ?",
        "answer": "1600",
        "options": [
            "327",
            "1600",
            "183",
            "301",
            "227"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Muhammad and Terry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Muhammad consumes 1698 calories per day whereas Terry consumes 2186 calories per day. Muhammad is bulkier than Terry.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 414 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "129",
        "options": [
            "129",
            71,
            "Not possible",
            25,
            91,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "329",
            "5010",
            "263",
            "320",
            "240"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conner is younger than Lewis by 4 years. 5 years ago Lewis was 35 years old. What is Conner 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "49",
            "36",
            "53",
            "62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 316 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            29,
            56,
            "23",
            "Not possible",
            98,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 122 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            47,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            15,
            73,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Colin walks at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Lennon 's place which is 122 km away?",
        "answer": "17.43",
        "options": [
            "17.43",
            "87.14",
            "87.14",
            "87.14",
            "52.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            61,
            73,
            46,
            58,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 394 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "375",
        "options": [
            78,
            4,
            4,
            "Not possible",
            "375",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 1000 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 4000,
        "options": [
            5000,
            7000,
            9000,
            "4000",
            5000
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            61,
            66,
            50,
            51,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 145 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            63,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            "Not possible",
            81,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a laptop in 25 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            97,
            98,
            53,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 109 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            52,
            98,
            101,
            136,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            64,
            64,
            84,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 37 19 6 50 15 27 17 50 14 47 23 9 38 29 34 7 8 19 32 42 27 4 18 12 35 18 12 23 29 4 42 25 43 20 47 28 ",
        "answer": "25.28",
        "options": [
            "25.28",
            "101.12",
            "101.12",
            "50.56",
            "101.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 607 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2428,
        "options": [
            "2428",
            3035,
            4856,
            6070,
            5463
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 269 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            68,
            "Not possible",
            "31",
            15,
            84,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Julian sold a book to Mohammad at a price of 445 after giving 75 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1780.00",
        "options": [
            "278.12",
            "254.29",
            "323.64",
            "1780.00",
            "284.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 308 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 300,
        "options": [
            410,
            300,
            153,
            454,
            232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 105 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            102,
            39,
            108,
            160,
            178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Liam and Alaric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Liam consumes 2310 calories per day whereas Alaric consumes 1688 calories per day. Liam is less weight than Alaric.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 40 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            31,
            30,
            23,
            55,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 460 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "33",
            26,
            100,
            53,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephen consumes 772 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Xzavier is 22 years old. How much calories should Xzavier consume?",
        "answer": 1544,
        "options": [
            168,
            1544,
            279,
            412,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kairo walks at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Harry 's place which is 168 km away?",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "96.00",
            "24.00",
            "96.00",
            "72.00",
            "96.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            21,
            31,
            21,
            15,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            46,
            5,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 30, 30, 120. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            17,
            25,
            -1,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryson consumes 940 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Willie is 39 years old. How much calories should Willie consume?",
        "answer": 1880,
        "options": [
            247,
            230,
            505,
            349,
            1880
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rafael consumes 974 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Guillermo is 31 years old. How much calories should Guillermo consume?",
        "answer": 1948,
        "options": [
            335,
            511,
            229,
            287,
            1948
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lennox and Watson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lennox consumes 1842 calories per day whereas Watson consumes 2666 calories per day. Lennox is more weight than Watson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 220 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 212,
        "options": [
            91,
            212,
            126,
            316,
            306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            44,
            60,
            43,
            53,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            87,
            102,
            110,
            102,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 48 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            70,
            38,
            41,
            45,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kane and Huxley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kane consumes 2542 calories per day whereas Huxley consumes 2313 calories per day. Kane is weaker than Huxley.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 328 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            37,
            "Not possible",
            80,
            "Not possible",
            73,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alan consumes 702 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Arturo is 28 years old. How much calories should Arturo consume?",
        "answer": 1404,
        "options": [
            154,
            1404,
            279,
            368,
            215
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 94 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            49,
            86,
            61,
            19,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 77 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            33,
            87,
            68,
            84,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enzo and Nixon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enzo consumes 1679 calories per day whereas Nixon consumes 2406 calories per day. Enzo is less weight than Nixon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the cooler for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            55,
            65,
            59,
            65,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathaniel consumes 815 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Jad is 32 years old. How much calories should Jad consume?",
        "answer": 1630,
        "options": [
            438,
            193,
            231,
            1630,
            300
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given martians ? 30 44 47 16 6 30 6 ",
        "answer": "25.57",
        "options": [
            "102.28",
            "102.28",
            "25.57",
            "102.28",
            "127.85"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a powerbank in 47 minutes. How much time will it take for a 29 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            81,
            57,
            71,
            12,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliot and Finnley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliot consumes 1967 calories per day whereas Finnley consumes 2564 calories per day. Elliot is less weight than Finnley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 19 26 31 3 17 44 14 29 1 13 8 6 38 48 1 3 11 25 50 31 6 41 40 39 ",
        "answer": "22.67",
        "options": [
            "45.34",
            "68.01",
            "45.34",
            "113.35",
            "22.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erik and Kenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erik consumes 2784 calories per day whereas Kenzo consumes 1946 calories per day. Erik is weaker than Kenzo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 152 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            13,
            87,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            "13",
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 24 minutes. What is the temperature after 24 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            42,
            30,
            53,
            41,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            41,
            100,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronin consumes 545 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Shepard is 38 years old. How much calories should Shepard consume?",
        "answer": 1090,
        "options": [
            1090,
            144,
            305,
            150,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            5,
            -19,
            6,
            20,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bodhi and Devon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bodhi consumes 2589 calories per day whereas Devon consumes 1720 calories per day. Bodhi is lighter than Devon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 34 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            19,
            35,
            25,
            9,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 15 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            3,
            12,
            12,
            22,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 261 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            21,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            61,
            "17",
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zaiden sold a book to Lachlan at a price of 790 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "887.64",
        "options": [
            "726.10",
            "729.79",
            "748.82",
            "711.71",
            "887.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Titus and Boston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Titus consumes 2037 calories per day whereas Boston consumes 2373 calories per day. Titus is weaker than Boston.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nasir and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nasir consumes 2289 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 2188 calories per day. Nasir is more weight than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayne and Blaze are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayne consumes 2556 calories per day whereas Blaze consumes 1845 calories per day. Zayne is stronger than Blaze.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 442 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "33",
            61,
            81,
            99,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 120 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            120,
            139,
            141,
            132,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Josue is younger than Curtis by 1 years. 15 years ago Curtis was 25 years old. What is Josue 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "42",
            "39",
            "71",
            "56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 93 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            22,
            28,
            91,
            53,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 16 watt charger charges a powerbank in 19 minutes. How much time will it take for a 2 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            18,
            15,
            13,
            15,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            77,
            36,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            73,
            75,
            81,
            66,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 112 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            101,
            57,
            45,
            21,
            162
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beau sold a book to Ulises at a price of 136 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "485.71",
        "options": [
            "100.00",
            "79.07",
            "88.31",
            "485.71",
            "86.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 361 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            43,
            10,
            68,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gabriel cycles at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Case 's place which is 111 km away?",
        "answer": "10.09",
        "options": [
            "30.27",
            "10.09",
            "20.18",
            "30.27",
            "40.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 223 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            72,
            63,
            17,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 164 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 163,
        "options": [
            321,
            299,
            261,
            37,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matthias and Alexzander are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matthias consumes 2693 calories per day whereas Alexzander consumes 2180 calories per day. Matthias is more weight than Alexzander.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Pedro sold a book to Bjorn at a price of 846 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "950.56",
        "options": [
            "950.56",
            "781.52",
            "801.90",
            "762.16",
            "777.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 244 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 242,
        "options": [
            180,
            242,
            254,
            176,
            318
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            131,
            128,
            134,
            121,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 133 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            92,
            62,
            34,
            "9",
            "Not possible",
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jason and Elisha are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jason consumes 2271 calories per day whereas Elisha consumes 2730 calories per day. Jason is weaker than Elisha.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given elephants ? 2 45 29 28 24 33 44 46 11 8 49 22 8 1 30 4 17 18 34 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "49.00",
            "8.00",
            "30.00",
            "2.00",
            "24.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathan sold a book to Makai at a price of 407 after giving 17 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "490.36",
        "options": [
            "490.36",
            "358.27",
            "360.98",
            "347.86",
            "375.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            -4,
            -18,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Erik sold a book to Hugh at a price of 930 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3321.43",
        "options": [
            "540.70",
            "3321.43",
            "590.10",
            "603.90",
            "683.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leo and Billy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leo consumes 2451 calories per day whereas Billy consumes 1562 calories per day. Leo is more weight than Billy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            566,
            318,
            345,
            2977,
            954
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            354,
            7,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sean and Santana are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sean consumes 2574 calories per day whereas Santana consumes 2181 calories per day. Sean is stronger than Santana.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 174 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            283,
            280,
            23,
            172,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            24,
            26,
            0,
            24,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 42 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            20,
            41,
            41,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both King and Anakin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. King consumes 1548 calories per day whereas Anakin consumes 2840 calories per day. King is lighter than Anakin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 379 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            83,
            98,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            "43",
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jace and Gatlin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jace consumes 2742 calories per day whereas Gatlin consumes 2717 calories per day. Jace is bulkier than Gatlin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mathias and Ignacio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mathias consumes 2167 calories per day whereas Ignacio consumes 1621 calories per day. Mathias is more weight than Ignacio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Ali sold a book to Davion at a price of 942 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1449.23",
        "options": [
            "746.14",
            "697.78",
            "735.94",
            "1449.23",
            "801.70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 407 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            98,
            100,
            75,
            54,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 181 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 170,
        "options": [
            93,
            229,
            287,
            170,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reid consumes 736 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Leandro is 28 years old. How much calories should Leandro consume?",
        "answer": 1472,
        "options": [
            233,
            268,
            194,
            1472,
            381
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 148 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            12,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            "Not possible",
            53,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hendrix and Maxton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hendrix consumes 1804 calories per day whereas Maxton consumes 1966 calories per day. Hendrix is lighter than Maxton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brick is 4200. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3853",
            "5317",
            "4816",
            "343",
            "1682"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 120 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            141,
            123,
            131,
            108,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 150 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            48,
            14,
            169,
            102,
            146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Landon and Layton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Landon consumes 2841 calories per day whereas Layton consumes 1953 calories per day. Landon is bulkier than Layton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 469 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            48,
            82,
            16,
            "43",
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 10 years ago Benjamin was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "34",
            "41",
            "37",
            "51",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 9 44 32 23 25 5 28 31 43 12 45 19 41 25 49 26 41 31 3 33 ",
        "answer": "29.50",
        "options": [
            "45.00",
            "3.00",
            "32.00",
            "3.00",
            "29.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given tigers ? 9 35 48 45 9 13 39 48 44 9 ",
        "answer": "37.00",
        "options": [
            "13.00",
            "45.00",
            "9.00",
            "13.00",
            "37.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 387 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            6,
            5,
            "Not possible",
            80,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 41 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            44,
            59,
            27,
            46,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Archer and Coen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Archer consumes 2742 calories per day whereas Coen consumes 2870 calories per day. Archer is bulkier than Coen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhett and Ford are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhett consumes 2016 calories per day whereas Ford consumes 1546 calories per day. Rhett is lighter than Ford.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the cooler for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            55,
            38,
            73,
            56,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 488 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            83,
            70,
            17,
            11,
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dante consumes 829 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Sonny is 36 years old. How much calories should Sonny consume?",
        "answer": 1658,
        "options": [
            249,
            180,
            459,
            1658,
            322
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 466 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1864,
        "options": [
            3728,
            4194,
            4660,
            "1864",
            2796
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harrison sold a book to Aries at a price of 976 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1284.21",
        "options": [
            "818.79",
            "827.12",
            "1284.21",
            "787.10",
            "871.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks sold a book to Reginald at a price of 220 after giving 71 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "758.62",
        "options": [
            "140.31",
            "128.65",
            "143.56",
            "162.36",
            "758.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 334 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 332,
        "options": [
            341,
            121,
            332,
            391,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 292 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 291,
        "options": [
            54,
            291,
            297,
            288,
            416
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            100,
            102,
            109,
            92,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            35,
            24,
            31,
            24,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            42,
            25,
            40,
            69,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 435 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "163",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            67,
            54,
            "163",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            80,
            99,
            64,
            79,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            -2,
            1,
            0,
            5,
            -11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Keegan is younger than Deangelo by 3 years. 8 years ago Deangelo was 28 years old. What is Keegan 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "33",
            "47",
            "47",
            "42",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clark consumes 664 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Lee is 30 years old. How much calories should Lee consume?",
        "answer": 1328,
        "options": [
            233,
            1328,
            183,
            374,
            170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 229 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            72,
            "Not possible",
            46,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 141 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            37,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            26,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Liam by 1 years. 11 years ago Liam was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "62",
            "61",
            "38",
            "62",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 484 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            9,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            4,
            7,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cody and Bo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cody consumes 2088 calories per day whereas Bo consumes 1860 calories per day. Cody is more weight than Bo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Anderson consumes 788 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Amos is 29 years old. How much calories should Amos consume?",
        "answer": 1576,
        "options": [
            305,
            427,
            242,
            1576,
            191
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 648 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2592,
        "options": [
            5184,
            "2592",
            6480,
            3240,
            4536
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 469 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            50,
            29,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca consumes 620 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Tony is 20 years old. How much calories should Tony consume?",
        "answer": 1240,
        "options": [
            172,
            1240,
            334,
            250,
            156
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 5 years. 8 years ago Liam was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "44",
            "36",
            "39",
            "38",
            "18"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            24,
            38,
            14,
            4,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            105,
            125,
            114,
            134,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given kangaroos ? 6 14 26 34 11 32 28 22 2 15 43 34 43 34 28 20 38 41 13 48 34 5 38 33 46 37 12 43 28 33 18 48 25 30 ",
        "answer": "31.00",
        "options": [
            "31.00",
            "37.00",
            "34.00",
            "34.00",
            "41.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 206 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 198,
        "options": [
            198,
            19,
            136,
            295,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Peter and Dayton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Peter consumes 2064 calories per day whereas Dayton consumes 1729 calories per day. Peter is less weight than Dayton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Travis and Leonidas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Travis consumes 2092 calories per day whereas Leonidas consumes 2478 calories per day. Travis is heavier than Leonidas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jace and Roy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jace consumes 2168 calories per day whereas Roy consumes 2844 calories per day. Jace is weaker than Roy.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Samuel and Keith are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Samuel consumes 2236 calories per day whereas Keith consumes 2955 calories per day. Samuel is heavier than Keith.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            23,
            17,
            13,
            13,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Antonio and Dane are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Antonio consumes 2603 calories per day whereas Dane consumes 2133 calories per day. Antonio is less weight than Dane.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Amir sold a book to Tripp at a price of 763 after giving 69 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2461.29",
        "options": [
            "502.80",
            "451.48",
            "567.29",
            "491.62",
            "2461.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Layne at a price of 214 after giving 23 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "277.92",
        "options": [
            "191.93",
            "182.52",
            "277.92",
            "180.74",
            "173.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given martians ? 41 20 35 16 46 46 21 3 32 12 30 2 21 43 40 47 47 10 26 16 45 47 19 18 42 12 45 31 11 31 25 4 20 47 31 17 28 44 3 24 4 30 19 1 47 31 45 7 27 50 ",
        "answer": "27.50",
        "options": [
            "16.00",
            "26.00",
            "31.00",
            "27.50",
            "12.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 49 41 42 31 27 36 33 37 1 39 7 1 10 24 1 14 35 23 21 2 48 48 26 14 22 ",
        "answer": "25.28",
        "options": [
            "126.40",
            "75.84",
            "126.40",
            "75.84",
            "25.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Raymond consumes 916 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Ameer is 26 years old. How much calories should Ameer consume?",
        "answer": 1832,
        "options": [
            269,
            489,
            202,
            1832,
            320
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            80,
            93,
            89,
            103,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 130 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            42,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            84,
            88,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            59,
            49,
            68,
            73,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in concrete is 3700. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5139",
            "343",
            "13350",
            "1554",
            "6278"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Braylen is younger than Graysen by 5 years. 9 years ago Graysen was 30 years old. What is Braylen 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "34",
            "72",
            "62",
            "72",
            "58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 450 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            23,
            "Not possible",
            28,
            92,
            "Not possible",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            79,
            95,
            86,
            78,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shawn and Cassius are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shawn consumes 2988 calories per day whereas Cassius consumes 2745 calories per day. Shawn is lighter than Cassius.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            57,
            70,
            94,
            77,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 488 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            90,
            79,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 69 minutes. What is the temperature after 69 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            73,
            93,
            87,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass pyrex ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "203",
            "5640",
            "170",
            "234",
            "294"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston consumes 844 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Ares is 23 years old. How much calories should Ares consume?",
        "answer": 1688,
        "options": [
            1688,
            203,
            441,
            255,
            295
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elian consumes 991 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Lian is 33 years old. How much calories should Lian consume?",
        "answer": 1982,
        "options": [
            512,
            355,
            281,
            232,
            1982
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in granite is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1159",
            "343",
            "13024",
            "11622",
            "3147"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a powerbank in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            81,
            86,
            69,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Landon and Franco are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Landon consumes 2050 calories per day whereas Franco consumes 2993 calories per day. Landon is less weight than Franco.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Andy consumes 952 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Kylan is 34 years old. How much calories should Kylan consume?",
        "answer": 1904,
        "options": [
            272,
            1904,
            347,
            524,
            214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            1635,
            12,
            1772,
            1427,
            1692
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finn sold a book to Neil at a price of 488 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1109.09",
        "options": [
            "1109.09",
            "337.02",
            "343.66",
            "312.82",
            "381.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            18,
            24,
            36,
            15,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 89 minutes. What is the temperature after 89 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            27,
            34,
            29,
            45,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin sold a book to Gerald at a price of 162 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "490.91",
        "options": [
            "107.82",
            "105.47",
            "121.35",
            "490.91",
            "97.01"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 487 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "61",
        "options": [
            100,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            "61",
            65,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 492 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            98,
            "33",
            82,
            "Not possible",
            74,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lucas and Noe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lucas consumes 2982 calories per day whereas Noe consumes 1510 calories per day. Lucas is less weight than Noe.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            56,
            52,
            60,
            69,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Calvin and Clay are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Calvin consumes 2106 calories per day whereas Clay consumes 2215 calories per day. Calvin is weaker than Clay.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 114 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            59,
            67,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chase consumes 551 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Dominik is 33 years old. How much calories should Dominik consume?",
        "answer": 1102,
        "options": [
            130,
            1102,
            214,
            299,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Archer and Kase are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Archer consumes 2746 calories per day whereas Kase consumes 1899 calories per day. Archer is more weight than Kase.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 472 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            66,
            46,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 298 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "77",
        "options": [
            34,
            20,
            "77",
            "Not possible",
            28,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than William by 4 years. 14 years ago William was 25 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "43",
            "59",
            "35",
            "27",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 121 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            195,
            74,
            74,
            117,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ricardo and Issac are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ricardo consumes 1700 calories per day whereas Issac consumes 2635 calories per day. Ricardo is stronger than Issac.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamison consumes 605 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Lachlan is 22 years old. How much calories should Lachlan consume?",
        "answer": 1210,
        "options": [
            149,
            215,
            350,
            1210,
            193
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxon sold a book to Dariel at a price of 413 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "878.72",
        "options": [
            "290.03",
            "878.72",
            "269.93",
            "295.53",
            "326.48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 60. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "23*43",
        "options": [
            "42*104",
            "55*106",
            "23*43",
            "48*69",
            "61*99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 191 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "151",
        "options": [
            "151",
            23,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            48,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sergio walks at a speed of 9 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Cason 's place which is 111 km away?",
        "answer": "12.33",
        "options": [
            "37.00",
            "37.00",
            "37.00",
            "12.33",
            "49.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 48 * 30. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "27*23",
        "options": [
            "73*55",
            "88*35",
            "89*33",
            "86*45",
            "27*23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finn drives at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Trace 's place which is 142 km away?",
        "answer": "17.75",
        "options": [
            "53.25",
            "35.50",
            "17.75",
            "53.25",
            "53.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lorenzo drives at a speed of 13 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jamir 's place which is 101 km away?",
        "answer": "7.77",
        "options": [
            "31.08",
            "38.85",
            "38.85",
            "7.77",
            "31.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conner is younger than Mohammad by 4 years. 14 years ago Mohammad was 27 years old. What is Conner 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "63",
            "81",
            "73",
            "67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nathan and Ayaan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nathan consumes 2315 calories per day whereas Ayaan consumes 1509 calories per day. Nathan is weaker than Ayaan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 292 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            77,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            1,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            "Not possible",
            73,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            17,
            15,
            2977,
            17,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            16,
            45,
            19,
            36,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carlos sold a book to Aden at a price of 477 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1014.89",
        "options": [
            "377.08",
            "311.76",
            "334.97",
            "341.32",
            "1014.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 104 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            114,
            102,
            4,
            122,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aidan and Deandre are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aidan consumes 2371 calories per day whereas Deandre consumes 1780 calories per day. Aidan is less weight than Deandre.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            63,
            71,
            64,
            47,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 280 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 269,
        "options": [
            474,
            487,
            233,
            71,
            269
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bruce and Justice are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bruce consumes 2376 calories per day whereas Justice consumes 2950 calories per day. Bruce is less weight than Justice.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaleb and Dillon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaleb consumes 2909 calories per day whereas Dillon consumes 2915 calories per day. Kaleb is heavier than Dillon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Miguel and Randy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Miguel consumes 2684 calories per day whereas Randy consumes 2181 calories per day. Miguel is bulkier than Randy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Zander consumes 515 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Grey is 23 years old. How much calories should Grey consume?",
        "answer": 1030,
        "options": [
            302,
            1030,
            133,
            150,
            206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Seth and Trenton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Seth consumes 2063 calories per day whereas Trenton consumes 1859 calories per day. Seth is bulkier than Trenton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            60,
            75,
            69,
            75,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            129,
            131,
            122,
            137,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 192 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            90,
            33,
            77,
            86,
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clayton and Briggs are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clayton consumes 2917 calories per day whereas Briggs consumes 2889 calories per day. Clayton is more weight than Briggs.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            67,
            96,
            73,
            75,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            2,
            -19,
            -3,
            23,
            -9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayceon and Kristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayceon consumes 2003 calories per day whereas Kristian consumes 1687 calories per day. Jayceon is lighter than Kristian.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            141,
            121,
            117,
            103,
            139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "5362",
            "11772",
            "6885",
            "9054"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            429,
            619,
            548,
            3,
            589
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber gum is 1550. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6195",
            "8035",
            "343",
            "13417",
            "13157"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gianni and Clay are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gianni consumes 1697 calories per day whereas Clay consumes 2084 calories per day. Gianni is weaker than Clay.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            42,
            39,
            33,
            46,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 106 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            23,
            26,
            "31",
            "Not possible",
            21,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 51, 40, 89. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 421 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "19",
            75,
            53,
            65,
            65,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nehemiah and Briar are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nehemiah consumes 1936 calories per day whereas Briar consumes 2581 calories per day. Nehemiah is stronger than Briar.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 290 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 281,
        "options": [
            485,
            375,
            530,
            230,
            281
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dante and Zakai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dante consumes 2687 calories per day whereas Zakai consumes 1574 calories per day. Dante is weaker than Zakai.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 326,
        "options": [
            619,
            465,
            11,
            326,
            600
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 336 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            31,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            "17",
            65,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            56,
            65,
            46,
            62,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            29,
            24,
            41,
            23,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham walks at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Decker 's place which is 172 km away?",
        "answer": "12.29",
        "options": [
            "12.29",
            "24.57",
            "36.86",
            "24.57",
            "49.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            95,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            34,
            84,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            50,
            35,
            52,
            47,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 127 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 123,
        "options": [
            169,
            231,
            87,
            123,
            234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            95,
            92,
            98,
            60,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carter and Augustine are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carter consumes 1518 calories per day whereas Augustine consumes 2345 calories per day. Carter is heavier than Augustine.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 168 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 158,
        "options": [
            45,
            157,
            158,
            14,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Noah by 3 years. 14 years ago Noah was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "33",
            "30",
            "50",
            "30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            101,
            110,
            91,
            98,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 216 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            13,
            "51",
            98,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derrick consumes 956 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Larry is 37 years old. How much calories should Larry consume?",
        "answer": 1912,
        "options": [
            491,
            361,
            1912,
            268,
            201
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 6 watt charger charges a phone in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            72,
            95,
            67,
            98,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Santiago and Reece are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Santiago consumes 1732 calories per day whereas Reece consumes 2019 calories per day. Santiago is bulkier than Reece.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jace and Rudy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jace consumes 2393 calories per day whereas Rudy consumes 2435 calories per day. Jace is more weight than Rudy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 79 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            45,
            78,
            14,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 69, 53, 58. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            279,
            12,
            279,
            152,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Axel and Trace are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Axel consumes 2149 calories per day whereas Trace consumes 2503 calories per day. Axel is lighter than Trace.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Alan sold a book to Vihaan at a price of 667 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "725.00",
        "options": [
            "641.35",
            "629.25",
            "626.88",
            "617.59",
            "725.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 23 50 16 41 30 11 32 25 27 21 16 5 24 48 15 20 39 29 18 24 6 43 27 24 45 29 17 10 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "20.00",
            "24.00",
            "30.00",
            "18.00",
            "24.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Axel and Nickolas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Axel consumes 1710 calories per day whereas Nickolas consumes 2414 calories per day. Axel is stronger than Nickolas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            80,
            69,
            82,
            82,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Liam by 1 years. 6 years ago Liam was 35 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "44",
            "38",
            "46",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paxton sold a book to Byron at a price of 101 after giving 42 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "174.14",
        "options": [
            "75.60",
            "83.47",
            "174.14",
            "76.81",
            "71.13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            12,
            11,
            13,
            1979,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 89 minutes. What is the temperature after 89 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            -2,
            -9,
            11,
            23,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 435 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            21,
            "Not possible",
            47,
            22,
            "27",
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 30 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            24,
            36,
            29,
            21,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jax and Markus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jax consumes 1943 calories per day whereas Markus consumes 1897 calories per day. Jax is less weight than Markus.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            1826,
            1781,
            12,
            1382,
            1734
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ace sold a book to Louie at a price of 667 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "725.00",
        "options": [
            "641.35",
            "725.00",
            "629.25",
            "617.59",
            "626.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 374 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "83",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            52,
            82,
            77,
            50,
            "83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given dogs ? 46 29 48 13 19 20 21 1 21 4 31 4 28 48 2 41 26 49 22 25 39 21 8 44 7 42 16 5 11 25 12 45 43 14 ",
        "answer": "21.50",
        "options": [
            "21.50",
            "4.00",
            "48.00",
            "21.00",
            "11.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen consumes 515 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Shiloh is 21 years old. How much calories should Shiloh consume?",
        "answer": 1030,
        "options": [
            146,
            269,
            1030,
            126,
            188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cyrus and Kylo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cyrus consumes 2944 calories per day whereas Kylo consumes 1738 calories per day. Cyrus is less weight than Kylo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in marbel is 3810. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12226",
            "7888",
            "343",
            "730",
            "4622"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 42 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            51,
            32,
            41,
            9,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            1,
            -8,
            -7,
            1,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            66,
            60,
            77,
            75,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a powerbank in 36 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            64,
            51,
            6,
            77,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ari and Sylas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ari consumes 1704 calories per day whereas Sylas consumes 1825 calories per day. Ari is heavier than Sylas.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in slate is 4510. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8678",
            "8417",
            "343",
            "2024",
            "2890"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "174",
            "2620",
            "173",
            "184",
            "128"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 276 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            33,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            18,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both David and Azariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. David consumes 1988 calories per day whereas Azariah consumes 2784 calories per day. David is stronger than Azariah.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            0,
            29,
            11,
            13,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sebastian sold a book to Harley at a price of 613 after giving 45 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1114.55",
        "options": [
            "1114.55",
            "422.76",
            "500.41",
            "458.32",
            "450.74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 1 . We turned on the heater for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            -3,
            -7,
            -4,
            -27,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 324 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            31,
            19,
            6,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carter and Julio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carter consumes 2911 calories per day whereas Julio consumes 1931 calories per day. Carter is less weight than Julio.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesse sold a book to Benedict at a price of 380 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "760.00",
        "options": [
            "253.33",
            "276.36",
            "304.00",
            "760.00",
            "271.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a powerbank in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 15 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            9,
            28,
            50,
            36,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 229 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            95,
            14,
            "Not possible",
            74,
            "Not possible",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 241 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            61,
            75,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass silicate flint ?",
        "answer": "3980",
        "options": [
            "284",
            "128",
            "160",
            "3980",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adan sold a book to Rey at a price of 235 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "250.00",
        "options": [
            "224.24",
            "228.16",
            "224.88",
            "250.00",
            "221.70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jay consumes 651 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Fox is 37 years old. How much calories should Fox consume?",
        "answer": 1302,
        "options": [
            362,
            195,
            253,
            141,
            1302
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 430 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            30,
            "27",
            66,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 972 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3888,
        "options": [
            7776,
            4860,
            "3888",
            4860,
            5832
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaylen and Benicio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaylen consumes 2741 calories per day whereas Benicio consumes 1514 calories per day. Jaylen is weaker than Benicio.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a laptop in 43 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            85,
            17,
            62,
            87,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            65,
            60,
            61,
            53,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Esteban consumes 688 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Jasiah is 34 years old. How much calories should Jasiah consume?",
        "answer": 1376,
        "options": [
            189,
            166,
            367,
            273,
            1376
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 100 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            78,
            "Not possible",
            5,
            43,
            61,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon consumes 809 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Jasiah is 24 years old. How much calories should Jasiah consume?",
        "answer": 1618,
        "options": [
            244,
            286,
            205,
            422,
            1618
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7104",
            "343",
            "4371",
            "9448",
            "882"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 33 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            31,
            43,
            30,
            13,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Vincent and Zyaire are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Vincent consumes 2367 calories per day whereas Zyaire consumes 2343 calories per day. Vincent is weaker than Zyaire.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 51, 53, 76. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given tigers ? 45 45 32 42 33 45 33 14 21 31 41 30 38 18 11 10 2 30 42 25 ",
        "answer": "29.40",
        "options": [
            "29.40",
            "147.00",
            "58.80",
            "147.00",
            "117.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            110,
            102,
            107,
            126,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            33,
            43,
            31,
            28,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 259 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 250,
        "options": [
            117,
            159,
            54,
            250,
            250
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rodrigo and Fisher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rodrigo consumes 1848 calories per day whereas Fisher consumes 2609 calories per day. Rodrigo is lighter than Fisher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given cats ? 46 10 18 5 33 4 23 32 16 12 47 29 5 31 9 26 24 19 49 17 20 18 5 49 20 7 2 21 16 38 28 12 35 6 38 49 20 19 18 40 24 27 34 41 5 38 46 ",
        "answer": "21.00",
        "options": [
            "10.00",
            "10.00",
            "7.00",
            "7.00",
            "21.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Troy and Davian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Troy consumes 2342 calories per day whereas Davian consumes 1538 calories per day. Troy is heavier than Davian.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 308 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            59,
            18,
            66,
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gregory consumes 554 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Willie is 22 years old. How much calories should Willie consume?",
        "answer": 1108,
        "options": [
            231,
            299,
            177,
            137,
            1108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "David is younger than Jaxxon by 5 years. 7 years ago Jaxxon was 33 years old. What is David 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "52",
            "64",
            "45",
            "64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            60,
            46,
            42,
            79,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dawson and Marley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dawson consumes 1672 calories per day whereas Marley consumes 2268 calories per day. Dawson is bulkier than Marley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            92,
            135,
            106,
            125,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Xander sold a book to Zavier at a price of 573 after giving 52 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1193.75",
        "options": [
            "454.76",
            "1193.75",
            "404.66",
            "412.23",
            "376.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 340 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            26,
            91,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            "19",
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            200,
            250,
            264,
            207,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 261 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1044,
        "options": [
            1827,
            2349,
            2088,
            "1044",
            2610
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cristian consumes 708 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Jaxtyn is 24 years old. How much calories should Jaxtyn consume?",
        "answer": 1416,
        "options": [
            155,
            1416,
            376,
            215,
            264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 97 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            41,
            87,
            117,
            80,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            339,
            2977,
            236,
            467,
            602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in cadmium ?",
        "answer": "2780",
        "options": [
            "273",
            "237",
            "207",
            "2780",
            "100"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Waylon and Alaric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Waylon consumes 1790 calories per day whereas Alaric consumes 2221 calories per day. Waylon is more weight than Alaric.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            137,
            120,
            129,
            117,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            61,
            60,
            72,
            57,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dawson and Kyng are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dawson consumes 1700 calories per day whereas Kyng consumes 1765 calories per day. Dawson is bulkier than Kyng.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry consumes 811 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Baker is 40 years old. How much calories should Baker consume?",
        "answer": 1622,
        "options": [
            205,
            1622,
            450,
            224,
            288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aiden sold a book to Hezekiah at a price of 912 after giving 45 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1658.18",
        "options": [
            "1658.18",
            "744.49",
            "628.97",
            "681.87",
            "670.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erik and Creed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erik consumes 2188 calories per day whereas Creed consumes 2397 calories per day. Erik is less weight than Creed.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 417 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "23",
            "Not possible",
            93,
            79,
            88,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 214 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 211,
        "options": [
            26,
            205,
            337,
            153,
            211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than William by 2 years. 11 years ago William was 27 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "47",
            "32",
            "47",
            "32",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            65,
            67,
            77,
            82,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            76,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            62,
            "Not possible",
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Iker sold a book to Keanu at a price of 130 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "203.12",
        "options": [
            "203.12",
            "95.59",
            "100.93",
            "110.17",
            "102.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14235",
            "1155",
            "1389",
            "343",
            "11029"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Major consumes 954 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Rey is 39 years old. How much calories should Rey consume?",
        "answer": 1908,
        "options": [
            1908,
            240,
            515,
            332,
            249
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both August and Jabari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. August consumes 1546 calories per day whereas Jabari consumes 2591 calories per day. August is less weight than Jabari.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Adan sold a book to Kylo at a price of 235 after giving 9 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "258.24",
        "options": [
            "215.60",
            "219.22",
            "220.14",
            "258.24",
            "224.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            1979,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            24,
            33,
            37,
            51,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 46 * 57. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "28*37",
        "options": [
            "55*90",
            "83*60",
            "28*37",
            "94*110",
            "61*89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakota sold a book to Eddie at a price of 938 after giving 17 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1130.12",
        "options": [
            "864.52",
            "825.70",
            "801.71",
            "831.93",
            "1130.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrew sold a book to Howard at a price of 451 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "530.59",
        "options": [
            "419.53",
            "402.68",
            "530.59",
            "405.39",
            "392.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 272 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 264,
        "options": [
            404,
            264,
            358,
            130,
            426
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ali and Heath are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ali consumes 2946 calories per day whereas Heath consumes 2184 calories per day. Ali is stronger than Heath.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Logan and Vance are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Logan consumes 2193 calories per day whereas Vance consumes 2035 calories per day. Logan is less weight than Vance.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 301 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "33",
            "Not possible",
            62,
            57,
            31,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Conner and Lyric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Conner consumes 2879 calories per day whereas Lyric consumes 2472 calories per day. Conner is less weight than Lyric.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Karson and Abdullah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Karson consumes 1682 calories per day whereas Abdullah consumes 2277 calories per day. Karson is heavier than Abdullah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Samuel and Cristiano are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Samuel consumes 2948 calories per day whereas Cristiano consumes 2460 calories per day. Samuel is more weight than Cristiano.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Austin consumes 735 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Asa is 33 years old. How much calories should Asa consume?",
        "answer": 1470,
        "options": [
            417,
            257,
            1470,
            219,
            196
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Karter sold a book to Tripp at a price of 881 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1797.96",
        "options": [
            "625.71",
            "1797.96",
            "583.44",
            "701.99",
            "637.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aaron and Ernesto are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aaron consumes 2942 calories per day whereas Ernesto consumes 1598 calories per day. Aaron is less weight than Ernesto.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 363 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "161",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            21,
            42,
            87,
            "161",
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            -1,
            -1,
            -14,
            13,
            -13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than James by 1 years. 11 years ago James was 28 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "59",
            "49",
            "37",
            "36",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corbin consumes 970 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Willie is 28 years old. How much calories should Willie consume?",
        "answer": 1940,
        "options": [
            213,
            1940,
            372,
            527,
            292
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Riley and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Riley consumes 2891 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 2534 calories per day. Riley is weaker than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 175 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 170,
        "options": [
            239,
            170,
            205,
            303,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Atticus consumes 883 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Harold is 22 years old. How much calories should Harold consume?",
        "answer": 1766,
        "options": [
            256,
            336,
            221,
            1766,
            463
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gavin sold a book to Sam at a price of 367 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1112.12",
        "options": [
            "238.93",
            "274.91",
            "244.26",
            "219.76",
            "1112.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 92, 37, 51. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            118,
            124,
            94,
            102,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in ivory ?",
        "answer": "3010",
        "options": [
            "3010",
            "274",
            "341",
            "252",
            "227"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 39 45 16 26 21 11 16 36 15 16 3 48 38 45 12 24 47 23 21 40 42 24 28 7 47 11 48 2 4 29 37 18 9 ",
        "answer": "25.70",
        "options": [
            "102.80",
            "77.10",
            "128.50",
            "25.70",
            "102.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Grayson and Kingsley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Grayson consumes 1942 calories per day whereas Kingsley consumes 2264 calories per day. Grayson is less weight than Kingsley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaiden sold a book to Cassius at a price of 839 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2796.67",
        "options": [
            "493.53",
            "621.48",
            "550.16",
            "537.82",
            "2796.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 423 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1692,
        "options": [
            "1692",
            3384,
            4230,
            3807,
            2538
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 463 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            74,
            "Not possible",
            80,
            25,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen sold a book to Jabari at a price of 111 after giving 68 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "346.88",
        "options": [
            "66.07",
            "82.84",
            "71.89",
            "73.51",
            "346.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 93 . We turned on the cooler for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            93,
            95,
            96,
            117,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            -4,
            22,
            -4,
            -2,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 38 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            36,
            47,
            54,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 58 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            69,
            88,
            42,
            93,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            105,
            143,
            108,
            125,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 106 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            147,
            28,
            101,
            75,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 96, 31, 53. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo consumes 704 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Ahmir is 25 years old. How much calories should Ahmir consume?",
        "answer": 1408,
        "options": [
            1408,
            190,
            364,
            190,
            246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            139,
            151,
            132,
            117,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            32,
            35,
            36,
            43,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "820",
            "4616",
            "343",
            "11700",
            "6591"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 217 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            87,
            "49",
            56,
            16,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Christopher consumes 595 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Yusuf is 21 years old. How much calories should Yusuf consume?",
        "answer": 1190,
        "options": [
            144,
            342,
            241,
            1190,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 30 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            27,
            12,
            22,
            26,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 112 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "33",
            31,
            54,
            70,
            10,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            91,
            85,
            94,
            86,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the cooler for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            68,
            54,
            67,
            71,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tobias is younger than Wilder by 2 years. 6 years ago Wilder was 33 years old. What is Tobias 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "43",
            "45",
            "53",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in ivory is 3010. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12394",
            "12544",
            "7052",
            "1910"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 134 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            23,
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "11",
            25,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 35, 38, 107. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 169 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 165,
        "options": [
            165,
            84,
            103,
            49,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Liam by 4 years. 13 years ago Liam was 29 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "64",
            "46",
            "47",
            "30",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            107,
            122,
            92,
            110,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 48 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            26,
            47,
            52,
            47,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Skyler and Benton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Skyler consumes 2291 calories per day whereas Benton consumes 2464 calories per day. Skyler is stronger than Benton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles sold a book to Marlon at a price of 270 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "964.29",
        "options": [
            "171.32",
            "198.53",
            "175.32",
            "156.98",
            "964.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 60, 52, 68. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            69,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            71,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hector consumes 930 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Markus is 37 years old. How much calories should Markus consume?",
        "answer": 1860,
        "options": [
            276,
            344,
            1860,
            219,
            494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jett and Marlon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jett consumes 2583 calories per day whereas Marlon consumes 2771 calories per day. Jett is more weight than Marlon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 212 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            50,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Legend sold a book to Idris at a price of 302 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "592.16",
        "options": [
            "202.68",
            "592.16",
            "216.95",
            "242.57",
            "220.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 160 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            2,
            25,
            42,
            74,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            -29,
            -2,
            -2,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            62,
            59,
            51,
            72,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 207 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "17",
            73,
            2,
            37,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 109,
        "options": [
            113,
            119,
            114,
            109,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roman sold a book to Colten at a price of 303 after giving 34 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "459.09",
        "options": [
            "258.97",
            "238.21",
            "241.43",
            "226.12",
            "459.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            4268,
            3287,
            3638,
            12,
            3639
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given elephants ? 47 50 49 41 34 14 33 50 7 13 38 16 24 38 10 35 34 22 3 35 7 9 17 40 34 27 15 38 34 20 14 46 6 32 41 15 36 47 37 39 33 38 34 34 22 1 ",
        "answer": "28.46",
        "options": [
            "28.46",
            "142.30",
            "142.30",
            "142.30",
            "85.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson is younger than Musa by 3 years. 5 years ago Musa was 30 years old. What is Kyson 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "44",
            "32",
            "49",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayce consumes 526 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Valentin is 22 years old. How much calories should Valentin consume?",
        "answer": 1052,
        "options": [
            192,
            170,
            1052,
            285,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Titus consumes 882 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Krew is 39 years old. How much calories should Krew consume?",
        "answer": 1764,
        "options": [
            457,
            262,
            1764,
            328,
            214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 618 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2472,
        "options": [
            6180,
            "2472",
            5562,
            3090,
            4326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            1979,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 296 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            51,
            "Not possible",
            44,
            69,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "38*27",
        "options": [
            "111*74",
            "38*27",
            "78*48",
            "106*87",
            "81*90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 53 * 42. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "31*28",
        "options": [
            "77*64",
            "92*44",
            "96*53",
            "88*68",
            "31*28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caden and Bowie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caden consumes 2292 calories per day whereas Bowie consumes 2385 calories per day. Caden is weaker than Bowie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Connor and Brycen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Connor consumes 1808 calories per day whereas Brycen consumes 2008 calories per day. Connor is lighter than Brycen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 305 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            82,
            7,
            12,
            "Not possible",
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 469 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            94,
            89,
            "25",
            87,
            "Not possible",
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adriel runs at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Turner 's place which is 133 km away?",
        "answer": "13.30",
        "options": [
            "66.50",
            "39.90",
            "13.30",
            "53.20",
            "26.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliot and Ridge are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliot consumes 2604 calories per day whereas Ridge consumes 2471 calories per day. Elliot is stronger than Ridge.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in mercury ?",
        "answer": "1540",
        "options": [
            "198",
            "285",
            "273",
            "1540",
            "256"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            2,
            -22,
            0,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 449 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            47,
            15,
            "39",
            "Not possible",
            54,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given tigers ? 14 40 49 13 37 20 42 45 10 3 26 29 32 30 31 4 26 20 13 4 38 25 31 27 17 29 21 41 27 17 8 2 42 46 39 32 24 45 24 47 44 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "26.00",
            "4.00",
            "27.00",
            "2.00",
            "21.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than William by 4 years. 15 years ago William was 27 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "64",
            "46",
            "60",
            "64",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given cats ? 20 28 35 3 7 26 20 21 2 42 39 13 38 6 37 36 3 38 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "69.00",
            "92.00",
            "92.00",
            "69.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Memphis and Lionel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Memphis consumes 1851 calories per day whereas Lionel consumes 2441 calories per day. Memphis is weaker than Lionel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckett and Brixton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckett consumes 1797 calories per day whereas Brixton consumes 1748 calories per day. Beckett is more weight than Brixton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 109 . We turned on the cooler for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            125,
            126,
            132,
            115,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 5 minutes. What is the temperature after 5 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            49,
            62,
            44,
            37,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            36,
            50,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in antimony ?",
        "answer": "3400",
        "options": [
            "111",
            "245",
            "253",
            "187",
            "3400"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kamden sold a book to Niko at a price of 390 after giving 54 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "847.83",
        "options": [
            "272.35",
            "847.83",
            "277.58",
            "253.25",
            "307.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moses and Emery are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moses consumes 2347 calories per day whereas Emery consumes 1584 calories per day. Moses is less weight than Emery.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Louis sold a book to Julio at a price of 186 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "489.47",
        "options": [
            "114.81",
            "126.96",
            "124.33",
            "141.98",
            "489.47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Porter and Merrick are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Porter consumes 1791 calories per day whereas Merrick consumes 2013 calories per day. Porter is lighter than Merrick.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 63 minutes. What is the temperature after 63 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            99,
            103,
            95,
            108,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Drew and Aldo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Drew consumes 2034 calories per day whereas Aldo consumes 2489 calories per day. Drew is stronger than Aldo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Gunnar consumes 564 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Issac is 33 years old. How much calories should Issac consume?",
        "answer": 1128,
        "options": [
            1128,
            127,
            161,
            326,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cruz and Gustavo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cruz consumes 2490 calories per day whereas Gustavo consumes 2791 calories per day. Cruz is lighter than Gustavo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            391,
            3,
            366,
            670,
            676
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brass is 4700. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3146",
            "343",
            "13069",
            "14758",
            "13379"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Patrick and Julien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Patrick consumes 1526 calories per day whereas Julien consumes 2147 calories per day. Patrick is heavier than Julien.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            40,
            20,
            35,
            38,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eric sold a book to Avi at a price of 816 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1511.11",
        "options": [
            "596.49",
            "558.90",
            "606.69",
            "663.41",
            "1511.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Silas and Louie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Silas consumes 2103 calories per day whereas Louie consumes 1760 calories per day. Silas is more weight than Louie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tungsten carbide is 6655. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2142",
            "14236",
            "5702",
            "11145",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 290 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 288,
        "options": [
            274,
            157,
            236,
            254,
            288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 309 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            35,
            25,
            82,
            99,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a tablet in 22 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            32,
            9,
            31,
            77,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 309 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "55",
        "options": [
            46,
            5,
            62,
            "55",
            "Not possible",
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 190 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 181,
        "options": [
            258,
            179,
            181,
            175,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Trevor and Alonso are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Trevor consumes 2402 calories per day whereas Alonso consumes 2142 calories per day. Trevor is weaker than Alonso.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3697",
            "9514",
            "10658",
            "343",
            "14701"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 34 * 49. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "25*41",
        "options": [
            "44*66",
            "51*88",
            "50*80",
            "25*41",
            "42*75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckham and Heath are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckham consumes 1860 calories per day whereas Heath consumes 2174 calories per day. Beckham is less weight than Heath.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Beryllium is 12890. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "2413",
            "1269",
            "10156",
            "4910"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            94,
            100,
            116,
            98,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in mercury ?",
        "answer": "1540",
        "options": [
            "270",
            "277",
            "100",
            "191",
            "1540"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 468 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            51,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            80,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            61,
            23,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            "Not possible",
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luciano sold a book to Achilles at a price of 727 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3304.55",
        "options": [
            "458.68",
            "447.66",
            "523.02",
            "408.43",
            "3304.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            113,
            125,
            112,
            107,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tobias and Joey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tobias consumes 2592 calories per day whereas Joey consumes 1535 calories per day. Tobias is weaker than Joey.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 427 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "63",
        "options": [
            1,
            "Not possible",
            9,
            12,
            "63",
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 71, 46, 63. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper annealed ?",
        "answer": "4760",
        "options": [
            "215",
            "190",
            "180",
            "163",
            "4760"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 87 minutes. What is the temperature after 87 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            87,
            85,
            94,
            79,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 89 minutes. What is the temperature after 89 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            25,
            66,
            57,
            56,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            119,
            107,
            115,
            130,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alonzo and Leandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alonzo consumes 1807 calories per day whereas Leandro consumes 2087 calories per day. Alonzo is heavier than Leandro.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling sold a book to Zaire at a price of 358 after giving 27 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "490.41",
        "options": [
            "294.41",
            "281.89",
            "315.42",
            "297.71",
            "490.41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pierce consumes 860 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Jagger is 40 years old. How much calories should Jagger consume?",
        "answer": 1720,
        "options": [
            1720,
            195,
            453,
            304,
            249
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            13,
            23,
            12,
            -2,
            -7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given martians ? 47 40 14 18 3 35 48 18 8 50 37 17 7 32 9 48 18 11 25 15 43 45 14 20 34 25 19 2 2 25 18 21 29 3 37 42 31 3 ",
        "answer": "20.50",
        "options": [
            "20.50",
            "48.00",
            "29.00",
            "17.00",
            "3.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaden consumes 826 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Isaias is 33 years old. How much calories should Isaias consume?",
        "answer": 1652,
        "options": [
            180,
            237,
            316,
            432,
            1652
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Braylen sold a book to Kylan at a price of 508 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1036.73",
        "options": [
            "360.80",
            "1036.73",
            "404.78",
            "336.42",
            "367.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 263 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 257,
        "options": [
            422,
            412,
            342,
            235,
            257
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            78,
            59,
            55,
            58,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Juan is younger than Miller by 3 years. 5 years ago Miller was 29 years old. What is Juan 's age today?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            "48",
            "31",
            "48",
            "42",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 486 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            69,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            80,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 87 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            92,
            88,
            106,
            88,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5750",
            "3982",
            "1064",
            "343",
            "8138"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            99,
            139,
            118,
            121,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            122,
            115,
            114,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson walks at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Shepherd 's place which is 170 km away?",
        "answer": "17.00",
        "options": [
            "85.00",
            "51.00",
            "68.00",
            "17.00",
            "34.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Quinn and Dennis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Quinn consumes 1600 calories per day whereas Dennis consumes 2344 calories per day. Quinn is lighter than Dennis.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 66 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            88,
            41,
            58,
            79,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Corey and Tommy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Corey consumes 2690 calories per day whereas Tommy consumes 2800 calories per day. Corey is less weight than Tommy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 155 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            56,
            22,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            "Not possible",
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 280 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 272,
        "options": [
            37,
            181,
            12,
            510,
            272
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tobias and Clay are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tobias consumes 2978 calories per day whereas Clay consumes 2373 calories per day. Tobias is more weight than Clay.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 30 minutes. What is the temperature after 30 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            110,
            103,
            106,
            117,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 40, 50, 90. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "right angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 362 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "161",
        "options": [
            65,
            "Not possible",
            "161",
            17,
            100,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            83,
            94,
            73,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 79 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            72,
            66,
            48,
            116,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clayton and Krew are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clayton consumes 2913 calories per day whereas Krew consumes 2621 calories per day. Clayton is more weight than Krew.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 14 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            3,
            11,
            1,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10165",
            "12932",
            "6929",
            "343",
            "5328"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephen sold a book to Crew at a price of 944 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1242.11",
        "options": [
            "1242.11",
            "842.86",
            "791.95",
            "761.29",
            "800.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Matthew consumes 817 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Allan is 36 years old. How much calories should Allan consume?",
        "answer": 1634,
        "options": [
            207,
            1634,
            247,
            299,
            445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "237",
        "options": [
            91,
            51,
            47,
            "Not possible",
            "237",
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 930 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3720,
        "options": [
            9300,
            8370,
            5580,
            "3720",
            6510
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adriel consumes 537 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Cedric is 36 years old. How much calories should Cedric consume?",
        "answer": 1074,
        "options": [
            169,
            211,
            142,
            289,
            1074
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kenneth is younger than Terrell by 5 years. 9 years ago Terrell was 25 years old. What is Kenneth 's age today?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            "53",
            "44",
            "29",
            "62",
            "53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 441 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            10,
            "Not possible",
            31,
            55,
            79,
            "69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Louis and Rodney are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Louis consumes 2933 calories per day whereas Rodney consumes 1501 calories per day. Louis is more weight than Rodney.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Cade consumes 703 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Bodie is 34 years old. How much calories should Bodie consume?",
        "answer": 1406,
        "options": [
            393,
            194,
            1406,
            177,
            271
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyler sold a book to Leroy at a price of 533 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "903.39",
        "options": [
            "378.01",
            "401.36",
            "407.65",
            "442.32",
            "903.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 2 years. 6 years ago Liam was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "33",
            "33",
            "35",
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 399 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            92,
            "Not possible",
            5,
            27,
            "Not possible",
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malcolm walks at a speed of 16 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Kellen 's place which is 159 km away?",
        "answer": "9.94",
        "options": [
            "39.75",
            "9.94",
            "39.75",
            "29.81",
            "19.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in titanium ?",
        "answer": "6070",
        "options": [
            "6070",
            "186",
            "294",
            "296",
            "234"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            98,
            95,
            112,
            132,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            100,
            51,
            "19",
            "Not possible",
            8,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 49 * 49. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "34*41",
        "options": [
            "34*41",
            "60*87",
            "76*84",
            "70*58",
            "77*60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beau sold a book to Edison at a price of 813 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2710.00",
        "options": [
            "521.15",
            "602.22",
            "533.11",
            "2710.00",
            "478.24"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elian consumes 618 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Ty is 38 years old. How much calories should Ty consume?",
        "answer": 1236,
        "options": [
            137,
            221,
            195,
            1236,
            333
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dax and Niko are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dax consumes 1852 calories per day whereas Niko consumes 2960 calories per day. Dax is stronger than Niko.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Gianni sold a book to Boston at a price of 771 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1285.00",
        "options": [
            "1285.00",
            "550.71",
            "593.08",
            "642.50",
            "584.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            21,
            14,
            354,
            10,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            17,
            24,
            16,
            18,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zachary and Dariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zachary consumes 2348 calories per day whereas Dariel consumes 2498 calories per day. Zachary is bulkier than Dariel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Augustus and Fox are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Augustus consumes 2565 calories per day whereas Fox consumes 2190 calories per day. Augustus is more weight than Fox.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in duralumin is 6320. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9844",
            "5907",
            "8589",
            "343",
            "372"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Armando and Julien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Armando consumes 1560 calories per day whereas Julien consumes 2723 calories per day. Armando is bulkier than Julien.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in ivory ?",
        "answer": "3010",
        "options": [
            "123",
            "217",
            "3010",
            "199",
            "156"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than Liam by 2 years. 13 years ago Liam was 28 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "35",
            "50",
            "48",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in annealed tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5220",
        "options": [
            "144",
            "5220",
            "189",
            "175",
            "149"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 216 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            "27",
            35,
            61,
            "Not possible",
            59,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            33,
            6,
            29,
            86,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dallas and Marley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dallas consumes 1931 calories per day whereas Marley consumes 2189 calories per day. Dallas is lighter than Marley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a airpods in 12 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            3,
            1,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dominic and Danny are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dominic consumes 1551 calories per day whereas Danny consumes 1681 calories per day. Dominic is weaker than Danny.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 265 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "101",
        "options": [
            4,
            "Not possible",
            48,
            78,
            81,
            "101"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aiden sold a book to Zaire at a price of 235 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "398.31",
        "options": [
            "195.02",
            "398.31",
            "176.96",
            "166.67",
            "179.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 171 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            31,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            47,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            10,
            18,
            25,
            11,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brantley and Eddie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brantley consumes 1541 calories per day whereas Eddie consumes 1620 calories per day. Brantley is bulkier than Eddie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            8,
            56,
            47,
            "Not possible",
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the cooler for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            56,
            67,
            56,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Conor and Jakob are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Conor consumes 2414 calories per day whereas Jakob consumes 2910 calories per day. Conor is bulkier than Jakob.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Benjamin by 5 years. 10 years ago Benjamin was 26 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "31",
            "41",
            "21",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 63 minutes. What is the temperature after 63 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            -1,
            29,
            37,
            31,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a laptop in 19 minutes. How much time will it take for a 25 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            9,
            18,
            32,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 433 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            58,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            48,
            32,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 56 * 41. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "42*36",
        "options": [
            "65*68",
            "73*67",
            "42*36",
            "70*64",
            "89*57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Calvin sold a book to Felipe at a price of 299 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "467.19",
        "options": [
            "219.85",
            "467.19",
            "232.14",
            "235.43",
            "253.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7865",
            "6866",
            "343",
            "8281",
            "13571"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 202 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            14,
            "Not possible",
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andy sold a book to Ronnie at a price of 825 after giving 7 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "887.10",
        "options": [
            "781.25",
            "797.10",
            "771.03",
            "783.85",
            "887.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "King sold a book to Apollo at a price of 947 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1088.51",
        "options": [
            "838.05",
            "857.79",
            "1088.51",
            "889.20",
            "862.87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis consumes 702 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Gordon is 25 years old. How much calories should Gordon consume?",
        "answer": 1404,
        "options": [
            177,
            1404,
            371,
            203,
            246
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zion and Gary are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zion consumes 2742 calories per day whereas Gary consumes 2038 calories per day. Zion is bulkier than Gary.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 7 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            35,
            "28",
            49,
            42,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 16 watt charger charges a laptop in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 12 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            68,
            48,
            7,
            44,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than William by 3 years. 13 years ago William was 25 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "61",
            "48",
            "61",
            "29",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 490 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            55,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            7,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 450 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            53,
            66,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            98,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 51 * 51. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "47*50",
        "options": [
            "47*50",
            "58*70",
            "92*96",
            "83*62",
            "58*80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            35,
            41,
            48,
            32,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 55 * 48. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "52*32",
        "options": [
            "52*32",
            "93*97",
            "109*66",
            "62*66",
            "61*71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 234 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 233,
        "options": [
            233,
            173,
            404,
            428,
            178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean sold a book to Nelson at a price of 690 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "718.75",
        "options": [
            "663.46",
            "718.75",
            "669.90",
            "668.60",
            "676.47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Augustus and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Augustus consumes 2634 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2502 calories per day. Augustus is weaker than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 232 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            32,
            24,
            98,
            44,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Patrick and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Patrick consumes 2954 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 1590 calories per day. Patrick is heavier than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 31 . We turned on the heater for 113 minutes. What is the temperature after 113 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            15,
            19,
            6,
            37,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            31,
            45,
            36,
            32,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            380,
            724,
            1979,
            30,
            533
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 260 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 251,
        "options": [
            383,
            347,
            377,
            251,
            179
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Milan and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Milan consumes 2843 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2490 calories per day. Milan is more weight than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Julius and Santino are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Julius consumes 1681 calories per day whereas Santino consumes 1851 calories per day. Julius is less weight than Santino.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 359 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            58,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            96,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chance consumes 847 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Cayson is 22 years old. How much calories should Cayson consume?",
        "answer": 1694,
        "options": [
            208,
            458,
            296,
            240,
            1694
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 291 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 281,
        "options": [
            409,
            476,
            128,
            281,
            245
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            108,
            115,
            99,
            110,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sean and Quinton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sean consumes 2566 calories per day whereas Quinton consumes 2112 calories per day. Sean is weaker than Quinton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 80 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            79,
            84,
            137,
            75,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 293 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 286,
        "options": [
            84,
            271,
            181,
            241,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 260 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            59,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            72,
            "Not possible",
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 99 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            84,
            27,
            88,
            105,
            170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 623 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2492,
        "options": [
            6230,
            3115,
            3738,
            5607,
            "2492"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Grant and Case are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Grant consumes 2188 calories per day whereas Case consumes 2162 calories per day. Grant is more weight than Case.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in zinc rolled is 4210. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "5375",
            "914",
            "4074",
            "13999"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 30 watt charger charges a tablet in 60 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            41,
            70,
            4,
            26,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Manuel runs at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jermaine 's place which is 161 km away?",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "115.00",
            "23.00",
            "69.00",
            "115.00",
            "69.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            122,
            120,
            137,
            111,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given kangaroos ? 40 37 15 9 20 34 19 44 25 17 39 32 43 42 5 ",
        "answer": "32.00",
        "options": [
            "40.00",
            "34.00",
            "34.00",
            "5.00",
            "32.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enrique and Kellan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enrique consumes 1817 calories per day whereas Kellan consumes 2991 calories per day. Enrique is lighter than Kellan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in duralumin ?",
        "answer": "6320",
        "options": [
            "235",
            "6320",
            "217",
            "179",
            "293"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Drew is younger than Finnley by 3 years. 7 years ago Finnley was 26 years old. What is Drew 's age today?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            "56",
            "53",
            "56",
            "46",
            "30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 127 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            66,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            24,
            93,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bennett and Lee are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bennett consumes 2998 calories per day whereas Lee consumes 2209 calories per day. Bennett is lighter than Lee.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a laptop in 45 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            51,
            75,
            67,
            6,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 184 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            48,
            52,
            40,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in gold is 3240. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10606",
            "5348",
            "343",
            "14678",
            "12819"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 179 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            15,
            88,
            "Not possible",
            17,
            "29",
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            -3,
            5,
            20,
            15,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "John consumes 926 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Korbyn is 37 years old. How much calories should Korbyn consume?",
        "answer": 1852,
        "options": [
            216,
            495,
            346,
            266,
            1852
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in mercury ?",
        "answer": "1540",
        "options": [
            "118",
            "1540",
            "315",
            "265",
            "125"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 73 . We turned on the cooler for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            91,
            63,
            104,
            75,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronin sold a book to Benedict at a price of 428 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "713.33",
        "options": [
            "324.24",
            "713.33",
            "329.23",
            "305.71",
            "356.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 132 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            44,
            157,
            99,
            129,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber butyl is 1830. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12094",
            "4113",
            "11642",
            "343",
            "8135"
        ]
    }
]